Good evening, everybody.
This is Matthew McConaughey saying
welcome to the Graham Norton Show.
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
Oh!
Wow!
I jumped!
Oh, I'm keen! I'm very keen!
Hello!
CHEERING
Good evening!
Yes, yes.
Thank you.
You're all very welcome to the show.
Oh, so many great guests
for you tonight.
My sofa's going to be like Theresa
May in Parliament this week.
Totally stuffed!
God love her. On Tuesday,
the Prime Minister managed to lose
three House of Commons votes
in the space of an hour.
An hour!
In one of the debates,
things were so bad,
she actually received fewer votes
than Noel Edmonds. Yeah!
At least he had
the good grace to leave.
By the way, did you know this?
I only found out this week that
I'm A Celebrity, after they make
them eat those disgusting things,
they have a way of getting
the celebrities to vomit.
LAUGHTER
That would work, wouldn't it?
HE MAKES A RETCHING NOISE
I do feel a bit…
The government was also found
to be in contempt of Parliament
over access to legal advice
on the Brexit deal.
This is the man who gave the advice.
There he is. Mm!
That's the Attorney General,
Geoffrey Cox.
Apparently, it's quite unusual
to see "Cox" addressing Parliament.
LAUGHTER
Well…
LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE
Let's get some guests on!
CHEERING
Later, we'll have an amazing
performance of the new hit single
by Mark Ronson
featuring Miley Cyrus.
CHEERING
I know!
And they'll be chatting as well.
But first, he's one of our
most-loved chefs and restaurateurs
who's published
20 bestselling cook books.
Here to tell us about his latest,
Jamie Cooks Italy,
please welcome Jamie Oliver!
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
Woo!
- Hello.
- How are you? Nice to see you.
- Nice to see you.
Have a seat, do.
It is that time! It is that time!
She's an Oscar-nominated actress,
pop sensation
and one of Hollywood's
hottest rising stars.
Now she's saving the world
in the new action movie Bumblebee.
It's Hailee Steinfeld!
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
Woo!
Sparkling!
- Hello, my dear.
- Hello.
- Lovely to see you.
- Thank you so much.
- Hailee, Jamie.
- Hello, hello.
Starring alongside Hailee, he's
a 16-time World Wrestling champion
and WWE Superstar who's now
kicking ass on the big screen.
It's John Cena!
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
Woo!
That's him!
- How are you?
- Thanks so much.
- John Cena, everybody!
CHEERING
And he's gone from king of romcom
to Oscar-winning Hollywood icon.
Now he's back on our screens
in White Boy Rick.
Please welcome back
the great Matthew McConaughey!
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
Woo!
Lovely to see you.
Hey.
Sit, sit, sit on the seats!
Welcome, everybody. Hello,
how are you doing?
- Are you good?
- Very good.
You all look well. You look happy.
Yeah, it's all good.
You were saying backstage
I'm the only one who didn't get
- the memo about dress code.
- Well, is it dress down Friday?
I don't know about that, if it is
in the McConaughey household.
Everyone else made an effort!
LAUGHTER
Now, listen, we are very
lucky on the show.
We often have very
esteemed, acclaimed couches.
But I think this is the most
varied couch of achievement.
Lots of different achievements
on this couch.
Hailee Steinfeld, Oscar-nominated.
Well done, you. Congratulations!
APPLAUSE
So that's already very impressive.
This is impressive/annoying.
How old were you when you got
nominated for an Oscar?
- I was 14.
- Wowsers!
I know!
Nothing. You've done nothing
with your lives!
- That was, of course, for True Grit.
- Yes.
There you go. Look at her there!
Oh, the baby!
And we have to say,
welcome to John Cena!
- CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
- Very excited to be here.
- This is my first time.
- It's the first time.
And normally, it's fine, everybody
walks on to the theme music.
But I felt bad making you
do it to ours
because you are probably
our first guest ever
who has their own theme music.
- Yeah!
- Yeah.
- It comes with the territory.
So, if we play it, would you like
to come on to your own theme music?
Well, there's a trick. It's kind of
an audience participation thing.
They'll love that! They will.
CHEERING
They will love it.
It's a catchy tune. Lots of brass.
And the trumpets go somewhat like…
♪ Da-da-da-daaa!
Da-da-da-daaa. ♪
And the WWE audience is very excited
and very dedicated
and they sing along with the brass.
And…the chorus is…
♪ John Cena sucks
♪ John Cena sucks… ♪
It's their way of
showing they like me!?
- So are we going to do this?
- Yeah, let's do it.
- One, two, three.
AUDIENCE: ♪ John Cena sucks
♪ John Cena sucks! ♪
Thank you, I think we're warmed up.
OK, let's do this. OK.
- OK.
- Wow!
- OK. Here we go. Here we go.
MICROPHONE ECHOES:
Ladies and gentlemen,
please welcome WWE superstar,
John Cena!
CHEERING
DRAMATIC MUSIC
- AUDIENCE:
- ♪ John Cena!
Here we go, here we go!
- AUDIENCE:
- ♪ John Cena sucks!
♪ John Cena sucks
♪ John Cena sucks! ♪
Hurray!
That's my life
in about 20 seconds!
That's your intro song?
Into the ring?
Oh, yeah.
And tens of thousands of people
will say
♪ John Cena sucks! ♪
So, every night I go out with
a smile on my face, get told I suck.
The more you put your hand there,
the louder they get.
- Oh, man, yes!
- Yeah.
- Oh, man.
Even in the reverse, too.
If you act like it doesn't get you,
they know they're getting at you.
There's no way around it.
And talking of music,
this is such a bizarre thing.
Matthew, one of your
standout performances
in The Wolf Of Wall Street…
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
You were amazing in it.
Now, you've talked about this
before.
What would you call the beating,
the humming beating thing?
- HE HUMS:
- Mm-hm-mm.
I'd call it awesome.
- So, the humming and the beating has now been sampled.
- Yes.
It's been sampled quite a few times.
I hear it a lot.
It's been sampled
on this dance track.
So this is your Wolf Of Wall Street
thing in a song.
DANCE MUSIC FEATURING
MATTHEW'S HUMMING
♪ Where are my residuals?
- Isn't this great?
- ♪ Give me the mailbox money!
I think that's the name of the song!
APPLAUSE
Now, here's the weird thing.
So, you kind of think, oh, right,
someone on the couch
got sampled in a song.
He's not the only one on the couch
who's been sampled in a song.
Jamie Oliver is also in a song.
LAUGHTER
This is the Jamie Oliver
Pukka Techno Remix.
Oh, for God's sake!
DANCE MUSIC
♪ Pukka, pukka, pukka
♪ Pukka, pukka, pukka…
Which part are you doing?
♪ Garlic and lemon, oh, yeah!
Garlic and lemon, oh, yeah!
Garlic and lemon, oh, yeah! ♪
- It's good!
- Garlic and lemon! Pukka.
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah.
APPLAUSE
- Christmas, your house!
- Well, yeah.
Pukka!
Oh, dear! Is that real?
That song? Oh, we didn't make it.
No, that's real.
- Who does that stuff?
- I don't know!
I rather enjoyed it!
Do people club to that?
Maybe they did.
I don't think they do now.
The moment may have passed.
Now, we're going to start tonight
with Bumblebee.
This stars Hailee Steinfeld
and John Cena.
It's previewing next weekend
and then it opens everywhere
on Christmas Eve.
And even with the poster, you can
tell this is a Transformers movie.
- But this is a kind of origins movie, it goes back, right?
- Yeah.
It does, yes.
It takes place in the '80s.
It precedes all the Transformers
films that we've seen and love.
And it's the origin story
of Bumblebee
so we get to really see
where he comes from
and how he becomes
what we know him to be.
And you're a young woman
who kind of bonds with Bumblebee?
Yes, so I play a character named
Charlie Watson, she's turning 18,
she's working a dead-end job
to save for a car
because a car, in her mind,
and in most people's,
represents independence and freedom.
And she is struggling with…
I mean, the struggles
of growing up as a teenager,
trying to figure out
who you are and what you're good at,
what your voice is.
And she's suffering from a loss.
She lost her father.
And so she's trying to feel
understood by somebody
because that was her person,
that was her best friend
and that was the person she felt
really saw her and heard her.
And she loses that,
only to hope to find something
that fills that gap.
And on her way to finding her
freedom and independence and a car,
she discovers that the one she ends
up with isn't just a car.
No.
And John, your character
is quite ambiguous.
In wrestling terms, are you more
of a babyface or more of a heel?
You have done your homework, sir!
Look at you!
- Google works here!
- My goodness!
OK, for those not playing
inside baseball,
a babyface is a good guy,
a heel is a bad guy.
And in this movie
I am both a heel and a babyface.
- Ooh, that is true, that is true! We see all sides, yes.
- Indeed.
This is a clip. This is the two
of you and Bumblebee in action.
Get out and move away
from the vehicle!
Stay cool, Bee.
What's going on?
Hey!
- Come on, come on!
- Stop it!
Let go of me!
Take it down!
- Run!
- No, don't run! Do not run!
She ran.
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
Good!
That thing looks so real.
The Bumblebee, you really forget,
it seems crazy that
that thing isn't there.
Not at all, it is not there at all!
Not even in the slightest,
unfortunately.
The cost of a Transformer
minus CGI is about 7.
LAUGHTER
It is a long piece of PVC pipe
and a tennis ball.
But they've done an amazing job with
that, they really have.
Fantastic.
And this is set in 1987.
So, Hailee, what were
you doing in 1987?
Well…
LAUGHTER
Um…
No. I wasn't born yet.
So, yeah, this little dive back
into the '80s,
I had some interesting conversations
with my parents
about their experiences
in the '80s.
Er, John, I've heard quite a bit
from you…about the '80s.
You were only ten, in fairness.
'87 was a tough year, dude!
I was a young boy growing up in
New England. '87 was a tough year.
The Red Sox just got whupped in the
World Series by the New York Mets.
The New England Patriots
got their keisters kicked in
by the Chicago Bears.
That was a whole year of me
walking with my head down.
These were dark days!
And you want to bring it up,
like, "You were only ten"?
'87, man. '87.
But I like that Hailee, in this
film, you were using props that,
to my mind, were just like,
oh, yeah, that's out there.
But you were dealing with things
you'd never really seen before?
Yes, I had to be shown
how to use a Walkman.
LAUGHTER
And there were other items
that I came across
that I tried for a moment
to act as if I knew what it was
but I didn't get away with it
for long without asking.
But I do have to say
our director, Travis Knight,
as a child of the '80s and a fan
of the toys and of the movies,
he really not only brought to life
this incredible world of the '80s
that feels really authentic,
he created a space for me.
And I never felt entirely
out of place in any way.
It was really made so I could step
right in and feel right at home.
But John Cena, this is a weird kind
of almost a link to Bumblebee
because when you were starting off
in wrestling,
you had a persona that, am I right,
was sort of half-man, half-machine?
- Was that the idea?
- Yes, that's correct.
- This was Prototype?
- It was awful.
LAUGHTER
Yes, you want to try to find
a persona or,
here's some more inside baseball
for you, a gimmick…
- Oh!
- …where it describes you as a character
so, when you walk out,
people notice you
and you can describe
your character.
But these are not gimmicks,
this is real?
Well. I mean, if they work…
- Yes.
- It's…
It's a trial and error process
with a lot of errors.
And my first try was The Prototype,
which was half-man and half-machine.
And 100% crap!
LAUGHTER
But given that
you're not half a machine,
how did you demonstrate
you were a machine?
Well, I used this ability to talk
rather monotone,
and would say things authoritative,
and just,
"When I said, I would kick your ass
at the fairgrounds on Sunday,"
I would rewind it
and say it again for you…
IMITATES SPEECH ON REWIND
"…I would kick your ass
at the fairground."
Yes. And it didn't work?
You… No!
- No, it didn't!
- That's a good one!
- It worked on one. I have one.
- I'm in!
You found huge success as John Cena.
Imagine that! I figure I need
to come up with some sort of name.
Doesn't every…
Every wrestler has a name, though?
Yes, and people think that, like,
hey, man,
how do you make up
the name John Cena?
It's like, no, dude,
I'd have made up Dick Hammerbush
or something cool like that.
- No, not Dick Hammerbush.
- Or something, I don't know.
That's a start!
No-one's letting you go out
with that, no.
But they actually think that
John Cena is a gimmick name
but, no, that's actually…
Through all the presentation that
is WWE, I'm stuck with John Cena.
Are you a wrestling fan, Jamie?
I used to love wrestling.
When we were much younger,
about the same time as Transformers,
back in the day, we had Big Daddy.
CHEERING
The Giant Haystack.
GRAHAM CHORTLES
No, I used to love it.
I thought it was just fantastic.
By the way, I'm John Cena.
All these awesome names… You know,
the Ultimate Drooler or, like…
- No, nothing.
- Wrestlers like to have signature moves.
- Yes.
- And one of yours is the You Can't See Me.
- That's correct.
Is that true that came out
of your family somehow?
Yeah, I was dared to do it,
so I was actually making the music
for my own theme song that you just
heard
and so finely serenaded to me…
thank you very much…
and we played it for my brother.
The first time he heard it…
50 Cent's crew had a really popular
song called In Da Club…
and he heard it the first time and,
instead of dancing,
he was our litmus test to see
what songs were good and what songs
were bad, he did this.
Oh, my gosh!
I'm like,
"Dude, what are you doing?"
He's like, "No, everybody
does this, man!"
And I guess this was
from 50 Cent's video.
He's like, "You won't do it on TV."
What the hell have I got to lose?
What are they going to do, fire me?
Of course I'll do it on TV.
But, instead of doing
this, I did this.
And, now, for 15 years…
LAUGHTER
…because of a dare…
…I've been doing this.
And I'll do you one better…
people actually think I'm invisible.
There will be people who look
at this couch and be like,
"Why is there nobody
next to McConaughey?"
They said John Cena would be there,
but we can't see him.
So, you never know.
You remember Hacksaw Jim Duggan
and King Kong Bundy
and Skandor Akba and Kerry Von
Erich, who carried the Claw.
I got kicked out of…
We're talking Texas wrestling.
I got kicked out of Hirsch Coliseum
in Shreveport for pelting
Skandor Akba with a bag of tomatoes.
Skandor Akba was a man dressed
as a sheikh that used to throw fire.
Yes, and he managed King Kong Bundy,
who was 484lb
and one of the missing links,
parts unknown…
He had a green face,
spit green mist.
- They sound really good!
- Good stuff.
Entertaining!
And I'm John Cena.
And he's got this!
APPLAUSE DROWNS SPEECH
Listen, we'd like to move
on to Matthew's film.
The film is called White Boy Rick.
It opens tonight.
This is a tough tale.
- Yes.
- And it's based on a true story.
- Mm-hm.
- So you play Rick Senior.
- Rick Senior.
This is a story about Rick Junior,
the young man who plays my son,
Richie Merritt. True story…
this was the youngest informant
in American history.
He… This is in Cleveland
in the '80s.
And the FBI came to him to be
an informant and help him try
and bring down these dealers
and track where the money
and how far up the political ladder
it went in Detroit at this time.
Well, if you're going to be
a good informant, trying
to bring down dealers, you need to
be dealing yourself. So he was 15.
He gets busted by the state.
And, at that time,
it was the 600g law,
which means, if you get busted
with over 600g,
you go to prison for life,
even at that age.
And, obviously, he and his dad
go to the Feds, who had him
as an informant, and said,
"Do you have our back?"
And they could neither confirm
nor deny that he was an informant,
and he was in jail for just over 27
years and he got out
- four months ago.
- Wow.
And this father… I've heard you
in interviews say that this
is the character that's furthest
away from you.
Yeah, well, in the fact that this
guy… I mean, this role is
my sad country song. I've never…
What I mean by that is, you know,
"Mamma got run over by a train
"the day I got let out of jail."
It's like bad luck on top of bad
luck. This guy is a loo-ser.
He loses continually.
He's a guy whose heart's
in the right place,
he has all the want-to,
but he's really a bad dad.
He doesn't have anything of the
follow-through. One of those
fathers… One of the first things
that gave me a track on the guy,
and we all know those fathers that
want to be best friends
with their children at all times,
and it's usually not the best recipe
for raising a child that's ready
to go out into the world,
and this was one of those fathers
who couldn't lay down
consequences for his children,
and there was a lot
that he and his family had to pay
for that.
Listen, we've got a clip.
This is you as the father having
a disagreement with your daughter,
who is played by our own Bel Powley.
- She's wonderful in this.
- You might know her.
- She was in Informer.
- Tremendous actress.
- Here we go.
- Dad, don't go!
- Get back.
- Get off of me!
Get back in the house, Dawn.
Go in the house and get dressed.
Stop! Dad!
Stop, no.
No!
Dad!
Oh, Christ. Keep going!
I've got it under control.
You don't need to stop the car, Pop.
Everything's fine.
Don't get out of the car.
Everything is not fine!
A man just ran out of your house,
almost dents my Imperial.
You don't have a goddamn
thing under control!
I hate you!
You're going to let her
talk to you like that?
Go in the goddamn house! I've got
this under control, all right?
- It ain't under control.
- Ray, stay out of it.
Looks like Richard's
having a bad day.
No, Ma, I'm not having a bad day.
My son and I walked into the lion's
den this morning and walked out
- with the golden fleece. Ain't that right, Ricky?
- That's right.
- You are pathetic! Both of you!
And put some clothes on, will you?
We're going for custard.
APPLAUSE
So, yeah, it's a little
romantic comedy.
Now, obviously, somebody
played your mother there,
but your own mother, I know she
likes to visit you on set,
- so did she visit you on this set?
- Yes, she did.
- Oh, there's your mum.
A lot of families like to visit
sets, because they get to take
pictures with people and it's fun,
but your mum's, like, hustling
- when she gets there.
- Absolutely. My mother…
Yes, she says she wants
to come to see me.
We already had that discussion.
Mum, if I was an accountant
in Chicago, you wouldn't
want to come and see me
all the time.
"No, I wouldn't, because what do
I want to do, son?
"I want to get in that movie."
And she's been to all my sets,
and she's persistent,
and she has a pitch that she's not
got tired of and she continues.
She's 86 now, and she comes to me
and says, "Who's the person on set
"that can make it happen?
"Who's the one with the money?"
And I'll go, like, "That guy."
And I've learned to send her
to the wrong people.
Even then, her pitch is this.
OK.
"Remake The Graduate.
"What, what's so funny?
No, it's a great idea.
"Look, I'm the Anne Bancroft
character.
"Matthew is the
Dustin Hoffman character."
And what does everyone
right away say?
"Wait a minute, that's pretty bent."
She's immediately like, "Oh, knock
it off. I've seen it before.
"It's not that big of a deal."
She wants to do
a remake of The Graduate.
She started off just
wanting to do Golden Girls,
but that didn't happen. Now she
wants to do a remake of The Graduate
and she wants me to be
the Dustin Hoffman part.
Yeah, there's Freudian stuff in
there.
Right?
Has anybody said
they'll think about it?
You know what, I… No.
I mean, it could kind of
work, but I don't know.
But she was kind of responsible
on setting you towards
your path of stardom. Didn't she
enter you in a competition
when you were quite young?
Yes, she entered me
in a lot of competitions.
It's kind of part and parcel
to the same moment
I just explained to you.
There was one competition
which was a poetry competition,
and one of those poetry
competitions,
there was Little Mr Texas. Let me
just tell a Little Mr Texas one.
This is the same woman.
You'll know exactly what I mean.
We've got a picture
of you as Little Mr Texas.
So, this picture there, right.
Little Mr Texas, right?
She tells me at eight
years old in 1977,
"You won Little Mr Texas,"
so I was Little Mr Texas.
Until about 26 years old…
how many years is that,
18 years later? One day, I've got
the picture, and I decide I'm just
going to zoom in on that trophy.
Can you zoom in on that trophy?
- No, we can't, I don't think.
- Well, anyway, it says runner-up.
LAUGHTER
It says runner-up!
APPLAUSE
Same lady. I enter a poetry contest
and I write a nice poem
and I think I showed you.
She goes, "Yeah, that's not
bad, go try it again."
She says, "That's not bad either,
but have a look at this poem."
And I look at it and she says,
"Isn't that a good one?"
It says, "If all that I would want
to do is meet to sit
"and talk to you, would you listen?"
And it was EE Cummings. And I was
like, "Yeah, that's a good one."
She goes, "Do you like it?" I go,
"yeah, I like it." She goes,
"Then it's yours." I go, "What do
you mean?" She goes,
"Well, you understand it.
It means something to you.
"Therefore it's yours." I go,
"What are you saying?"
She goes, "Write that."
And I go, "And sign EE Cummings?"
She goes, "No, you can sign it
because you understand it."
I won the contest.
Yeah, she's a bit of an outlaw.
Don't try this at home.
Now, Jamie, you were born into this.
You were like Jesus.
You were born in an inn.
I was born in an inn, yes.
Because your parents,
they ran a pub.
They still do,
43 beautiful years later.
- Wow.
- In Essex.
- Yeah.
SCATTERED CHEERING
And, yeah, it's…
That was my whole life,
growing up in the pub.
Locals… I still think the pub
is the most democratic,
brilliant place on earth.
Everyone's welcome.
I learnt a lot about people.
That was my real school, I think.
And it kind of runs in the family,
because one of your grannies
- was a publican as well.
- Yes.
And then your other granny,
was it Granny Betty?
Yes.
- Is Granny Betty still around?
- No, sadly, she left…
Well, both have sadly left us now.
But Betty used to be part of the big
family Christmas, didn't she?
- Massively.
- Why did you pick…?
It seemed like you picked
on Granny Betty.
Not really.
She loved a bit of attention.
We've obviously done Christmas
specials for the last 20 years
and she's,
"Oh, I love this, this is great!"
And she used to come and do
a bit of filming with us.
She's very cuddly,
very gorgeous, and I think
Christmas is about family.
But she used to come and
stay with us at Christmas as well,
and this is a brilliant thing to do.
Do you have Christmas crackers in
America?
We don't,
- but I just found out what they are.
- Good lad. Is it the same one?
- It's not a euphemism?
- Well, that depends.
OK. You can make them yourself…
The type that you hang
on to and yank.
Yes.
And something fun comes out.
LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE
- Christmas cracker.
- Yeah.
- Hailee's mind is going crazy now.
- I'm really trying to follow here.
A Christmas cracker,
you put on the place setting
of what you would call
the Thanksgiving dinner,
which we call Christmas dinner.
And you have the cracker,
it's basically just an empty
toilet roll with another
empty toilet roll… it's really
weird when you think about it…
cut in half, and then you wrap it up
and tie a little thing
- and it looks beautiful.
- All right.
And then they thought,
to make it a bit more fun
in the '60s, they put a cap,
you know, from a cap gun so,
when you pull it, it goes pssssh…
OK.
And then you put a joke in there
and a present in there and
a hat in there.
- It's normal, right?
- Yeah.
You put it inside the toilet roll?
Yeah. I'll show you later.
It's not a big gift, Matthew.
It's not…
All of the crackers, even the posh
ones, have rubbish gifts,
and I personally think
the jokes are rubbish as well,
so I have this thing called
hack the cracker,
which is brilliant, cos you can
kind of strategically look around
the table at all the characters
and then you hack
into one side of the cracker. You
pull out the joke,
you pull out the rubbish toy,
and then you can procure toys
that make people feel good or bad
about themselves, right?
So, in the case of my nan,
she just got a new boyfriend
after losing my poor grandad,
many years later, though,
and I went into Boots and I got
an empty packet, I said,
"Can I have an empty
packet of Viagra, please?"
And they went, "What do you want?"
"Yes, please." So I got a pack.
They were very helpful.
And then I got some Smarties
and filled them up,
put them in there, bang them in
there, wrapped it up.
Christmas Day, put the name
on the cracker, she opens it,
present comes out, Viagra,
boyfriend next to her…
Her face was like…
"I went, no, Nan, don't worry,
it's only Smarties."
And she went, "Oh."
APPLAUSE
Now, oddly, grandmothers play a huge
part in your new book.
- They do.
- This is Jamie Cooks Italy and it's out now.
So, this is you…
It took a long time, this book.
- I mean, how long?
- Nearly two and a half years.
- Wow.
It was a big job.
And I really had to do it,
because I believed it was the last
generation of nonnas
that grew up without gas,
electric, all the mod cons,
like the real cooks,
and we needed to catch them
before they passed on.
So, we had to pull our finger out.
But…
How did you find them, the
nonnas?
Well, we have researchers.
- What do you mean, nonnas?
- Italian grandmothers.
- OK.
Like there's one, Nonna Miriam.
It sounds really romantic
but, actually, technically,
filming and documenting cooking
with nonnas sounds great,
but it takes hours.
It's slow production.
So, we were like a year and a half
over budget, over time,
but we did get to document the most
incredible recipes,
techniques and all the things
that they were brilliant at.
Basically, it's like going…
You know in Star Wars,
when Luke goes to see Yoda?
I basically went to see 50 Yodas.
And they were, like,
the sort of Zen,
ninja warrior masters of cooking,
and they were teaching me how to use
the Force and uncook.
And what that means is
we're trained to cook proficiently,
and they are like, "No, no.
This is how we do it.
"We crack it, we rip it,
we tear it, we get amongst it."
And actually, the nonnas were
answering a lot of the questions
that we talk about in
the press today…
waste, nutrition,
taking a little a long way,
you know, cooking on a small budget.
They were brilliant.
It strikes me, you know, there's
some really ambitious things
in here, but there's more basic
things like pizza, say.
Did they teach you, kind of,
new techniques,
new ideas about some things
like that?
Yeah, because a lot of it
is about simplicity,
so there's stuff that you can
put together in ten minutes,
but you slow cook it over the day,
like six, seven hours,
and it's tender and delicious.
There's versions of what
we would call the bolognese in
different shapes and forms
that will just blow your mind.
Then we're in the north,
and we're meeting the people
who are now 85 that used to pick
the rice for the risotto,
and we learn all about the risotto,
and then quick salads,
quick pastas and, of course,
you've got the pizzas in there,
but really I think I learned a lot
about soul and what not to put in,
you know, about restraint.
The most important ingredient
is restraint, and I'm sure
it's the same in acting.
It's sort of maybe what you don't
say more than what you do.
I don't know. It's about being
confident and working
with what you've got.
John, I know you were
a big fan of pizza.
Is it called Zeppe's?
Zeppe's. Zeppe's kept me alive, man.
- Yeah.
- I mean for real, they kept me alive.
You were working in a bar.
I was doing any job I could
to make any money I could and I was
bouncing at a bar next door.
This is a strip of stores on
a beach in Southern California.
And I was trying to just get by
because the cost of living out there
is atrocious.
And the place next door was a
deep-dish pizza place
called Zeppe's.
And they ran a promotion.
If you could eat a 12-slice deep
dish pizza in one sitting,
you get it free and you get
a coupon for another pizza…
After a week I put them sons
of bitches out of business!
LAUGHTER
They stopped the promotion halfway
through the week and literally
closed down shortly thereafter.
- You closed them down?
- Yeah!
For about a week and a half
I was Zeppe's pizza eating champion,
thank you very much!
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
Yes, you're damn right!
I have to ask you, you're still
wrestling,
- you're still in tiptop condition?
- Yeah, my next match is December 26,
- Madison Square Garden.
- Oh, my God!
- Wow!
For the holidays I'm going to see
Bumblebee like 200 times,
just like everybody here!
And, then, right after that,
I'm going to WWE.
Wow!
I've seen you do a thing, I know
you're in a suit but can you do
- the dead lift thing?
- Yeah, yeah, hold on.
- Space… Come here…
- No, no!
- It's easy!
- Oh, no, no!
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
It's totally easy!
- Don't now slam me on my back!
- Yes!
So the take-off's easy.
But the landing… My goodness!
So we're going to set you down
gently!
Thank you, thank you!
I'm an elderly gentleman!
And a good sport.
And a very good sport.
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
But let me tell you something…
…December 26th in the Madison
Square Garden won't be so gentle!
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
You can't see me!
You found that so…
And that was ridiculous…
Yeah, that was weird!
That was like a machine!
Amazing!
Right, it's time to
meet my next guests.
One is a five-time Grammy-winning
record producer
and the other is one
of the world's biggest pop stars.
Please welcome Mark Ronson
and Miley Cyrus!
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
There they are!
- MILEY:
- Hi!
Very good to see you.
- How are you?
- Good to see you. Very well.
All move down so that
we can all sit in. Slide down.
There goes Mark and Miley.
Welcome, hello, hello, hello!
Thank you for having us!
God, no, thrilled you're here,
thank you very much!
Before we say another thing,
we should congratulate Mark Ronson
on a Golden Globe nomination!
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
- Yeah!
- Very exciting, yeah.
This was for A Star Is Born?
This is for the song Shallow that
I co-wrote on A Star Is Born
and it's super exciting.
Yeah, Oscars to follow! Nice!
By the way, do you all know each
other? Miley, who do you know?
Hi, everybody. I think we've worked
together a couple of times.
We did the VMAs together.
We almost worked together.
When? Now?
And then on Magnum? Magnum?
Did you even get…?
No, but I was supposed to!
Afterwards we're going to hang out.
I told them I was going to take them
to GAY but not tonight.
Do you guys want to switch places?
No, we're OK.
I met Mark here just recently in
Sicily.
In a steam room.
Yes, together.
I walked into a steam room
and I was like,
"Oh, this is interesting."
You don't mind me saying I'm a big
fan of your work and you seem
really cool so I sit down for a bit.
And he started talking to me
and he was like,
"We're going to jump in this ice
bucket bath as well."
So I didn't want to look a hunk,
so I was, like,
"OK, I've never done that
but that sounds cool."
And I get in and it's the most
freezing thing
I've ever felt in my entire life.
But I'm next to Matthew McConaughey
in this tiny tub
and I want to look tough.
And he just looks at me
and he's like, "Breathe." So…
LAUGHTER
So now I take this cold shower every
single morning, an ice cold shower.
And I think of you every morning!
I'm not joking.
Som thank you for letting us have
this.
That's nice.
We're having a little mini-reunion
here! That's very nice.
So, listen. Mark and Miley,
here you are together.
So how did this
collaboration come about?
Was it kind of Team Miley
calling Team Mark Ronson?
Or how did this happen?
This is Mark Ronson stalking
Miley Cyrus for four years!
He has a story that I don't
remember exactly this way.
Do you want to tell
your story that you made up?
Yeah!
I saw Miley on television singing
on the Saturday Night Live
40th anniversary and I knew she
could sing and everything
but I saw her singing Paul Simon,
50 Ways To Leave Your lover,
in a way that just…
I was just transfixed.
So, I got her number,
I don't know if it was legal or not.
And I starting texting
and I just said,
"Hey, if you ever want
to make some music…"
And then four days went by, nothing.
This is the part I don't remember.
I feel like I must have
sent an emoji at least!
The broken heart emoji is great
to have cos when people text us
that they love the song you just put
the broken heart emojis.
I think you would text me
back after a few weeks
and write, "What's up?"
Probably at, like, four in the
morning, maybe?
Yeah.
And that went on for four years?
What we believe, I believe.
My family, we've always talked
about timing and trusting
the universe and always trusting
the timing and that everything
always works out when it should,
and I think… We've said it
multiple times to each
other in the studio that
at any time before this would
have not been right
and any time after this
would have been too far away.
I think it's perfect timing
with this song at the time that
it's out in the world. That's why we
made the video that we made
and the visuals that we've created.
It's just a timely song for me
and my personal life and what's
going on in the world,
so I wouldn't have it
any other way than sitting
with you right now, right here.
This song only came because of where
we were and how we met, and I agree.
Cosmic.
Everyone's talking about this
extraordinary video,
and am I right in thinking
that the whole car chase,
the concept,
was this down to you, Miley?
Well, he was very trusting.
I had this idea originally…
We've worked with each other
on multiple songs on my next record,
and we worked on this song
for Mark's new album, but we didn't
know what was going to come first.
Oh, we're going to watch it?
- Well, little bits, yeah.
- There's some old ladies
kissing in the hot tub.
It's all crazy.
But the budget on this thing…
I mean, this is like a movie.
That's what we wanted.
I had this idea of, for the music
that we're working on,
having this idea of putting a car
in places that it shouldn't be
and putting it inside a living room,
inside a club, and, then,
when me and Mark decided this
was the song I was going to use
coming out of my blackout,
and for his new record,
his first single, and we thought,
what is actually heartbreaking to us
in society every single day?
I think it's waking up
to new devastating news of violence
and judgment and hypocrisy,
so to make a video that's very
timely, and it's about a deeper
heartbreak than just losing love
in a romance or a relationship,
but what really breaks us
apart every single day.
Listen, your car awaits. We might
have to pay waiting
if you don't hurry up. So, if you'd
like to make your way over.
- Yes, please.
- Let's do this. OK.
CHEERING
There they go.
APPLAUSE
So, performing Nothing Breaks
Like A Heart
it is Mark Ronson
featuring Miley Cyrus!
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
♪ This world can hurt you
♪ It cuts you deep and leaves a scar
♪ Things fall apart
♪ But nothing breaks like a heart
♪ Ya, nothing breaks like a heart
♪ I heard you on
the phone last night
♪ We live and die by
pretty lies, you know it
♪ We both know it
♪ These silver bullet cigarettes
♪ This burnin' house
There's nothing left
♪ It's smokin', we both know it
♪ We got all night to fall in love
♪ But just like that we fall apart
♪ We're broken
♪ And nothing, nothing,
nothing going to save us now
♪ Well, there's broken silence
like thunder crashing in the dark
♪ Crash in the dark
♪ And there's broken records
spin endless circles in the bar
♪ Spin round in the bar
♪ This world can hurt you
♪ It cuts you deep and leaves a scar
♪ Things fall apart
But nothing breaks like a heart
♪ Ya, nothing breaks like a heart
♪ We'll leave each other cold
as ice and high and dry
♪ The desert wind is blowing
It's blowing
♪ Remember what you said to me
♪ We were drunk in love
in Tennessee and I hold it
♪ We both know it
♪ That nothing, nothing,
nothing going to save us now
♪ Nothing, nothing,
♪ Well, there's broken silence
by thunder crashing in the dark
♪ Crash in the dark
♪ And there's broken records
spin endless circles in the bar
♪ Spin round in the bar
♪ This world can hurt you
♪ It cuts you deep
and leaves a scar
♪ Things fall apart
♪ But nothing breaks like a heart
♪ Ya, nothing breaks like a heart
♪ Nothing breaks like a heart
♪ That nothing, nothing,
nothing going to save us now
♪ Nothing, nothing,
♪ Well, there's broken silence
by thunder crashing in the dark
♪ Crash in the dark
♪ And there's broken records
spin endless circles in the bar
♪ Spin round in the bar
♪ This world can hurt you
♪ It cuts you deep and leaves a scar
♪ Things fall apart
♪ But nothing breaks like a heart
♪ Ya, nothing breaks like a heart
♪ Ya, nothing breaks like a heart. ♪
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
Mark Ronson and Miley Cyrus!
Come on back. Come on back, you!
It's such a great track,
it's really, really lovely.
Thank you so much.
Hello. Hi. Welcome back,
thank you very much.
Have a seat there.
Perch yourselves there.
Really terrific track.
- I love that. And that's the first single off your new album?
- It is.
And the first time we've ever
performed it together.
The first time, yeah.
CHEERING
Well, I feel it was a good start.
It was a very good start.
- It was flawless.
- Thank you.
And when's the album out, Mark?
I think it's probably
going to be out in March.
- March 2019. And what's it called?
- It's called Late Night Feelings.
- Late Night Feelings.
- Yeah.
- And is that indicative of the album?
That I feel things late at night?
LAUGHTER
Yeah, I think it is.
I think I called it this thing,
basically, sad bangers, like,
songs that make you dance
but they have a bit of emotion,
like, melancholy, so
late night feelings is just
things that you think of at night.
That made no sense.
It will do. Well, we look forward
to hearing it all.
Mark Ronson and Miley Cyrus,
everybody!
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
Right, that's nearly it. Before we
go, just time for a visit
to the Big Red Chair. Who's there?
- Hello!
- Hi.
- Are you all right?
- Yeah, I'm good.
- What's your name?
- Leanne.
- Are you OK, Leanne?
- Yeah, I'm cool.
- All right, Leanne.
Shall I just let you get
on with your story?
Go for it.
OK, Leanne. Off you go.
Tell me your life.
I'm on my first-ever
girls' holiday, 18-30s.
We're in Tenerife, we're having
a party at the end of the night,
so we've got everyone over.
We notice that there's people
filming across from us
and we're, like,
what are they up to?
So my friends and I decided to pull
a moonie… so flash our bums,
for those who maybe don't know
what a moonie is.
So, a few weeks later, I'm sitting
there and I've got a new partner,
so I'm meeting his parents and we're
sitting and watching
a television programme and,
the next minute, the hotel
that I stayed in appeared on the
television, so I was, like, oh.
- So then…
- Oh.
The next minute, my bum appears,
along with my friend's.
The holiday show is called
Holiday Packages From Hell,
and that was my last time of seeing
any of those,
and a John Cena moment happened.
You walk! You walk.
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
No wonder she seems depressed.
Bless her.
The horror of seeing the hotel
and going, "I wonder what happened."
OK, who's up next? Hello.
- Hello.
- Hi, what's your name?
- My name's Mark.
- Mark.
- You're from Ireland, right?
- I'm from County Cork in Ireland, your way.
Oh, right. Am I in your story?
- Not the ones you want to hear.
- OK, good.
Off you go with your story, Mark.
So, I injured my foot
in the summer and it was really
badly damaged, and said I'd just
leave it and leave it but it never
healed, so I was like bite
the bullet and go the physio.
The funny thing is
I really fancy my physio.
She's really good looking.
Unfortunately, I've got really hairy
feet, so I didn't want to go
into the physio with my Hobbit feet,
so I decided at the last minute
to whip off the hair
on my damaged foot.
So I went in anyway, put the bad
foot up, she was checking it
and checking it, and she couldn't
really see what the problem was.
So she was like, can you pop your
other foot up there just so I can…
LAUGHTER DROWNS SPEECH
So, anyway, I lump the other
foot up and she kind of
has a smart grin on her face,
and she's examining again.
She just goes, "Don't worry, Mark,
you'd be surprised how many people
"come in here like that."
You can walk.
You can walk right out.
That's all we've got
time for, I'm afraid.
If you'd like to have a go
in the chair yourself
and tell your story,
you can contact us via
our website at this address.
Please say thank you to all of my
guests tonight… Mark Ronson…
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
…Miley Cyrus…
…Jamie Oliver…
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
…Hailee Steinfeld…
…John Cena…
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
LAUGHTER
…and Matthew McConaughey!
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
Join me next week with
super girl band Little Mix,
top comic Bill Bailey,
Strictly judge Dame Darcey Bussell
and Aquaman himself, Jason Momoa.
I'll see you, then!
Goodnight, everybody, bye-bye!
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE