This programme contains
some strong language
Good evening, everyone.
This is Keira Knightley saying,
it's New Year's Eve, and
welcome to The Graham Norton Show.
CHEERING
Oh!
Wow.
Wow!
Oh-ho-ho-ho!
Look at us!
Oh!
Hello! Good evening,
you're all very welcome.
It's New Year's Eve, everyone.
CHEERING
Hooray! Oh.
Yes, ladies and gentlemen,
it's the time to get drunk
and forget what
a horrible year you've had.
Keep drinking.
Have you all done your New Year's
resolutions? Have you? Have you?
AUDIENCE:
Yes!
I thought you might have.
Here is a tip for you.
If you are coming up with
New Year's resolutions
but don't believe
they'll ever happen,
write them on the side of a bus.
Yeah.
So, here comes 2019 and maybe…
mm-hm… another general election.
In which case,
Labour may well get into power,
and then it'll be up to
Jeremy Corbyn to sort out Brexit.
CHEERING AND BOOING
I tell you, there are a lot
of people praying that won't happen.
Let's get some guests on.
CHEERING
Later, we'll be meeting two stars
from the critics' hit of the year,
The Favourite…
Nicholas Hoult and Olivia Colman.
CHEERING
They'll be joining us.
And we've a special
musical performance
by pop sensation Rita Ora,
everybody.
CHEERING
Yeah.
But first, she's an award-winning
actress and comedian
who's given us characters like
Lauren "Am I bovvered?" Cooper,
and the foul-mouthed Nan…
please welcome back
Catherine Tate, everybody.
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
Argh!
I'll come this way.
They're loving you.
Mwah-mwah.
Have a seat, do.
Catherine Tate.
He's the Aussie star
who went from Neighbours
to Hollywood hits like Memento,
LA Confidential
and Priscilla, Queen Of The Desert.
Here to tell us about the new drama
Mary, Queen Of Scots,
it's a first-time welcome
to Guy Pearce.
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
Yes!
Hello, sir, how are you?
Very good.
Come and sit down.
Catherine Tate, Guy Pearce.
And this Oscar-nominated actor rose
to fame in Bend It Like Beckham
and went on to star
in Pride & Prejudice,
Love Actually, and Atonement.
Now she's playing
French writer Colette…
it's a warm welcome back
to Keira Knightley!
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
She's running! So keen.
Running on.
Hello.
Hi.
How are you?
Come in and sit down.
Thank you.
Woo!
Yay!
Happy New Year, everyone.
What a year.
We're not quite there, yet,
though, are we? No, no.
Hours to go!
Did you all have a nice Christmas?
Lovely. Did you?
It was a bit cold.
I spent Christmas here in the UK.
Did you?
I didn't know that.
Your invitation obviously got lost
in the mail… my apologies.
Where were you for Christmas,
Catherine?
England.
Keep it vague!
Yes, I was in England.
What was the best present you got,
Catherine?
LAUGHTER
Erm…
The one I gave you, wasn't it?
It's…
Yeah, it's this Tiffany…
Tiffany necklace.
That's lovely, what
a thoughtful gift, Guy, very nice.
Hey, I tell you who
had a good 2018…
because many people didn't…
but Keira Knightley did.
Did I?
Yes, you got an OBE,
remember?
Oh, I did, yes.
Yes!
Yes, I did.
CHEERING
But… This is so starry.
How long did that envelope
sit in your house unopened?
It was about three days.
Right, so, there's an envelope
that comes through the mail,
and it's from the Home Office.
And it's terrifying
because you think…
You thought you were in trouble.
Of course I did.
You thought
were being deported.
Right.
Yes, I thought… well, no,
I thought it was tax.
I thought, I've completely
ruined everything,
I've completely ballsed this up,
they're going to take away the house
and I'm a mother and
we're going to be homeless and…
So best not to open that letter.
So, basically, just hide it.
Hide it and don't think about it.
And then, after about three days, I
thought, no, because I am a mother,
and I'm a wife and a responsible
parent…
A responsible woman.
…that I am going to face the fact
and actually have to tell my husband
that I've completely messed it up
and we're going to lose the house.
So, I finally, after three days,
opened the letter
and I thought, "Oh, it's a prize."
LAUGHTER
Thanks, Government.
Yeah.
And what date did you receive it on?
Tomorrow?
HE MOUTHS
No, not tomorrow, what's the date
tomorrow, the 13th? Not tomorrow.
No!
No.
The 1st of January!
1st
of January? Uh… I… Thank you.
For goodness' sake!
She is so dizzy!
That's what happens when you get
an OBE.
I know, right!
We've got a picture of you getting
the OBE on December the…
13th.
Yeah.
Did you have a nice time?
LAUGHTER
It was so lovely.
Yes, thank you for asking.
What did they say to you
when they gave it to you?
LAUGHTER
Yeah, we had a chat
about my hat, and…
Were you wearing a hat? I mean,
did you wear a hat?
I don't know.
Was I wearing a hat?
This is like Doctor Who
Christmas Special, isn't it?
We'll stop now, we'll stop,
we'll stop, we'll stop, we'll stop.
So, Guy Pearce, first time
on the show, welcome to you.
Thank you very much.
Where do you…
Because you were here for Christmas,
but I thought you lived
in Amsterdam.
I'm sort of half in Amsterdam,
half in Australia.
I'm a bit all over the place,
really, so…
Nice to spend some time
here in the UK, though,
as I'm from here originally.
Talking of Australia,
your kind of breakout movie,
Priscilla, Queen Of The Desert…
WHOOPING FROM AUDIENCE
Yeah!
APPLAUSE
The three of you… yourself,
Hugo Weaving and Terence Stamp…
WHISTLING AND WHOOPING
…is it true or is it one of
these kind of publicity stories…
but did you go out on the town
dressed in your…
Obviously not in those outfits.
Well, pretty much like that.
Oh, was it, really?
We'd done sort of two weeks of
rehearsal and the plan always was
that on the final day, on the Friday
of the last week of rehearsal,
we would do camera tests
all in costume and make-up, etc,
and then we would go out that night.
Stephan, our director, just really
wanted to sort of send us out
into the public and see how we went,
I think.
Took us to all the sort of
drag clubs in Sydney.
Yeah, yeah.
So, yeah, we went out
and I remember Hugo Weaving
quite drunk under a table
and me sort of slapping him
in the face, saying,
"Come on, darling,
it's time to go."
So we did, we went out, and all
these local Sydney drag queens
were going, "Who are these bitches?"
"They're amazing,
who the fuck are they?"
So there was a lot that going on.
And, of course, it brought you
to the attention of Hollywood
and lots of Australian actors
now do very well in Hollywood.
I don't know if you know,
in Sydney,
there is a Madame Tussauds,
or a wax museum.
Yes.
And it celebrates many of
the very popular Australian actors.
For instance, there's Hugh Jackman
looking very rugged.
Very butch.
Yes, very butch and rugged.
There's Eric Bana.
Look at him, ooh! Yeah.
Then, we've got Hemsworth
dressed up there as Thor.
Again.
And then you're thinking,
you know, Guy Pearce,
star of The King's Speech, LA
Confidential,
Memento, where is he?
He's out the back!
That's amazing.
APPLAUSE
Hey, but now, you're in another
costume, an historical costume,
because you are in
Mary, Queen Of Scots.
This is out on the 18th of January.
So, Margot Robbie is Elizabeth I,
Saoirse Ronan, Mary, Queen of Scots.
Who are you?
I am William Cecil. So I'm
Elizabeth I's adviser, essentially.
So, there I am, in my drag
outfit, again…
Yes.
…essentially trying
to, you know, lead the way,
and protect the Crown,
protect Protestantism
and make sure that this Scottish
woman, Mary, doesn't get her way.
And was it nice, getting on set
in a big movie like that,
and finding another Aussie?
Yeah. I mean, we laugh,
but it always seems so odd to us,
to sort of, you know,
be working internationally,
and particularly two
Aussies here playing
such prominent English characters.
And, of course, I wanted to work
with Saoirse again because I'd…
I worked with Saoirse not long
after you'd worked with Saoirse,
about ten years ago, I think,
when she was just a kid.
She was incredible.
But, of course, in this film,
I have no scenes with her.
But all my scenes are with Margot.
She was, yeah, she was delightful.
Well, we've got one
of the scenes with Margot.
This is you trying to reason
with Queen Elizabeth.
Oh, don't bother!
What have you produced in all
your travels between our kingdoms?
Discord?
War?
Death?
And now you have the boldness
to doubt my judgment.
You had better question yours.
I regret that you perceive me
as a failure.
We serve you fully.
With all our hearts.
Any one of us
would gladly die for you,
but Mary is our foe,
and a Catholic.
She is only your Queen
if I should not produce an heir.
And will you, madam?
For you have given us
little hope so far.
Despite your every effort,
she has prevailed.
She has proven herself in fact
far more capable
than my own Privy Council.
Should I die before my time,
we could do worse than to place her
on the throne of England.
Woo! Very good.
Now, Catherine. Catherine Tate
brings us the last leg of her tour
The Catherine Tate Show Live,
which gallops into the West End
to the Wyndham's Theatre,
from January 7th to the 26th.
And, like, it's not like you just
pop a hat on, so what are
the logistics of that?
It's like, backstage, another show
happens. As I run off stage…
I always wanted to do the show live,
but it was the logistics of it.
And you think, "Well, how do I do
that?"
You have to find a way of obviously
getting off stage,
and I wanted it to be that I run
off stage as one character
and before you really
knew that I'd gone,
I was back as someone else.
And the way to do that is to get
brilliant quick-change artists
who just strip you down and you go
backstage. There's no dignity.
They'll just say, "Arm. Left arm.
Right arm."
It's literally like a dance you do.
And they strip you down and
sometimes you're underdressed
and they have to pull it off, you
know?
And I'd said once in an interview…
I said, "The thing about it is,
"by the end of the show I look
about three stone lighter
"because all the costumes
have come off me."
So you're wearing, like, six
people in the beginning?
You're sort of like one of those
Russian dolls and then you keep
coming out of it.
But then it comes back
to you and someone's done
some bits of research.
I mean, I had to go and do the
promotion in Australia and they
said… And I'm going to do
the Australian accent.
Yeah, do it.
Sue me!
They said…
AUSTRALIAN ACCENT:
…"So, I read
that you actually lose
"three stone each show."
She went, "What's that like?"
I said, "Well…"
We're a smart bunch.
"Obviously impossible,
because after four shows
"I wouldn't exist, would I?"
But the prosthetics… Are the
prosthetics as heavy now?
Well, here's the thing, right?
We tried really hard to do
a prototype of the nan,
the old lady nan character.
There she is.
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
And they said, "Look,
because it's not on camera,
"you can have something much cruder,
you just put it over your head."
But it just never worked. It just
looked like this massive thing
and I looked like Hannibal Lecter.
I was just like, "Oh, my God.
What are we going to do?"
So then someone said to me, "Well,
listen, as it's onstage,
"you've got the wig,
you've got the clothes,
"you do the voice, go
without the prosthetic."
And I was like, "I can't believe
you would even suggest
"I could go out as an old lady
without the prosthetic."
Anyway, in the end I had to go out
without the prosthetic.
Not one fucker noticed.
APPLAUSE
Very good!
And talking of extraordinary
costumes, Keira Knightley's latest
film, a great period drama called
Colette. Keira, you play Colette.
Yes.
And did I say it opens on
the 11th of January?
You didn't. It does.
It opens on the 11th
of January in 2019.
That's in the future.
Yes.
Now Colette, I think
people know about Colette,
that she was a writer,
and Gigi, things like that,
but this film kind of focuses
on this really extraordinary
first bit of her career.
It's this amazing part of her life
where she was married to a man
called Willy and they were a very,
very famous couple of the day and he
basically took credit for her first
four novels.
So it's the story of that marriage
and her sort of, at the end
of it, going, "I'm going to claim
my voice and my work."
But she was writing the novels
but he was getting
all the acclaim and credit.
He had a factory,
a bit like Andy Warhol,
and he had lots of writers working
for him, and it was all
under the name Willy.
You mean a man taking the credit for
a woman's work?
It's weird.
I can't imagine that would happen.
What kind of world are we living in?
Yeah, so he had lots of writers
working for him but she was sort of
arguably the genius and made a lot
of money and they were hugely
successful.
Well, listen, let's watch a clip.
This is you with your husband
and publisher, played by Dominic
West, and this is you demanding
recognition as an author.
Yes.
We can't risk it. Especially not
with our present finances.
We're completely broke.
You're always broke and yet
you gamble and you fill this place
with your antiques.
I bought those from bankrupts
from a debtors' auction.
The car?
The racehorse that went lame?
And
you with your funny clothes and your
hats and the exorbitant mortgage.
I need my name on the book.
No. Willy is a brand, and in any
case, women writers don't sell.
You bastard.
You fat, smug, lazy,
selfish bastard.
This is utter nonsense.
If you felt so strongly
about that you should never have
agreed to it all.
God damn you,
Willy.
Without the progenitor
there would be no Claudine.
And Colette, I didn't know the whole
performance element of her life.
She gave up writing for a
while to go on stage and sort of
perform pantomime-esque dances.
COUGHS: Soft porn!
Definitely…
It's behind you!
…a
bit of flashing went on.
She did.
He's still behind you!
But mimed.
Mimed.
Mimed!
And now your daughter Edie,
she came on set, but didn't
she come on one of the…?
The performance days, yeah.
So she thinks I'm a professional
dancer now.
I've sort of said,
"What does Mummy do for a living?"
And she goes, "Dancer. Dancer."
I thought it makes complete sense.
Trying to explain to her that Mummy
pretends to be other people
for a living… that doesn't
make sense, does it?
That's going to be very hard.
It's very tricky.
Mind you, she sounds
bright as a button.
Didn't she watch the American
election with you?
Yeah, so I think she was about 18
months old, and that was
when the American election happened.
It got to five in the morning,
and my husband had checked
on the election results
and he just said, "Trump's won."
And, you know, from that moment,
as many people were,
I think we were very awake suddenly.
Very woke!
Very woke.
We were suddenly watching
the television very much, and my kid
didn't wake up until about 8am,
which was when he was giving his
victory speech, so I brought
her into the bed and she sort of lay
on the bed on her belly
and the telly's there
and she's sort of like that,
really intently watching it.
And then she rolled over
on her back and she just went,
"Oh, fuck."
APPLAUSE
From the mouths of babes.
Exactly!
That's right.
Perfectly stable.
Wow.
I like the sound of her.
Yeah,
she's great. Yeah.
That's good.
Now, we have a tradition
here on the New Year's Eve show.
Yes, it's the moment
you've all been waiting for.
TOOT!
It's time for party pieces,
everyone.
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
Catherine, we'll start with you,
Catherine. What have you brought us?
I found this very
intimidating, and I think…
…I think I can make a noise
like a baby crying.
It's a party!
Whoo!
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
Like a newborn crying. OK?
OK, OK,
OK. Here we go.
I did only try this out today.
SHE IMITATES NEWBORN CRYING
That is so good!
APPLAUSE
Oh!
Forced!
You did the classic
underselling it and then
suddenly nailed it.
Forced to dredge that up.
I had nothing.
I wish my little boy was that quiet
when he was three months as a baby.
OK, we turn to Guy Pearce,
the pride of Australia.
The pride of Australia.
What are you going to give us?
In the spirit of Priscilla, I
thought perhaps I'd give you some
of the opera.
Are you seriously going to?
Top of the bus.
You're going to sing
some of the top-of-the-bus aria? OK.
Look, I'm a little croaky, I'm
croaky of throat at the moment.
OK.
But we'll see if we can remember it.
OK. Here we go, here we go.
♪ Follie! Follie!
♪ Delirio vano e questo!
♪ Povera donna
♪ Abbandonata in questo
popoloso deserto
♪ Che appellano Parigi
♪ A diletti sempre nuovi
dee volare il mio pensier
♪ Dee volar, dee volar
♪ Dee volar il mio pensier
♪ Dee volar, dee volar… ♪
HE VOCALISES
Wow!
And then there's a really high bit.
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
But I don't know it.
That was amazing!
I mean…
Wow.
…lt's no baby
crying, let's face it!
He cries when
I do that to him at home, though.
The party-piece pressure
has rolled down the couch.
It really has!
OK. OK, Keira Knightley.
What you got?
Going to do the
flicked bogey thing?
OBE!
Yeah! All right. Watch this.
Actually, this is good.
This is good. Wait for this.
I can play my teeth.
Wow!
I can play Raindrops
Keep Fallin' On My Head.
I mean, I can play anything you
want, but I'd go for Raindrops
Keep…
No, you've chosen that song.
The problem is I'm wearing a jacket
where I can't quite bend my arms.
I didn't think about this.
Put your hair back.
You need a microphone.
I think this mic will pick it up.
OK, fine. Wait a minute. Oh, I
haven't done this in a while.
So, just to remind you…
Wait a
minute, I was ready then!
…this is Raindrops Keep Fallin' On
Your Head, performed on her teeth.
Take it away.
Yeah. Er…
TAPPING TO MELODY
Wow!
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
Nice work!
That's… Yeah. Wow!
What does your dentist
think about that?
The dentist is at home going,
"I told you not to do
"that any more!"
They're falling
out.
Thank you so much for all of
that. Now, Catherine Tate, I know
you have to slip away.
I've double-booked, unfortunately.
I'm going to another party.
You've got a hot date?
That crying baby's
going to go down a storm.
Yes!
Catherine Tate, everybody!
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
There you go.
Right, my next guests are two of the
stars of the dark historical comedy
The Favourite.
One rose to fame in About A Boy
and went on to star in TV's Skins,
Mad Max and X-Men.
The other is the Bafta award-winning
star of Broadchurch,
Peep Show and The Night Manager.
Please welcome Nicholas Hoult
and Olivia Colman!
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
Oh!
Wowzer!
Lovely to see you.
Hello.
Sit down.
Hello, Nicholas. Hi. You sit there.
You go in there. Excellent. Whoo!
Hello. How are you?
There was a lot of waving going on.
I feel you know each other.
We've
met before. Never met before.
We haven't. Give us a kiss.
Happy New Year.
Happy New Year!
That's great.
We get to spend it all together.
I can go home now.
Now, congratulations to both
of you on The Favourite.
It opens tomorrow, next year.
I mean, it's one of those weird
films.
People have talked about this film
a lot already, but if people haven't
heard about it, try and describe
the movie to us.
That's in your hands, I think.
Oh, I don't think so.
I think it is.
One of you has to do it.
I'll do it.
Who do you play? Who
do you play? That will help.
Oh, Queen Anne.
There you go.
Queen Anne. It's about Queen Anne.
It's a love triangle between
yourself, Emma Stone and Rachel
Weisz,
a love power struggle triangle
between these three women at court.
That's good!
Wow! Bring him. Yeah!
And who do you play?
I play Robert Harley,
the Leader of the Opposition.
There he is.
OK.
Wow. Look at him!
Fancy.
Simple.
I tell you what, why don't we see a
clip first?
OK.
Let's see a clip first.
This is you as Lord Harley
addressing Parliament
in front of Queen Anne.
OK.
OK, it's good.
May I speak a moment,
with Her Majesty's pleasure?
May I exhort the chamber to roar
a mighty hurrah for Her Majesty
in her brilliant decision
to not raise the Land Tax?
ALL: Hurrah!
For the doubling of the tax
would have been a disaster
and the fields would have run
with blood as the countryside rose
up against our city friends to add
to the piling dead of our sons
already on the field of this war.
Again, to our Queen,
for her deep wisdom in knowing
where to draw the line
in holding our country together.
For there is no point winning
a war abroad if we are to start
one at home.
CHEERING
I apologise for the interruption,
Your Majesty.
The floor is yours, of course.
We look forward to hearing
what you have to say.
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
Very good.
Good clip!
Now, the director,
Yorgos Lanthimos…
Actually, Keira,
you've talked on the show
about doing sex scenes
and how embarrassing it can be.
I have!
With Yorgos Lanthimos…
I didn't have any sex scenes with
Yorgos.
No. But he's directing them.
Does he make them less embarrassing,
more embarrassing,
more awkward, odder?
No, he's very…
You have to feel safe to be able to
do those scenes, don't you?
You have to feel secure
with your director.
You have to trust them,
and I trust him completely.
It was just all
quite…embarrassing.
Yeah. You had a special
thing to protect…
Because Emma Stone,
she was worried about you.
Well, she was…
So Emma Stone had to finger me.
In order to sort of avoid finding
anything that you shouldn't,
because it's under the sheets
like that, and she said,
"I'm a little bit worried about…"
"Don't worry. Don't worry.
I know, I know!"
So I asked make-up
if they had a sponge, and so I put
a sponge there and said,
"It's all right.
"There's a barrier."
A finger
sponge?
It was a big, wet sponge.
Have you made up this
story afterwards?
No!
Her face was a picture. She was
going up my leg and she went…
"It's all right, it's a sponge,
it's a sponge!"
That's so good. I'm going to use a
sponge for every character I play
from now on.
Bring my own sponge.
"You'll feel something soft
and wet, so don't worry."
And, Nicholas, we saw in the clip
there, your wigs are extraordinary.
Yes.
Now, did you give them names?
I did. Yeah, yeah, yeah,
I had three wigs, and they all
had their own kind of
personalities and names.
This is
special, ladies and gentlemen.
I feel like we're in the Hard Rock
Cafe. We've got the real wigs.
And they're here tonight!
The girls are here!
Now, so…
Oh, they are!
They are, they are.
Be gentle.
So, who was this?
That's Lulu.
Oh, Lulu!
Lulu was more of a party wig.
Lulu is a good time.
She's in the scene where
I'm throwing oranges at a naked man.
She knows a good time.
She does. Now, who else have we got?
We've got this one.
That's Hattie.
That could be a dog asleep.
Do you want me to hold one?
There we
go. But actually, I imagined…
But you can just slip them on.
Take it for a spin, yeah.
Yeah!
That's it. Yeah!
It's good for winter, because
you can just go like that.
APPLAUSE
But you know what? I spoke to Nadia,
the make-up artist who helped
and made all these and everything,
and she was meant to come tonight,
I think, with these,
but she's gone to Kensington Palace
to perhaps do an installation
with these wigs or something.
She has. No, not these ones,
clearly.
No, not tonight.
No, because they're here.
Not tonight.
But that's what they're doing,
I guess, they're going
to Kensington Palace.
A couple of weeks ago, they went,
didn't they? Yes.
Were you there?
Yes. It was great.
GUY:
We were all there.
That's opened and closed.
We're in the future.
That's…
We were all there.
I'm so sorry.
APPLAUSE
Happy New Year!
GUY:
It was a great night.
An unforgettable evening.
I'll leave Hattie under the thing.
Come on, Hattie. Good Hattie.
We did a movie together.
We worked
together.
We did a movie called
Equals.
I had a shaved head.
Did you have a shaved head?
No, it was kind of similar to this,
I think, my hair.
OK, I had a shaved head. There was
not much hair going on in that.
No, not much hair.
Very clean costumes.
Set in the future, that one.
But you're making up for it now.
Like this show.
Can I just say, I think
you're being very quiet,
Keira, because you can
see his wigs…
I've taken a good look.
…and trump them.
100%.
You've rocked a wig or two in your
time.
My wigs have been bigger than
your wigs.
Keira in The Duchess.
Wow!
Look at that.
And that one, halfway through,
it was so heavy I couldn't do
a whole scene in it. So I'd start
sitting like this and then it was
like this and just keep going down,
so they had to suspend it from the
ceiling, which was quite tricky for
a performance because you suddenly
can't move at all.
So you're stood in one spot?
Your neck is at least not breaking.
What did they do when you needed to
sit down?
I was stuck.
It just stays there.
I would come
out from underneath.
They bring her a chair.
It would
hang?
It would hang and I would sort
of duck in and duck out.
Good idea.
That's quite easy.
Yeah.
Not if you needed to move
around.
You can't just turn round.
No. Yeah.
Cool!
But the thing is, Nicholas, your
wigs, I think they sort of brought
out your inner diva,
cos you posted this.
You posted this!
This is Nicholas Hoult
on the set of The Favourite.
HE MIMES ALONG TO
Hold Up by Beyonce
♪ I get my swag on
♪ I look in the mirror,
say, "What's up?"
♪ "What's up? What's up?
What's up?"… ♪
That's so good! Wow!
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
APPLAUSE DROWNS SPEECH
While you were acting, he was
doing that.
I was…
Olivia, we should say, you join us,
literally join us tonight hotfoot
from the set of your other queen
job, QE2 in The Crown.
Yes.
Where are you?
Are you nearly finished, or…?
It feels like… We're nearly
at the end, which feels
like the longest bit.
We've been going for months.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. But you're nearly
there.
Nearly there!
Nearly there.
And for you, it seems to me that
because of the way
this is happening,
you're basing it on
kind of two people.
There's obviously the real Queen
Elizabeth, but then are you in any
way having to be a continuation
of Claire Foy?
My first few weeks, I was just
trying to do an impression of
Claire. So I was thinking,
"What would Claire do?"
I had to channel Claire.
And then, now we're sort of so busy
I've forgotten, so I might not
be doing anything like
the Queen or Claire now.
But isn't there a thing…?
Because the mobility of your face
is not something that our
lovely Queen shares.
No!
How hard is that for you?
I'm suspended from the ceiling.
It's quite hard.
If other characters are saying
something that's sad,
I naturally can't
help myself, I go…
…and burst into tears,
which is not what the Queen does.
She is our rock.
Not often.
Not often. Not caught on camera.
Yeah.
So they filmed quite a lot
from the back of my head
on those days
and also they've come up with a
trick, so they give me an earpiece
and they play the shipping
forecast to me.
So I just have to try and tune
in to the shipping forecast,
which is rude, because I'm not
listening to my fellow actors.
I'm just trying not to listen to
them.
That's good.
We'll remember that
when we watch it.
That's bad.
I hope you can faintly hear it.
Like it's on in the next room.
I have to say, what's happened to
you is just amazing. It's wonderful.
You know, you're very successful
in this country and much beloved,
but now you see the world
discovering you.
But, like, now we see you in things
like Vogue and all these things,
doing high-fashion shoots and stuff.
Is this what you dreamt of?
Is this when you go, "At last.
"At last!"?
"The cover of
L'Uomo Vogue!"
No.
I love my job very much. I love it.
I love going to work,
which is, I know, very lucky.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But the other stuff is a bit
embarrassing, innit?
But do you have to do it?
Do you have to rock up?
I don't think you HAVE to do it. I
think I've been persuaded to do it.
I don't really know.
Do you know if you have to do it?
You have to do quite a lot of it.
She has to do it.
You do a lot.
Yeah.
We don't
have to do it. But they persuade us.
Do they say, "Oh, no, you have to"?
I don't know that I do, but then
suddenly you find yourself…
It's important.
Is it? They say
that.
They say that.
They do say that a lot.
They said you had to do THIS, right?
Yeah!
Even I'VE been told
I HAVE to do this!
Even THEY'VE been told
they have to do this.
But this is genuinely one of the
things
that's really enjoyable to
do.
Oh, bless you.
I mean that.
Awww!
That's very… Drink up.
APPLAUSE
Happy New Year.
But talking about being thrust into
the limelight, Nicholas Hoult,
I always thought the first thing
you did was About A Boy.
No.
But you started even younger
than that, didn't you?
AUDIENCE:
Awww!
I did my first gig when I was five.
Oh, now…
The gig I'm talking about is
Casualty.
How old were you in Casualty?
Er…
I think six, seven. I don't know.
I think you were about seven.
I remember I got to wear
a cool leather jacket…
or I thought at the time…
and my dad hit his head
on a car jack…
and was going to die?
Well, we've got the clip.
Not your actual dad.
No!
OK!
We've got the clip.
We've got the clip. So, this is
Nicholas Hoult, very young.
It's a classic Casualty set-up.
Nicholas Hoult is very excited.
He's very young.
And he's too young to be let loose
with a pump for a big tyre.
Yeah!
But he's playing with it.
Oh, no!
It probably won't end well.
Here he is. So, he's very excited.
He's pumping away. Look at him.
Oh, there's his cool leather jacket.
He's having a great time.
Now, there's the tyre.
I think he's getting overexcited.
The pressure's getting
a bit high now.
Oh, look at that face!
Look! Look!
He's loving it. It's too much!
It's too much!
Look! Look, the tyre is going to
burst.
Will someone come to help Nicholas?
Surely his dad will notice.
Oh, he HAS noticed. Hang on,
he's got to go and rescue him.
Craig?
Oh, no! No!
Oh! A classic redirect!
That was excellent, wasn't it?
APPLAUSE
One of the best Casualtys ever.
Amazing!
You didn't see it coming.
I didn't realise
it was all my fault.
Watching it back in hindsight,
if I hadn't been doing that,
then everyone would have been fine.
Ohhh, that was very good.
What was the job you did
when you were five?
A film called Intimate Relations.
Sounds worse than it was.
We don't have a clip of that!
Sorry I asked.
I remember the
audition for that because all
I had to do was sit under this table
and pretend to eat cake.
I was like, "All right."
"You've got the job." "Great.
"I can eat cake all day."
Can I just say, I think
I've done very well.
I've held off to this point
in the show before mentioning Guy's
seminal work as Mike Young
in Neighbours.
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
I was about to walk off the set.
You were thinking, "When?!
When will he mention my work?"
Now, obviously, this is never far
from me. Neighbours Who's Who.
Wow!
You're genuinely excited
by this, aren't you?
I bet there's some good haircuts in
there.
You get the whole back page.
Wow!
Check that out.
Yeah.
Yeah!
That's the Who's Who.
Can I have that?
Of course you can.
That is yours. That is yours.
Cos, Olivia, you were a big
Neighbours fan, weren't you?
Yes!
Still are, I'm sure.
Yes.
I was then, in the, yeah,
sort of early '90s.
But Neighbours has sort of come
back into your life.
It never goes away, Graham.
Well, it has come back into my life
because we had a little Twitter
exchange recently
because Annie Jones,
who plays Jane,
has gone back on the show.
Plain Jane Super Brain.
Plain Jane Super Brain,
the love of my life, of course.
And there was a storyline
where it was implied
that she was going to sort of go
off with Stefan,
who plays Paul Robinson. And I just
sent this tweet out going,
"Jane, no!"
And then Stef made this video
saying, "Well, nice tweet, Guy.
"Why don't you come back
on the show and why don't
"we have it out together?"
Anyway, so it was just funny banter
and then we found out
that, actually,
those guys were here in the UK,
so we caught up and we took some
photos together with Annie,
with us fighting and Annie
keeping us apart.
There you are, fighting. Oh, look,
Plain Jane Super Brain very upset.
Yeah. "Which grey-haired man
will I go with?"
"My life is complete."
APPLAUSE
I loved it.
Yeah.
Now, ladies and gentlemen,
the evening is not complete.
You guys have not been
let off the hook. No!
Because it's time for…
TOOT!
…more party pieces.
We've done ours, by the way. And
they were amazing, weren't they?
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
Oh, amazing. Amazing.
You've got a lot to live up to.
Yeah.
No pressure.
What did you do?
Let's see. So, Nicholas,
what have you got for us?
Well, this isn't really a thing.
They said, "Have you got any
party pieces?" I said, "Not really."
And they said, "We read that you
pick up things with your toes."
I think I said that in an interview
once because they were like,
"Do you have any tricks?"
I was like, "I don't know.
"I can pick anything
up with my toes."
Now people are running with that.
No, wait a minute. You say that.
Didn't you and your flatmates
have a
Picking Up Things With Your
Toes Olympics?
Yeah.
And who won that? Who won that?
I won that.
You won that.
Thank you.
I think it's the only
Toe Olympics ever to happen.
Basically, we just stuck different
things on the floor and picked them
up with our toes.
OK, so how heavy can you go?
Can you pick up a melon?
There's a metal pineapple.
Could you pick that up?
Oh, shit.
It's not that heavy.
I'll give it a try. Why not?
Yeah, OK, OK. Hang on. Do you want
to do it on the table or out there?
Cos if here, no-one can see you.
That will be like a tree
falling in a forest.
I did it!
"Oh, yeah, I did it.
Yeah, yeah."
Are you doing it with sockies on?
How are you going to do it with
socks on?
That's how good he is.
I don't want to get
my little hobbit toes out.
It's like showing off.
"I can do it with socks."
Can you really?
Oh, look, look, look!
DRUM ROLL
Oh, actually, you know what?
Hang on.
Take your socks off.
No, he's going to!
He's got it!
He did it!
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
Yes! Beautifully done.
Thank you very much.
Come on!
OK, so, that was very impressive.
That was quite stressful!
Olivia Colman,
now, what are you giving us?
I'm going to give you a lion.
A lion. Oh, is this when I need
the…?
Yes.
OK.
Olivia's brought a sponge.
OK, so you need a pint
glass for this.
OK, so, do you need to explain
what you're going to do first?
No, I don't think so.
No? OK.
OK. This is self-explanatory.
It's Olivia Colman doing a lion.
SHE ROARS LIKE A LION
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
Very good. Right…
…it's time for music. It's been six
years since her platinum-selling
debut album Ora and now she's back
playing a medley of hits
from her second album, Phoenix.
It is Rita Ora!
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
♪ Time flies by
when the night is young
♪ Daylight shines
on an undisclosed location
♪ Location
♪ Bloodshot eyes looking for the sun
♪ Paradise delivered
and we call it a vacation, yeah
♪ Vacation
♪ You're painting me a dream that I
♪ I wanna belong, yeah
♪ I wanna belong, yes
♪ Over the hills and far away
♪ A million miles from LA
♪ Just anywhere away with you
♪ I know we've got to get away
♪ Someplace where no-one
knows our name
♪ We'll find the start
to something new
♪ Just take me anywhere
♪ Take me anywhere
♪ Anywhere away with you. ♪
♪ Treating you well,
but I'm caught in the middle, yeah
♪ I caught the edge of the knife
and it hurts just a little
♪ Yeah, I know, and I know,
and I know
♪ And I know that I
can't be your friend
♪ It's my head or my heart
and I'm caught in the middle
♪ My hands are tied
but not tight enough
♪ You're the high
that I can't give up
♪ Oh, Lord, here we go
♪ I might hate myself tomorrow
but I'm on my way tonight
♪ At the bottom of the bottle
you're the poison in the wine
♪ And I know I can't change you
and I, I won't change
♪ I might hate myself tomorrow
but I'm on my way tonight
♪ Let's be lonely together
♪ Whoo!
♪ A little less lonely together
♪ Ooh, ooh, yeah. ♪
♪ I should've stayed
with you last night
♪ Instead of going out
to find trouble
♪ That's just trouble
♪ I think I run away sometimes
♪ Whenever I get too vulnerable
♪ That's not your fault
♪ I wanna stay the whole night
♪ I wanna lay with you
till the sun's up
♪ I wanna let you inside
♪ Oh, heaven knows I've tried
♪ I wish that I could let you love
♪ Wish that I could let you love me
♪ Wish that I could let you love
♪ Say, what's the matter,
what's the matter with me?
♪ What's the matter with me?
♪ Oh, I wish that I could
let you love
♪ Wish that I could let you love me
♪ Say, what's the matter,
what's the matter with me?
♪ What's the matter with me?
♪ Oh, I wish that I could
let you love
♪ Wish that I could let you love me
♪ Now
♪ Oh, I wish, oh, I wish,
oh, I wish, oh, I wish I
oh, I wish, oh, I wish I… ♪
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
Thank you.
Beautiful!
Rita Ora, everybody!
Come on over, Rita.
Oh! Beautiful job.
Come on down. Look at you.
You look like such a movie star.
Thank you!
Mwah!
Happy New Year! Hi, everyone.
Guy, Keira, Nicholas, Olivia.
There she is!
That was great.
Oh, thank you.
Lovely to see you.
And you.
Hello!
How are you? Oh, my God, I know you
from British Airways,
from flying on the plane.
Look, she's not an air hostess.
This is Olivia Colman.
I know that, but I have to say
I love that little thing
that they have.
Has anyone flown on British Airways
when they say put your seat belt on?
I just love you.
Thank you.
Well, of all your work, Olivia!
That was…
No, obviously, I know your work,
but that just makes me happy
when I see you.
Thank you.
Oh, God,
I really got myself in it.
Now, Rita Ora, thank you very much.
That's from the album Phoenix,
which is still out now.
It is, it is, yes.
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
If you've got a record voucher
for Christmas, then get that.
And there's a tour.
When is the tour?
I start touring…
I start in Australia next year,
March.
It all comes back to Australia.
AUSTRALIAN ACCENT:
We start in Aussie.
Do you still have your accent?
Yes.
That was perfect.
So that was bad,
basically?
No, it was fantastic.
No-one will find that offensive.
You're fine.
Yes, we start…
It's my first world tour ever,
so it's going to be really fun.
So if you guys are around next
year, please come and see me.
When do you get here? When do
you get to this country?
Er…
After that.
Graham, we've spoken about this.
I don't know my diary off by heart.
But the dates are on my website!
Yay!
You should really look at that.
I know.
I never know mine. It's fine. Fine.
Hey, everyone.
Guess what time it is.
TOOT!
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
Yeah. It's time for another
party piece.
Rita Ora, at the party,
what's your party piece?
OK, this might sound a bit weird,
but it's the only thing I can…
I might be a bit rusty, as well.
OK.
It's the only thing I can think of.
I can burp the alphabet.
Wow!
We haven't had that yet tonight.
Not from A to Z.
I'll give you a few letters,
because I am a bit rusty.
OK, OK.
Do you need
a sort of lubricant?
Maybe, actually. Just a little.
Yeah, yeah. Lovely.
OK.
By the way, only for you, Graham,
is this happening on TV.
No, no, this is New Year's Eve.
It's a party.
It is New Year's Eve!
OK.
Yeah. Here we go.
BURPS:
A…B…C…
…D…E…F…
…G…H…I…
…J…K…
OK, I've stopped.
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
Amazing!
You got to K. You got to K.
That was pretty impressive.
I haven't done that in AGES.
Whatever I thought
that would sound like,
I didn't think it would sound like
that. It's extraordinary.
Could you hear the letters?
Yes!
I've still got it!
Rita Ora, everybody!
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
Beautiful.
Beautiful. As enjoyable
as it was surprising.
Right, that's nearly it, but first
it's time for a visit
to the big red chair.
Who's there?
Hello.
'Old on. 'Old on.
Hi, what's your name?
It's Bev.
Sorry?
Bev.
CACKLING
'Old on!
Oh, my God. It's Nan, everybody!
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
Hello, darling.
SHE CACKLES
Hello, Nan.
Is it the red chair?
I didn't get your name.
What's your name?
What's her name?
Bev.
Oh, fuck that.
Have a seat, Nan. Have a seat.
You can sit down beside
Olivia Colman.
Oh, Gawd love us! I thought
I was on Loose Women.
They've nearly gone
right up me clacker there, look.
Look at all these people. Innit
lovely? Hello, Your Majesty.
It's lovely to meet you.
Here, I've got a story.
I won't go in the red chair.
No, but I have got a story for you.
I went to see Phantom Of The Opera.
Oh, yeah?
I didn't want to go, but me husband,
he always liked musicals.
I always had me suspicions but you
never like to ask, do you?
Anyway, we went
to see the show.
I don't know, a fellow in a mask,
a woman screaming,
chandelier fell down. I don't know
if it was supposed to.
Anyway, the thing I remember, clear
as day… and this is the truth…
the woman sat next to me,
she shit herself.
She sat…in her own shit.
This is true. And I said to her,
"Excuse me, darling."
I said, "You've just shit yourself."
She said… She was so
engrossed she didn't know.
She said, "Have I, love? Oh, yes,
you're right. I do apologise.
"I have shit myself."
Right, but it didn't…
It didn't impede her enjoyment
of the show. And that, to me,
is the mark of good theatre.
Yes!
APPLAUSE
Do you want to see some
more people on the red chair?
Go on, let's have them.
Let's have them. OK. Hello.
Oh, hello. Hi.
What's your name?
Paola.
She didn't shit herself.
No, she
didn't.
Where are you from, Paola?
I'm from Italy originally
but I live in London.
Oh, right. What do you do here?
I'm an art curator.
An art curator.
Ain't that lovely?
This New Year's Eve show is so hot.
Paola, off you go with your story.
Yes, so, I just moved to New York
from Italy a few years ago
and I was doing an internship
at the Guggenheim Museum,
and during a party I met
this really nice guy.
He asked me for a date after a few
days. So, I decided to meet him
in a busy restaurant.
And so we had some glasses of wine
and some laughs and at some point
I asked him, "What do you do?"
He goes, "I'm an exhibitionist."
I go, "Lovely! I love exhibitions.
"I'm in the arts, as well."
So we keep going on,
and the conversation is really nice
and we have some other wine
and laughs and he goes,
like, at some point, "Yeah, but you
should really meet my friend
"Barney." And I go, like, "Yeah,
sure, no problem."
"Barney would really love you and he
will need to meet you really soon."
I go, like, "Yeah, sure, no
problem."
He goes, "Would you like
to meet Barney tonight?"
I'm like, "Yeah, sure."
And I get a bit nervous, because
the situation was really strange.
So he goes, like, "Barney
will need to meet you right now."
I'm like, "That's OK."
And his face started
to become strange
and then he started to
just put his hands
down his trousers and unbutton
his pants, and at some point
it just hit me what
an exhibitionist is.
We have the same word in Italian.
She can walk.
She can walk?
You can walk!
APPLAUSE
Yeah. We'll keep that in.
Halfway through I thought,
"It's not going to make the edit."
But then she pulled it out the bag.
Literally.
Someone pulled something
out of somewhere.
APPLAUSE
All right, that really is
all we've got time for.
If you'd like to have a go in the
red chair yourself and tell your
story, you can contact us via the
website at this very address.
Please say a huge thank you to all
my guests. Rita Ora!
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
Guy Pearce!
Keira Knightley!
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
Nicholas Hoult!
Olivia Colman!
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
And Nan!
Thank you, Catherine Tate!
Please join me this Friday
for a special Good Story Guide
featuring some of our favourite
anecdotes over the years,
and then we're back to normal
service on the 11th of January
with musical act Westlife, Stan
and Ollie, Steve Coogan and
John C Reilly, actors Sarah Paulson
and Richard E Grant
and Professor Xavier
himself, James McAvoy.
Till then, have a very
happy new year.
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
Goodnight, everybody! Bye-bye!