Good evening, everyone.
My name's Emily Blunt -
welcome to a new series
of The Graham Norton Show!
This programme contains
some strong language
Hello! It's me! Hello! Hello, hello.
Lovely to see you. Hello! Welcome to
the show and the new series. What's
been happening while we've been
away?
Donald Trump has been accused
of sleeping with adult
actress Stormy Daniels.
Of actresses are adults but she's
really grown-up!
LAUGHTER
It's true, everything's
bigger in America.
Storm in a D-cup.
Even I'm impressed! Stormy Daniels.
Not to be confused with the other
woman in his life, Frosty Melania.
What else has been happening?
Well, a lot of people
were affected by the so-called
Beast from the East.
Now... Vladimir ... If you're trying
not to look evil, that is an
unfortunate pose.
APPLAUSE
See what I mean?
There's an ongoing diplomatic
row over the source
of the Salisbury nerve agent -
but the good news is,
it's not going to affect
the World Cup in Russia.
In fact, here's the England squad
getting ready to travel.
LAUGHTER
Let's get some guests on!
APPLAUSE
From the West End to the dizzying
heights of Hollywood this home-grown
star is back as Spider-Man
in the new Marvel blockbuster
Avengers: Infinity War -
please welcome Tom Holland!
That is Tom Holland! Hello, Tom
Holland. Lovely to see you. Welcome
back. Have a seat.
She's the Aussie goddess
of pop who's sold over
80 million records worldwide -
back with her sensational
new album Golden -
it's the fabulous Kylie Minogue!
Hello! Lovely to see you. Come in,
Kylie.
This actor shot to fame
as Jim Halpert in the American
version of The Office -
now he's terrifying audiences
with this year's must-see
horror A Quiet Place -
please welcome for the first
time John Krasinski!
That is John Krasinski!
And starring alongside John,
it's the Golden-Globe-
winning British star
of The Devil Wears Prada,
Sicario, Into The Woods
and The Girl On The Train -
it's always a pleasure
to welcome Emily Blunt!
O... Shiny! Shiny! Hello. Hello,
Emily.
Emily. Lovely to see you all. You
all well? Welcome to the show. Thank
you. Very nice. This is unusual,
ladies and gentlemen. We don't often
have this. On the couch tonight, a
celebrity couple!
CHEERING
I know! Sparks flew backstage. It's
incredible. Not just a couple, they
are married. Are you like Brad and
Angelina? George Edwards? Our name
is Crunt, we decided. I see how you
got there, I'm not sure why. It
seemed long winded, the alternative,
so Crunt belt division. Do you use
Crunt a lot?
Crunt a lot? We sometimes sent out
Christmas cards, Christmas with the
Crunts. That's going to go wrong,
really... That's why I like it, on
the edge. Kylie, such a famous name.
But you've been to court. You are
now definitely Kylie. I am most
definitely Kylie. I will remain
Kylie. Was there a question you
could have changed your name? No,
but there's another very Kylie...
AUDIENCE: O... No, there was a
settlement that came from agreement.
So that things are clear if it's a
Kylie Jeannette product or Kylie
Minogue. Does she only North America
and you the rest of the world? Kind
of! Sounds fair enough! I love it
here. Crunt might be... You need to
trademark! Per fee... Smell like the
Crunts. What is that aroma? Crunt.
Keep going, keep going. Tom Holland,
obviously, your name. Who is Dave
the frog and why does it have
something to do with you? This is
what I hear, what is that story?
Right, so we have to do red carpets
all the time and take pictures and I
found it awkward when they are all
shouting at you and stuff. A fan of
mind we did a picture of me saying,
Tom Holland looks like he has a frog
in his mouth when he is taking
paparazzi pictures. I thought it was
hilarious so I reposted the picture,
which then went viral and everyone
found it hilarious. But then weeks
go by and I'd look at myself in the
mirror and be like, I do look like I
have a frog in my mouth! I think
this is the original tweet. This is
you...
LAUGHTER
You do look like you got something
in your mouth. I think it's because
I'm trying to go for the chiselled
jaw look and it's not working. You
are Crunting. That's how John and I
do the red carpet. We do the Crunt
Kylie, you are singing for us later.
What will you be giving us? Well, as
I've been slightly unwell, I may be
giving you the husky rendition of
Stop Me From Falling. I should
public record my voice message
because I can speak very law. It's
the second single. We'll talk about
the album later but it's chock-full
of singles. It really is. Our first
big film tonight has already been
hailed as the horror movie of the
year will stop A Quiet Place.
Happily, it stars Emily Blunt and
John Krasinski. This is great, we'll
be able to talk about it!
LAUGHTER
Not just that. Directed and
co-written by yourself.
Congratulations, both of you. When
you see this film, it is such a
great premise for a horror film.
Explain it to the people. Me? Want
me to do it? You do it this time. We
teach it to each other every night
at dinner. This is a movie about a
family that you meet who has to
remain as quiet as possible and you
have to figure out why, I won't give
it away. They have to remain quiet
because they are being hunted by
creatures not from this planet that
only hunt by an acute sense of
sound, so if you make any sound you
will be dead within ten to 15
seconds. Which, honestly, it's...
Because the movie, it becomes eerily
quiet. It that you guys practice
that at home? Did we?
LAUGHTER
I feel like this became as if John
and I were role-playing at home.
Yes, I was a creature... Come on,
make some sound. Because it is...
LAUGHTER
It was funny, it was funny. We got a
clip. This will explain really what
it is. This is you and your family
on a really lovely day out. Bute.
Yellow lovely day out. Lovely day
out.
DISTANT EXPLOSION.
CHEERING
APPLAUSE
These movies... Kylie Minogue, would
you see this film? I'm beside myself
already. I couldn't watch that on my
own, though. No, well, hopefully
nobody will watch by themselves and
it will do very well.
LAUGHTER
Because, Tom, you wouldn't. You
don't like these films. Sorry, guys.
I'm not a fan of horror... Support
the film, Tom! I would be the worst
horror movie director you could
imagine. That's weird because, John,
you don't like these films. I don't
at all. The technical term is a
scaredy-cat. I never saw horror
movies growing up. I was too
terrified and obviously I'm a huge
horror fan now. You saw my iTunes
list over the last year you say, I
think we have a problem. It's a
phenomenal. I don't think my name is
the one that you see and say, can't
wait to see a horror movie from him!
The original script came to me and
it's an incredible story of family.
To me, you can't tell by looking at
the poster, we can show that again,
it's about what would you do as a
parent? What extremes would you go
to to protect your kids with white
is it true that you were originally
going to be in this film? We have
had our second child and I was about
to do Mary Poppins so I was in a
general feeling of joy and didn't
know if I wanted to go to the
darkness of the pitch he'd give me
for this film and I mentioned a
friend of mine to John and said, you
should call so and so. So and so is
so good. So good. So he did call so
and didn't send her the script,
admittedly. She wasn't hired... So
close! I read the script and said,
you need to call her and fire her.
You still friends? We are, until the
movie comes out. John, for you,
lovely that Emily wants to be in the
film, but as a director, is it then
weird, given your life partner
notes? It was weird because I was
very nervous. I think we both were.
Before we started shooting, I said I
was terrified and she said, oh,
good, me too. It's one of those
things where people think because
we're both in the same business, we
have the same experiences, but I've
never been on set with her and seen
how she worked. I'd heard she was a
diva and I...
LAUGHTER
Can't get Emily out of her trailer,
stuff like that. No, but I think
what it was, and it sounds really
sappy but it's true. I think it's
the greatest collaboration of my
career. I've never seen her work and
when you're actually in the room and
she does what she does, honestly, it
changes the air in the room.
Everyone is completely and totally
stunned by what she does. Aww.
APPLAUSE
This is what I had to learn early on
in our relationship. British people
are notoriously terrible at taking
compliments.
LAUGHTER
That's actually what she did. I'm a
huge fan of yours, get it out of the
way and she was like... You weren't
cool at all. There was none of that,
oh, I don't know your work. You were
a proper fan! She was full stalker!
I was like, hey, wants to go on a
date with me? How many times have
you seen The Devil Wears Prada? I
mean... Give or take, 72. It's one
of those things that back in the
day, both elderly people used to
channel serve and nobody does that
any more. What's that? Exactly. Just
one of those movies that whenever
you're going through the channels,
you stop and you look. Has anyone
seen the film here? Probably.
There's a sort of montage sequence
where Anne Hathaway has numerous
fabulous aspect two outfits and one
day I came home and John was
watching it and he was watching the
montage of it and goes, and...
That's my favourite outfit.
LAUGHTER
Well, I couldn't get Annie and so...
APPLAUSE
Now, talking of meeting famous
people, Tom, you recently presented
at the Oscars. I did. As if that
wasn't enough, afterwards, you met
one of the most famous people in the
world, one of the most famous women
in the world. I'd had one of the
most embarrassing experiences with
Madonna.
I was at the Oscars, I presented, it
went well, I went out after to
celebrate and probably had one too
many and I was at this party with a
couple of my friends and an old
friend of mine who is a manager
comes up to me. He's like, "Tom,
Tom, do you know Madonna?" I'm like,
"Funnily enough, no". He drags me
across the nightclub and introduces
me to Madonna. The whole way on the
way over there, I'm going, "What do
I say? Hello?" I had no idea. So I
get up there and I go, "Hello".
LAUGHTER
That is all I could come up with.
Weekdays model and Jason could see
me panicking and he said," Madonna,
Tom is an incredible dancer". I'm
looking at him, like, "I'm going to
kill you". She goes, "Really? That
is something I'd love to see. Show
me". I'm thinking, I have two
options, I can just faint, pass out
or I can take Madonna on the dance
floor, dance with her and show her
my moods and have a great time. So,
you know... Me being an idiot, I
went for option two and I saw dog
dragged her onto the dance floor and
as soon as I did, I realised this
was a mistake. I used to be Billy
Elliot and do a lot of dancing but
that was all choreographed. I didn't
wing it, I did not just go on stage
and do a different show every night.
I started dancing with her and...
There's not much arms in God, I'm
doing a little two step toward
myself up and she is so unimpressed!
She is so unimpressed, I just bailed
and left. "I Just can't do this!" O!
You should have fainted. So I leave
Madonna on the dance floor. The next
day I'm telling my family on phase
time, we were having a family dinner
and they wanted to know about my
evening at the Oscars and they
wanted the gossip and they wanted to
know the story, my dad is wetting
himself, my mum is cringing and then
my little brother goes, "Who's
Madonna?" APPLAUSE
Pray that she never sees this! A lot
of people have their signature... Do
you have a dance move? Is it that?
You must have something better than
that. That was a it's Madonna, I'm
stressing so much doorstop I've
adapted the last soothing a
Spiderman... Wow! Hello. It has not
worked yet, though. You look like a
man who has a signature dance move.
Of course I do. What is it? In order
to dance without getting hurt, I
stretch so I make the stretching
into the dance. It is called the
lunch. It has got a name, the Krunt
lunch. The Crunge. Can we have the
music, a bit of Kylie?
POP MUSIC
APPLAUSE
Absolutely, that's it. That is how I
Met Madonna. Yeah, auditioning for
her tour and she said no. I have not
asked you, do you have one? I don't
have one. Please do something after
that. Nothing, nothing at all! She
said you're the best that is what
she said. I Paul Blake Ward, so...
I'm not sure if the audience can top
that. Where is Jemae? I don't know
this dance, what is it called? The
turkey. I created it myself. Oh,
she's a choreographer! LAUGHTER
Ladies and gentlemen. OK, Jemae has
created this dance, when did you
make this up? Today? Know, a long
time ago. This should be good.
You've been working on it. No! What
have you selected? I Should Be So
Lucky Will Stop going back! Can you
do it on the stage? Yes. This is
Jemae giving us her turkey to I
Should Be So Lucky. . That is
beautiful! APPLAUSE
Have you ever got lucky doing that?
It works better with the sound, you
have to do the Goble.
have to do the Goble. -- gobble.
That is not a dance move, that is
just a tad gibberish and, when we do
animal oppressions, you will be
back. This will be good, where is
Drew? They're! You are giving us
two, so the first is...? Prayer
prayer, catch the flower. OK, and
the next one? Please, sir, I've got
a spider on my head. OK, we have
sort of seeing them. So what track
are you doing them to? Spinning
Around. So it is prayer, prayer,
first? Yes. Here is the music.
Excellent. Put the lights on, sir.
-- do the please, sir. APPLAUSE
Fabulous. Yes!
Where is Rhian? Is yours going to be
quite like the turkey? It's not but
it follows the same theme. What is
it called? The boneless chicken. It
is one I created myself. She took
the chicken and moved it on. Another
level. This is the boneless chicken
and is this genuinely something you
would do? I have been known to do it
in clubs. What is your track? Better
The Devil You Know. OK, this is
Rhian doing the boneless chicken to
Better The Devil You Know. APPLAUSE
That was so good! Incredible. No
disrespect to the others but the
standard has been quite low. That
took it to a different level. The
bar was raised. That is so, so good.
Thank you! Amazing. Now Tom Holland
returned as Spiderman in venue
marble spectacular... CHEERING AND
APPLAUSE
-- marvel spectacular. Fill one
opens on the 26th of April. We get
the idea of the avengers. --
Avengers: Infinity War. This is
insane, it is something like 40
superheroes in the one film.
Something like that, so overwhelming
when you watch on one set. Are you
ever all in one scene? Do you know
what? I don't know! Because I did a
lot of my scenes with Benedict
Cumberbatch with someone else, with
just dots on their faces who I guess
later in the process will become...
Benedict Cumberbatch so I don't know
the answer. So can you tell us
anything about the film? You may as
well ask me about quantum physics.
Is it true... Are you one of those
people they deliberately don't give
plot details to? I am, I definitely
am. Did you let something slip in
the past? Why do they think you are
going to tell everyone? I just tell
everyone! There are things that I
have spoiled. I was not allowed to
read the script, you know, so I
would be on set and working with
actors and actresses that were just
tennis balls for the date so I would
be texting people, "Are you in this
scene with Spiderman?" And they
would say no and I would cross them
off the list, "Are you in this
scene? Is what I had to do a lot of
background research to find out what
I was doing. Like a superhero
WhatsApp group. If there is one, I'm
not in it. I just did fight scenes
by myself imagining what would
happen. Have you seen the film yet?
I haven't even read it! I've no idea
what it's about which is quite good
fun. "Ticket For one, please!" This
will be exciting because this is a
clip and you are in it. Wow, I
haven't seen this yet? This is USB
to park on the school bus. I
remember this. -- this is you as
Peter Parker.
Hey, I need you to cause a
distraction. We are all going to
die! It's a spaceship!
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
Fantastic. That is all me, but
either way, no CGI. Very dangerous!
-- by the way. The excitement of
being Spiderman, this is your third
or fourth? My third movie. If it
still as exciting as it was or are
you a bit blase about being
Spiderman now? No, you can't,
really, I remember seeing Avengers
one with my best friend in the
cinema, so excited as a kid and now
on in it, I'm walking around with
iron man and Captain America and I
can call them peers and stuff so it
is still pretty surreal but this one
has definitely been a whirlwind. It
has been insane. I think what this
week is a lot of actors when they
get roles like this, they have to
say certain things but for you, this
is genuine because you post these
incredibly sweet pictures. This is
you as a young boy... You are
playing with yourself! LAUGHTER
But, no, that is so sweet and then
this one is amazing, I think you are
back at your house and you found
this. Yeah. That was genuinely
yours? That was my first ever
Spiderman costume which my mum who
is here tonight kept for me. Were
you one of the kids who wore it to
funerals and weddings? I slept in
that thing, it's still stinks today,
there is no power on earth that
could make it wearable. Is the
Spiderman outfit as we knew it gone
now? Oh, well, yes, it is,
basically... Spoiler alert. I have a
new suit in this film which Tony
Stark gave me, as an upgrade and it
is too fantastical to exist in real
life so essentially... There it is,
that is the first time I have seen
it, wow, it looks great. Aren't you
glad you came? So much. Is it metal?
I don't know! LAUGHTER
Essentially, I have to wear it
eventually pyjamas. I wear these
pyjamas with balls on them that
light up, it is super cool... It's
not! But I'm onset with the Avengers
who were wearing costumes that cost
hundreds of thousands of dollars
made by the best seamstresses you
can imagine and I'm there in a Marks
and 's suit. Marks and Spencer's
sued. Marks and Spencer's is an
English... Of the highest quality!
Autograph collection, hello!
APPLAUSE
John Krasinski, you were nearly in
this world, weren't you? Wow, make
me feel great! LAUGHTER
Look at this poster, John, you
almost hit that! Yes, I was
probably... 16th choice for Captain
America. But you had the costume and
everything, it was pretty close. I
got to the suit, it was a big day
for me, I was nerding out completely
and for a split second I was feeling
good about myself, they come out and
give you the suit, you get it and I
was putting it on, like, "Oh, my
God, this is an amazing", and
through the hallway came Chris
Hemsworth dressed as door and he
went, "all right?" And I was like,
"No, I'm not, I'm OK...". I ate a
burrito beforehand. No, yeah, when
you see Chris Hemsworth with next to
nothing on, you don't all of a
sudden want to be like, "I'm going
to take my clothes off". Maddy Green
imagine how I feel, these artful
blokes and I'm not battle and you
are doing a scene on a planet and
there are all these little dips and
rocks and I said to myself and
rehearsal, "Find a nice rock, you
will be fine as good. First
rehearsal, I'm on the Rock, working
with Chris Pratt, who is huge and I
was like shin height, like, "I'm
happy yet". They are setting up the
light and I'm hanging out and then I
end up in a hole. I said to myself,
just make sure you are not here when
they... "Action!" I literally stood
in a the borehole, smaller than all
of these people and I was waist
height. -- in this little hole. I
spent three days like this, awful.
Let's not forget Kylie Minogue's
great work in the seminal film
streetfighter. CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
Next one is even better. Look at her
go! Yeah... That looks like it hurt.
Yes, when you did that, did you
think, yeah, yeah, Kylie Minogue,
action star, I can do this? No, I
was mistaken. Training was fun,
yeah. I mean, look, I'm so puny that
they had to build me up. My body
changed shape and I was really
strong. Did you keep it up? No!
Emily, you've done some action
films. You've been on here talking
about them. But this December you
take on what is the greatest
superheroes of all time. Mary
Poppins. Which is... I imagine, sort
of cool and terrifying at the same
time. Yeah. It did feel quite
terrifying at first. Rob Marshall,
who directs this film, and he's
absolutely fabulous, user friend, I
worked with him before. He called me
and left this very ceremonious
message on my phone. He was like,
Emily, it Rob, call me back. I did.
He said, we're doing Mary Poppins
and I want you to be Mary Poppins. I
was like, oh, my God! So thrilling!
And scary, you know, because... I
think she is so iconic and Julie
Andrews is so iconic that it's a big
thing to take on. Ultimately, it'll
just be my version of her. This
version is mostly filmed here, am
right quiz yellow we filmed
everything here. You got to spend
time here, John. Absolutely. We need
to apologise, where we not
welcoming? Know, most people were so
welcoming. Customs, not so much. I'm
sure it's a pain for everyone, I've
got somewhere to be... Now? You guys
love it? We just walk through. I'm
in the line of 1800. I went up to...
When she was shooting I was shooting
in Montreal for... So I went to
visit the kids, and my wife. I went
through customs, everything was fine
and then one week got unlucky and
there was a guy about my age, seemed
a bit grumpy, and he said, you and
actor? I said yes. What do I know
you from? I don't know, we did the
American version of your Office.
Strike one! Oh, I loved that show.
UK version. I get it! I get it. He
said, who you visiting? I said, my
wife. Is she an actress? Yes. Would
I know her? I don't know. Who is
she? Emily Blunt. And he was writing
something and he said, you? You! All
rights, get out of here! Stamped my
passport with a Fiori. I also
encouraged him that he would be
welcome or if he stopped wearing a
baseball cap. I said to him, you
look so American! That makes it
better. You look so American... I
want you to blend in. That's
prejudice! He went out and bought
himself a tweed flat cap. He looked
awesome. Was that good? Looks like
someone out of a Guy Ritchie film.
You looked great. He walked down the
street and it was like the sun came
out because suddenly a guy turned to
him and said, all right? If you lose
the baseball cap and get flat cap...
What does it say about your country?
Was a nice question presumably
having your children spend time with
you was nice. Why American children?
You've said it kind of sneeringly...
Put your cap on, you'll be fine.
Exactly. By our American.
LAUGHTER
It's worse than the film! And then
an American came out of her! I mean,
they are semi-American... They did
become quite... Well, my eldest
daughter became quite British
sounding over the course of the year
that I was here for Mary Poppins and
she was saying things like Bath and
water and now she's back to
"wah-ter". You want the posh English
voice, Kylie, you were tricked... Is
this like the boneless chicken? Did
you develop this trick yourself?
Yes, I did. I don't know why. But to
sound very British, but, more
specifically a couple of
specifically a couple of Pimm's. We
just don't let your lips touch.
Honestly, I guarantee you, try.
APPLAUSE
That's hilarious! So good!
Go on, try it, Graham. I can't. I've
had several Pimm's. Now, Kylie, this
new album, which I have an actual
copy here.
CHEERING
This is it. Finally out today and
you know I was lucky enough to hear
some of it earlier and you know how
much I love it. The reviews. Must be
thrilled. This is... I'm pretty
chuffed, yeah. I'm just so pleased
it's worked. I guess it's like
making a film, it's such a journey
to even just launch into it again,
like the 30th year of my career of
music. Yeah, I think I could do it.
I'm really happy with the result.
You talk about how personal this
album is. A lot of the tracks are
love letters to your fans, songs
about your relationship with music.
I read an interview where you were
saying that when you started writing
the songs, they didn't work. They
were rubbish! I'm really glad they
were rubbish because I'd just gone
through a break-up, yawn! And so
kind of got all this stuff out of my
system and then I'm searching for
the songs, searching for, what is
the DNA of this album? What will it
be? Six months in, but to Nashville
and it all made sense. By that time
I'd reclaimed myself, I felt great.
I felt absolutely, so happy to be
working and kind of, you know... On
my own path again. It transpired
that the good songs came later,
which are really happy about. The
title, it's such a great title for
an album, Golden. You look so
beautiful in that picture. Thanks!
Kylie, Golden. Available now! This
is a sweet thing, going full circle.
In Australia, the album's going to
be promoted by your original label
from 30 years ago. Yes! I signed
with a company called Mushroom
Records in 1987. This is a long time
ago. This is kind of cool because,
see this album... It's older than
him!
LAUGHTER
APPLAUSE
An album that is older than a guest!
You can't look at that without...
It's not really a hat. It's more of
a... It's a glimpse. It's a brim,
yeah. That's your hair, isn't it?
Great but calling taxis.
Great but calling taxis. This is the
album that started it all. It's
dead. God, I can't believe it. So I
signed with this company in 1987,
over 30 years ago and I'm still
releasing records with them in
Australia.
OK, Kylie, the time has come -
would you like to make your way
over to your stage?
I absolutely well. Thank you.
APPLAUSE
Performing Stop Me From Falling,
from her album Golden,
it is Kylie Minogue!
CHEERING
# Somehow
# We've always been together
# But never got together
# I've never felt
the pressure till now
# There's something in the air
# I'm here and you're just there
# I can't pretend that I don't care
# Yeah
# One day I might get it right
# Am I ready for tonight?
# Yeah
# Caution, caution, amber lights
# Just can't get you off my mind
# Don't know how
# I don't know when
# But we're becoming
more than friends
# Getting closer to the edge
# Stop me from falling
# Shoulda seen the warning signs
# Now I'm running out of time
# Kinda wanna cross the line
# Stop me from falling for you
# Ooh, ooh, ooh
# For you
# Ooh, ooh
# Stop me from falling for you
# Ooh, ooh, ooh
# For you
# Ooh, ooh
# Stop me from falling
# One risk from lying
on your shoulder
# When I was feeling colder
# And now I can't get over
# One kiss
# A dangerous situation
# I'm lost in hesitation
# My heart's a little shaken
# Yeah
# One day I might get it right
# Am I ready for tonight?
# Yeah
# Caution, caution, amber lights
# Still can't get you off my mind
# Don't know how
# I don't know when
# But we're becoming
more than friends
# Getting closer to the edge
# Stop me from falling
# Shoulda seen the warning signs
# Now I'm running out of time
# Kinda wanna cross the line
# Stop me from falling for you
# Ooh, ooh, ooh
# For you
# Ooh, ooh
# Stop me from falling for you
# Ooh, ooh, ooh
# For you
# Ooh, ooh
You already? Here we go! Hey!
# Don't know how
# I don't know when
# But we're becoming
more than friends
# Getting closer to the edge
# Stop me from falling
# Shoulda seen the warning signs
# Now I'm running out of time
# Kinda wanna cross the line
# Stop me from falling for you
# Ooh, ooh, ooh
# For you
# Ooh, ooh
# Stop me from falling for you
# Ooh, ooh, ooh
# For you
# Ooh, ooh
# Stop me from falling.#
CHEERING
. Thank you!
. Thank you! Oh! Kylie Minogue,
everybody! That was terrific! I love
that! Yeah! Yeah!
that! Yeah! Yeah! So the album is
out will stop people can buy that
music now. Presumably you are
touring. Is it... September. And is
it in UK, Ireland... And I'll be
stealing some of the dance moves I
learned tonight. Of course. I
trademarked them in the break. That
boneless chicken of... All over. Is
attributable and book it is now?
Yeah. Kylie Minogue, everybody.
Nearly it but before we go, our
first visit of the series to the big
red chair. Is there? Don't know if
you want John about this. Hello.
Hello. What's your name? My name's
will. Where do you live? In Kent.
And what do you do? I'm a management
consultant. OK, the ghost. I was in
an airport lounge with my dad and he
goes off to the toilet and icy
Robbie Williams and I go to him and
say, Robbie, Kenny make me look
cool, come over to me and say, high,
well, how are you? I go back to my
seat, my dad comes back, Robbie
comes over and says, high, will, how
are you? And I say, fuck off,
Robbie, I was speaking to my dad.
APPLAUSE
You think he'd be nice and then he
turns on you! One more? One more,
OK. Hello! Hello. What's your name?
George. Lovely. Where do you live?
Peter Browne the moment. At the
moment? At any moment, you could
move. Really, it's a Winnebago.
That's where he's parked at the
moment. What do you do in Peter
Breen? I'm a teacher. A teacher of?
Primary school. Primary school. All
the ages? Usually the upper end, 11
and 12. OK, the ones that can talk.
LAUGHTER
Of you go. So this is probably the
most mortifying moment of my life
ever. There was one day when the
children pushed me too far and I
thought, no, you're sitting in
silence, I'm not having it. One boy
who is really quite studious was
doodling in the corner and I
thought, absolutely not, I'll make
as little two showcase out of this.
I brought up to the front and he
brought his doodle with him and
added the classic tea just above,
you made a mockery of your
education, the education of
everybody this classroom. And then
he started crying and I thought, why
decrying question might not funny
but maybe I'm getting through to him
finally. The rest of the class then
noticed at the same time that I did
that the doodle he'd been drawing
said, our IP Nanna, and she'd died
recently -- RIP Nanna. I love that
story.
Well done, everyone.
If you'd like to join us on the show
and have a go in the red chair,
you can contact us via our website
at this address.
That's it for tonight -
please say thank you to my
guests - Tom Holland...
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
Kylie Minogue...
John Krasinski...
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
And Emily Blunt.
Join me next week with rock
legend Roger Daltrey,
Sherlock and Hobbit star
Martin Freeman, Oscar-nominated Brit
Naomie Harris and the mighty Rock
himself, Dwayne Johnson.
I'll see you then!
Goodnight.