Good evening, I'm Harrison Ford.
And I'm Ryan Gosling.
BOTH: Welcome to the
Graham Norton Show.
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
Oh, oh, oh, oh!
Oh, hello, what a
lovely welcome back!
Thank you very much everybody.
Hello, and welcome!
Did you all have a nice summer?
AUDIENCE: Yes!
I know some people
are still on holiday.
They hadn't planned it that
way, it's just they had
tickets with Ryanair.
LAUGHTER
18,000 further cancellations
announced this week.
I mean, the whole thing
could cost Ryanair ?17
million in compensation.
I mean, they're hoping
to make that back by
selling two packets of Pringles
on their next flight, but, still...
LAUGHTER
The good news, though is that
Ryanair customer services have been
very sympathetic to passengers.
You know, advising them to use
the exits here, here and here.
LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE
You'll all be aware
of the big news, of course.
Twitter are trialling a plan
for a new 280 character limit.
280 characters!
It's more than you get
in Game of Thrones.
LAUGHTER
People will now be able to tweet
their followers twice as many of
their thoughts...
LAUGHTER
Uh-oh...
Hey, it might keep him busy
so he won't have time
to start World War three!
Tensions with North Korea continue.
This week leader Kim Jong-un
said Donald Trump was
"Mentally deranged".
Hello, kettle?
LAUGHTER
I mean...
That's like Trump accusing Kim
Jong-un of having weird hair!
Let's get some guests on!
Later we'll have music
from pop icons Bananarama!
CHEERING
Yes!
They're back, Bananarama,
and they'll be performing
Cruel Summer.
But first, this Aussie star went
from Neighbours' Ramsay Street
to The Wolf of Wall Street
and is now one of the most in-demand
actors in Hollywood -
it's Margot Robbie, everybody!
CHEERING
It is Margot Robbie.
Hello!
I was looking at the curtain...
Is she, is she?
She's here, Margot Robbie!
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
This Oscar winning star
and producer has given us hits
like Legally Blonde,
Walk the Line and Big Little Lies -
it's a warm welcome back
to Reese Witherspoon.
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
Oh!
Hello!
Reese Witherspoon!
And we've waited 35 years
for a sequel to Blade Runner -
at last it's here.
Please welcome the stars
of Blade Runner 2049 -
Ryan Gosling and Harrison Ford.
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
Hello, sir!
Very nice to see you again.
All right, that's all right, please,
please, have a seat.
They seem pleased!
They seem pleased
with their line-up.
Lovely to see you all.
Reece and Harrison, do you know each
other out of show business land?
A little bit.
I've seen her in the
parking lot at school!
LAUGHTER
At school!
At school, yeah.
Picking up and dropping off.
So do you do the school
run, Harrison?
My son is now of driving age.
Oh.
Yes.
LAUGHTER
My daughter can drive, too.
So she drives her little brother.
It's a different world, isn't it?
Here, no one drives to school.
Really?
Unless they're a bus driver,
they don't drive to school.
LAUGHTER
That's a good thing.
Reese Witherspoon, how
hot are you right now?
The Emmys, how many...?
Thank you.
We won eight Emmy awards.
APPLAUSE
Yes, a round of applause.
What a brilliant night
it must have been.
I was nervous, though,
because there were so many people
nominated in our team,
and instead of just, you know...
I was just worried every single time
that they talked about somebody
that they weren't going to win,
I was just nervous.
So by the time we won, I went
backstage and I burst into tears.
Ahh.
Yeah, nervous.
Ryan, the last time you were here
was to celebrate La La Land.
And of course that went
on to win all sorts
of accolades and win things.
APPLAUSE
Yes.
Do
Do you
Do you want
Do you want my
Do you want my drink?
I want to clap, too.
At the end of the Oscars...
I don't know what
you're talking about!
Well...
At the end of the Oscars when La La
Land didn't win, but had won.
There's a picture of you...
This is right when I think you find
out that La La Land hadn't won.
Yeah...
What emotion is this?
LAUGHTER
It was so good!
Did you see what the
crowd looked like?
Oh, we've got a picture of that,
the crowd were amazing.
Matt Damon looks like he's
swallowed his own teeth!
LAUGHTER
With shock, look at him!
I mean, it was like they were
watching their childhood
homes catch fire.
LAUGHTER
The Rock has never cared
about anything more.
LAUGHTER
Were you there, you guys?
I wasn't, I was shooting
in Atlanta at the time.
I was watching on TV, though.
I had a similar
expression to that, yeah.
That must have been a bonkers
moment, when that all went down?
Well, it was...
You know, interesting.
But it was, you know, unexpected.
But I thought someone had
been hurt, you know?
The way everyone was talking amongst
themselves, it felt like someone had
a heart attack or worse and it felt
like someone was in danger.
And then I found out that they just
read the wrong name.
LAUGHTER
Now, here's the thing,
I would have thought Harrison Ford,
that you wouldn't like these
sorts of award bashes,
that you'd never go,
but you do go, don't you?
On the rare occasions that I've got
anything to do with it.
Yeah.
Which is usually
presenting an award.
LAUGHTER
That's an honour.
Is it?
Then I've won.
LAUGHTER
Because Margot, she is
an enormous Harrison Ford fan.
It's true, isn't it?
Yeah, I am.
This is really weird.
That's why we separated you.
It's going to stay that way.
This is your intervention.
LAUGHTER
I mean, to be honest...
Disabuse you of
that notion.
And you'll help, won't you?
Don't you worry.
I can count on him!
I have to admit something, Harrison.
Though Indiana Jones is one
of the most iconic characters ever,
my favourite movie that you're
in is actually Six
Days, Seven Nights.
Oooh...
APPLAUSE A very good movie,
if you haven't seen it.
I guess it's still available.
LAUGHTER
I hope so.
I should stay on this side
of the couch, shouldn't I?
I'm getting too excited.
I have a bunch of DVDs
in the back of my car,
I'll meet you out in the street.
LAUGHTER
SOMEONE BLOWING THEIR NOSE
Oh, you saw it.
LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE
Now let's start tonight
with Harrison and Ryan's movie,
it's the much awaited
Blade Runner 2049.
It opens on the 5th of October,
and I mean the expectation,
the hopes that this film are high.
Ridley Scott is involved,
Harrison, you're involved.
But presumably this
isn't the first time...
I'm not just involved.
You're in it, you're in it.
You are on the poster!
APPLAUSE
But, OK, my question is this.
There must have been mentions
of a sequel between...
It was 1982, wasn't
it, when it came out?
So between then and now,
so why now, why not before?
I guess because Ryan
wasn't available.
LAUGHTER
For many years
he was unavailable?
Yes, well not for 30 years.
But they were waiting
for me to grow up.
But they decided they'd
have to go ahead anyway.
They finally came up with a story.
I read it and I thought it was
awesome, I thought it was great.
And as I read it, I read
about the character that Ryan...
Ryan?
It's Ryan.
LAUGHTER
That Ryan came to play and I said,
with great enthusiasm,
I called up the producers
and I said, this is great,
can't wait, blah, blah, blah,
and what a great part...
Why don't we see if we can get...
Ryan.
Ryan Gosling.
And they said, oh, I don't...
Did you say Rosling?
Ryan Gosling.
Good, right.
You got that on tape, Ryan Gosling?
And I said, it's a great
part for Ryan Gosling.
LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE
And they said we've been
talking to him for months.
Now wait a second, they'd only been
speaking to me for weeks.
LAUGHTER
So they probably would have
gone ahead without me.
No!
No?
No.
That's what I said, no.
Because the fact is,
Ryan, when the movie
came out, you were two?
Yeah, that's right.
Sorry about that!
LAUGHTER
So when did you first
become aware of this film?
I was about 12, and Harrison likes
to say where was your mother and why
was she letting you watch it at 12?
Well...
That's another story.
LAUGHTER
Let's keep this nice, OK?
I didn't know what I
was getting into.
I thought I was just
about to watch, you know,
a regular science fiction film,
I guess.
Yeah.
But it's a little more than that.
So you are Deckard again,
so who are you, Ryan?
I play...
You want to field that one?
Can't tell you anything about it.
LAUGHTER
Shall we watch a clip?
I can tell you anything!
So the questions we were left
with at the end of the first
Blade Runner, are they all answered
in this one?
No.
OK.
We'll watch a clip, this is,
I believe, in the story, Ryan's
character is looking for you.
He finds you but he's not alone.
They know you're here.
I came alone.
DRAMATIC MUSIC
EXPLOSION
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
Now we saw there some action
and things do take preparation,
like fights take preparation.
They take a lot of preparation.
Yes, now Ryan...
Harrison feels...
Here we go.
Harrison feels, Ryan, you were
underprepared for one fight.
No...
I know what you're referring to.
Yes.
Just say it.
Use your words.
Stop beating around the bush.
He punched you.
Yeah, that's right.
"Well, he punched you".
LAUGHTER
Yeah, of
course I punched him.
But you weren't meant to punch him.
Right?
Oh, I misread the script.
LAUGHTER
He stepped on my foot,
for Christ's sake.
We were doing a scene in lights,
in flashing strobe lights.
He was walking backward,
I was walking forward,
the camera was hand-held.
You know, you have to make the punch
look like it's intended.
Yes.
But I hit him.
LAUGHTER
One out of
100 times I hit him.
Right, right, I should be lucky
I didn't get hit more.
Is the theme of this.
I apologised...
It's not just a punch,
though, I think it's
like a Harrison Ford punch
is a different animal altogether.
It was not, it was not a good punch.
I just...
I will be the judge of that.
LAUGHTER
I tried to apologise.
I went to his dressing room,
his palatial motorhome.
With a bottle of Scotch in hand.
Lovely gesture.
Cracked the top, poured him a drink,
gave him a drink...
He said, I'm kind of busy now.
LAUGHTER
And I went back to my trailer,
with the rest of the bottle.
LAUGHTER
I had the intention
to leave it but...nah!
My hand hurts.
I needed some medicine.
Actually we do have,
there's a still, I think.
This is the actual moment
when you punched Ryan for real.
LAUGHTER
Look at his face!
Is that the face
of regret or is that just,
I really hurt my hand?
No, that's the face of oh, shit,
I'm in deep doo-doo.
LAUGHTER Harrison Ford,
here you are, Blade Runner.
But Indiana Jones, is it
five, is coming next?
Yeah.
APPLAUSE
Five, yes.
Yeah.
That's all, that's
definitely happening now?
Yes, it is.
OK, just asking.
We have a release date.
We're working on a script.
It will be great.
I'm looking forward
to working with Steven again,
revisiting the character.
I think that can be
a good thing to do.
I've heard you talk about how
Indiana Jones is one of those things
where you might as well do it
because you cannot escape it,
especially the music
is a constant thing in your life.
CHUCKLES
I did a tribute
for John Williams and they played
me on with the theme
from Indiana Jones, and I said,
I cannot escape this god dam music.
I said, and this is true,
I hear it in the elevator,
the last time I was lightly sedated
and rolled in for a colonoscopy they
were playing it on the speakers.
LAUGHTER
INDIANA JONES THEME TUNE PALYS
-- PLAYS
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
A special treat.
Right, Reese Witherspoon's
new movie is Home Again,
which opens tonight.
Now, you look at the poster
and you think, OK, it's a rom-com,
and it is a rom-com,
but in fact it is different,
it's kind of got an edgy twist.
Yeah, my character's recently
separated, she's a single mum,
she is contemplating getting
divorced, so she moves back
home to her family home,
and she starts a relationship
with a 26-year-old guy.
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
Because guys
do all the time, so why not girls?
Yeah, yes.
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
And, you know, you're the star
of the film, so do you get,
are you in on the casting
of your younger love interest?
Yeah, I thought it was important
that I really got to know
the actors really well
during the casting process.
We saw a lot of guys.
A lot of them came back
for multiple readings, but yeah,
I think we got a really great cast.
We've got a clip.
This is you with your young admirer.
This is the morning after.
Hey, Alice.
Yeah?
Do you have a minute?
Sure.
Could we may be just exchange
phone numbers or...?
Harry, I'm really...
Listen, I think you woke up
to a completely different person
than you met last night,
and I appreciate the gesture,
I really do, but how
old are you, like 30?
29?
28?
Something like that.
Oh, Jesus.
OK girls, come on,
time to get in the car.
OK, OK!
She's so intense.
No, I'm not.
Good luck with everything,
maybe I'll see you around.
I hope so.
Come on, ladies.
Did you guys have a sleepover?
Are you friends with his mum?
With his mum, how old do I look?
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
There's three generations,
there's your mum in it,
played by the great Candice Bergen.
Yeah, Candy, yeah, Candice Bergen.
There she is.
In her "Free Melania" sweatshirt.
LAUGHTER
She's rad,
she's really cool.
I've worked with her twice now,
she's got great stories.
She actually went on a date
with Donald Trump.
When she was in college.
It's kind of crazy.
It's really cool.
It's a great story!
I mean, it looks like one of those
films that is just a pleasure
to make because of her...
Yeah, it was really fun,
we shot it about ten
minutes from my house.
Ten minutes from school.
So I could do the drop off
and just go to work.
But it was a great time.
We made it really fast
and for not a lot of money.
It was very much...
It was a great story to actually dig
into, character wise.
And your real mom, has
she seen this film?
Because I know she likes
to review your work.
Yes, she has seen this film, yeah.
Good reviews?
She likes it, yeah, she thought
it was like a feel-good movie.
She writes these funny text messages
after she sees movies and they're
really short and they will be like,
like the movie, three boys, hot.
Love, Mom.
She liked Big Little Lies.
You Instagrammed some texts.
Oh, yeah.
I asked if she had seen Big Little
Lies when it first premiered.
This was her text.
LAUGHTER.
She has reviewed some of the work
of some of your couch mates.
Yeah.
She liked La La Land a lot.
Like, a lot!
She was like, La La Land, singing,
dancing, sexy, Ryan.
Does she put Mom at
the end of all of them?
She puts heart, Mom.
The reviews are in...
Heart, Mom.
Is she a fan of Harrison Ford?
Of course!
OK.
I mean, he might be one
of her favourites of all time.
Oh, I see...
"Might be".
We talked about the success
of Big Little Lies at the Emmys.
It is extraordinary,
the producing side of your life
is a really major part of your life
and I didn't realise that went
all the way back to Legally Blonde?
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE.
Legally Blonde 2, then?
Yes, I produced Legally Blonde 2.
It's not as good as Legally Blonde!
It took me a few
years to get better!
It took me a few years to figure out
the producing thing.
But it did take a while...
You would think, Reese Witherspoon,
people would take you seriously,
but how many studios passed
when you were pitching
Gone Girl as a movie?
Oh, yeah.
I got the book of Gone Girl
and I took it to every studio
and every studio passed,
except for one.
They were quite happy,
I would imagine?
They actually lost it after that.
It's kind of a crazy story.
Then the book hit number one
and another studio came in that
turned it down and bought it
for five times the amount of money.
That's good, isn't it?
I guess it's good.
I kind of figured out through that
process that nobody reads books!
When you try to explain it to them.
That's good for movie-making!
That'll keep us in business!
Margot, already you are tapping
into that side of the business,
you are doing a lot
of producing already?
Yeah, our first feature will be
out later this year.
Is that your first one?
Yeah, that's the first
one to be released.
We actually have filmed two and we
are in preproduction for our third.
Wow!
Are you in them all?
The first three, yes.
But after this, no.
OK.
It seems like the business
part of your brain was
developed quite young?
You were a little girl
and you were quite business savvy.
I was quite savvy as a kid.
I would steal my brother's toys
and sell them on the side of
the road for an extortionate price.
I would make up magic tricks
and make my family pay to come
and see my magic show and then pay
extra if they wanted to know
how I did the trick!
That's a really good idea!
You would pay extra to find out
how they do the tricks.
Once you get them in, they already
paid their dollar, sure!
Because, Ryan, you were also a young
entrepreneur, weren't you?
I wouldn't say that.
Didn't your father, he wanted
you to sell, was it cellophane?
My parents came upon a truck
of cellophane somehow.
I was asked not to ask
too many questions.
I just suddenly...
There was a basement
filled with cellophane.
And they encouraged me
to go to school and see
if I could sell it to my teachers.
I put a few in my backpack and tried
to hock them at recess.
Convince kids that they might be
good stocking stuffers
for their parents.
What are the uses of cellophane?
How did it go?
What do you mean, what are
the uses of cellophane?
I know the name but I don't
know what to do with it.
You wrap sandwiches in it,
it keeps things fresh.
Oh, OK.
I'm sorry.
No, it was an important question,
you needed to ask it.
I'm not doing a good job
of selling it, obviously.
Did you sell it?
There's still some left,
if you're interested?
Knowing that it keeps
things fresh, I want some.
The dream would be someone
would just say, I'll take all of it!
Never happened.
That's a weird story.
It is a bit weird, now you tell it.
It seemed like a good
idea at the time.
Harrison, famously you worked
as a carpenter in your early life.
But you studied woodwork with your
father, but he wasn't that good.
My dad was in advertising
and he liked to make things
and we were down in the basement
working on building a table
and he cut off his finger.
Why are you laughing?
He's laughing!
It's quite funny when
it's told like that.
It wasn't funny.
At the time.
I was 16 years old.
I had not much experience with this
but I wrapped my dad's hand up
and I got him upstairs and I called
the police and then I ran downstairs
and I picked up the finger and I put
it in a Kleenex and this was a long
time ago so when I got
to the emergency ward I said...
Here's my dad's...
And he went...
And threw it in the bin,
in the trash bin.
Because it was a while ago
and they didn't really think
about trying to attach fingers.
If only you had some cellophane.
Yeah!
Thank you.
Who knew?
Yeah.
Did he just have no finger?
He had no finger here.
He cut off about this
much of this finger.
Why are you pointing that at me?
I'm not pointing it at you.
He got about halfway
through this finger as well.
But they were able to save that.
But my father, he used
to admonish me sometimes
and he would point at me.
But he would be pointing at me
but his finger was going like that.
So I would always look...
It really made him mad.
APPLAUSE.
Reece, very quickly,
to bring you back to Legally Blonde,
there was a thing last year,
when it hit the headlines...
President Trump, he made
the commencement speech.
Oh, yeah.
And then it turned out it bore quite
a strong resemblance to Elle's
speech in Legally Blonde.
Yeah.
It did!
Was it Jimmy Fallon
who found this out?
It was all over the internet.
Maybe it was on Jimmy's show.
If you haven't seen it,
it's sort of unbelievable.
Show them the thing?
As we take our next
steps into the world.
We must go forth into the world.
It is with passion.
Passion.
Courage of conviction.
Courage in your convictions.
And strong sense of self.
Be true to yourself.
We did it.
I did it.
APPLAUSE.
Had you not seen that?
No!
I have never seen that and I always
fall down YouTube rabbit holes
and I missed that completely!
He is better when he
sticks to the script.
APPLAUSE.
Do you know how that happened?
Is he just a fan of the film?
I'm sure he's just a big fan.
Very bizarre.
Let's move on to Margot Robbie's
movie, it's a very British movie,
it's called Goodbye Christopher
Robin.
It opens tonight.
And it's the real story and a much
darker story than you think it's
going to be of AA Milne,
the man who created
the Winnie the Pooh stories.
Yeah, Winnie the Pooh was always
prevalent throughout my childhood
but I had never wondered its origins
or why or when it was written.
It was written right
between World War I and World War II
and AA Milne, the author,
very famous author, actually
fought in World War I.
And part of the reason
it was so successful is because it
came at a time when the country
was very damaged and the world
was damaged and people kind
of felt they were robbed
of their innocence, probably.
And the books became this safe place
for people and became
this global phenomenon.
And Domhnall Gleeson plays AA Milne
and you play Daphne,
his wife and the mother
of Christopher Robin.
Yeah.
She's a piece of work.
She is complicated.
Yes.
She is not immediately likeable
and maybe she is not even that
likeable by the end...
I really love her.
She had her own trauma,
he was dealing with PTSD,
although it was not really coined
that term back then.
They didn't really
speak about it then.
And she had postnatal
depression and they didn't
really talk about that.
There was a lot of stiff upper lip,
not talking about your feelings.
But they had this child
and he was brilliant and Will,
who plays him, is the most gorgeous
kid you have ever seen -
a brilliant actor.
He makes everyone cry when they see
it, including myself,
and I know what's going to happen
in the film but I still cry.
And they love him but they kind
of end up ruining his childhood
by him becoming so famous.
Because that was the thing
I didn't understand.
Christopher Robin became
a sort of Shirley Temple,
Macauley Culkin figure.
That's what they said, he was
the Macauley Culkin of his time.
Yeah.
There was no real distinction
between him in real life
and him on the books.
His name is Christopher Robin,
he was drawn, he was
photographed everywhere.
It was pretty traumatic for him.
So there are some of
those sad parts to it.
But there's also a lot of nice,
happy moments, too.
This is one of the nice,
happy moments.
This is you entertaining
young Christopher Robin
with the original bear.
Well, I say, this is
an unexpected pleasure.
Have you come to see my woods?
Are they really your woods?
Oh, yes.
As far as the eye can see.
Well, a bear does feel more
at home in the woods
amongst the wild animals.
Are there really wild animals?
I can't continue this
conversation until we have been
properly introduced.
I'm Billy Moon.
And you're teddy bear.
Edward Bear, if you don't mind.
I don't like that name.
Mummy will have to
think of a new one.
You do know it's me
talking and not a bear?
I was just playing.
Yes, I was just joining in.
APPLAUSE.
He's so sweet.
And a very good English accent.
Great!
Thank you.
A very specific English accent?
Yes, it's like a 1930s one.
And an aristocratic Englishwoman,
it's very specific, not just
a traditional RP accent.
I hear you had a mental trick
for getting yourself into it?
Yeah, when I'm doing accents I need
a phrase to get into it.
When I did Wolf of Wall Street,
I had a phrase and when
I did this one I...
So in Wolf of Wall Street
I would be like...
NEW YORK ACCENT: I'm not talking
to you, I'm talking to her.
OK, I'm ready to do it.
On this one, it was...
POSH ACCENT: I'm so happy, no,
I simply couldn't do that.
It's not a line in the script
or anything and it doesn't
make sense as a line.
It was like, I don't know...
The thing I would say,
and it helped me.
You are kind of an honorary
Brit because you have
spent a lot of time here.
How long did you live here for?
I just begrudgingly moved...
We have a production office in LA.
But I was living here
for the last three years.
OK.
And I don't know why
I would be surprised
because you are Margot Robbie living
in London, so of course you did...
But you did mix in some
highfalutin circles?
Yes, oh yes.
I don't know where this
picture came from...
That's obviously you.
Is that Sienna Miller?
Yeah, I think so.
And that's a princess.
Is that a Beatrice
one or a Eugenie one?
I can't tell by the picture.
It kind of looks weird.
You are picking everyone
better than I can.
I think it's one of them.
Tell us who this is.
You know who that is.
I know, but tell us.
It's Prince Harry.
I don't normally go to parties
where those people are there.
That was a one-off.
That doesn't normally happen.
My friends aren't Royals!
There, of course, is Cara Delvingne.
She is a good friend of mine.
You were in Suicide Squad together.
Yes.
She was awesome.
In Suicide Squad, you tattooed
the cast members, is this right?
Yes.
Because you were trained...
These are the tattoos you do.
Yeah, we called them Toemojis.
Oh?
OK.
And did you do all the cast?
No, funnily enough, no
one else wanted them!
So, just the two of
us got the Toemojis.
But everyone else got squad written
on them and other people would come
by the trailer and get anything.
Yes, we did all sorts of things.
So you can still tattoo people?
Yet, I reckon I have done...
Yeah, getting close to 100.
Little ones.
And honestly, they are probably
getting worse as they go along.
Because we have a tattoo gun here.
If anyone...
If any of your coach
mates want a tattoo?
To commemorate this lovely evening?
LAUGHTER.
You pierced your ear.
I what?
Yeah, not myself.
It would be so funny.
Please?
Bless you for thinking it might...
I have seen you actually
are prepared...
Yes.
She can tattoo at will.
This is not actually my gun
but I can make do with it, for sure.
You're genuinely
thinking about this?
No!
I didn't think you were.
I thought you were!
That's acting!
APPLAUSE.
Ryan isn't looking so shocked
because you have already tattooed
yourself, haven't you?
Yeah.
How did that go for you?
Not great.
What did you do?
It was, you know, it was supposed
to be a monster hand
dropping a bloody heart.
But it looks more like a chicken...
Making love with a
cactus or something.
I don't know what happened.
My friend had one at his
house, I like to doodle,
it's a bad combination.
Do you have a tattoo?
Oh, God.
I knew you were going to ask that.
Do you?
Yeah, I do.
Where is it?
I went to college in the '90s.
Can we just leave it there.
Is it a tramp stamp?
No!
Oh, God, no!
Is it a dolphin?
No, no, no.
Is it a...?
I'm not getting it.
The thing is, there is someone
who works on our team and they are
a big Margot Robbie fan.
And when I say they are willing to
do this, I mean they are very keen.
He has washed his feet, talced them.
Is it difficult to do
this Toemoji thing?
No.
Adam, your moment is here,
this is happening.
So, sit down beside Margot, there.
I don't mean to criticise
my own production team
but you could have taken your shoes
and socks off first.
It would have saved a little time.
You knew this moment was coming.
I wanted to make it more real.
OK, here we go.
You don't have to do this
if you don't want to.
Honestly, he kept saying
he wants to do this.
Are you sure?
OK.
Oh, my God.
There is something I have to say...
Don't try this at home!
Really don't!
I will sit on this side of you.
OK, perfect.
OK, here we go.
In your own time.
It is not that easy to do!
Here we go.
I haven't actually
done one for a while.
I'm probably more
nervous than you are.
Sorry, that's not comforting!
That wasn't very professional.
I'm so scared!
I was going to say my hands
are shaking but you don't
want to hear that.
TATTOO GUN BUZZES.
This is nuts!
APPLAUSE.
OK.
Sorry!
TATTOO GUN BUZZES.
Does it hurt?
It's a little funny.
Don't worry about your finest work.
You do seem happy in your work,
I'll give you that.
I really do.
I'm not particularly good
but I like doing it.
APPLAUSE.
Good poker face, Adam, very good.
Sorry, is that all right?
It's good.
I can neaten it up
when we are backstage.
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE.
Show it to that camera.
There it is!
That's not bad!
It's not bad!
Obviously, trained medics
are coming to the studio.
In the meantime,
it's time for music.
These pop pioneers have sold over
40 million records and are one
of the greatest girl bands
of all time.
Now the original line-up
is back - hurrah!
Performing Cruel Summer,
please welcome Bananarama!
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE.
# Hot summer streets.
# And the pavements are burning.
# I sit around.
# Trying to smile.
# But the air is so heavy and dry.
# Strange voices are saying.
# What did they say.
# Things I can't understand.
# It's too close for comfort.
# This heat has got.
# Right out of hand.
# It's a cruel, cruel summer.
# Leaving me here on my own.
# Now you're gone.
# The city is crowded.
# My friends are away.
# And I'm on my own.
# It's too hot to handle.
# So I got to get up and go.
# It's a cruel, cruel summer.
# Leaving me here on my own
# Now you're gone.
# It's a cruel, cruel summer.
# Leaving me.
# Leaving me here on my own.
# It's a cruel, cruel summer.
# Now you're gone.
# Leaving me here on my own.
# It's a cruel, cruel summer.
# Now you're gone.
# Leaving me here on my own.
# It's a cruel, cruel summer.
# Now you're gone.
# Now you've gone.
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE.
Oh, Bananarama, everybody!
So, so good.
Come on over, ladies.
Here they are!
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
Very lovely to see you,
hello, my darling.
Hello.
Hello!
Come and sit down.
I think, I think you'll all fit on.
Will we all fit on?
Hi.
I think we'll all fit in.
There we go.
Bananarama back in the world.
We're all squeeze on, yes.
We're good, we're good,
we won't be here for long.
So, Bananarama, honestly,
a great night for the 80s.
Blade Runner back, now Bananarama.
CHEERING
Obviously Britain really
excited that Bananarama are back,
but we forget it's a global thing.
Yeah.
Cruel Summer, that was a top ten hit
in America, wasn't it?
Yes.
It's still remembered fondly.
I often hear it in the supermarket.
LAUGHTER
And it's in Blue Crush.
That's right.
The first time we thought we'd
actually maybe made it was in LA,
because we were coming back
from breakfast, about to go
to the beach, on the bus,
in Santa Monica, on the bus.
And we saw Mike Tyson sitting
on the front of his limo
and he started singing Cruel Summer
at us, and we were like wow.
LAUGHTER
We made it!
With our beach bags.
And this is a tour,
you're back for a tour.
Yes.
We've got we've got Siobhan back
in the fold for a tour.
We've never actually
toured together.
We went on a world tour
just after Siobhan left.
Just after I left.
LAUGHTER
Bye!
And it was great.
But we've never actually
done anything together.
The tickets sold out, because
the response was so fantastic.
We had to add another
ten dates, which was...
I'm not sure how we're
going to manage it, to be honest.
We've got 23 dates now
between November than 9th and
December the 9th.
OK.
At our age!
LAUGHTER
It is so great to have
Bananarama back in our world.
Ladies and gentlemen, Bananarama!
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
Bananarama!
OK, that is nearly it.
But before we go, let's make our
first visit of the new series
to the Big Red Chair.
Who's there?
Hello.
Hi, what's your name?
Justine.
Justine, and what do
you do, Justine?
I'm a barrister.
And actual barrister?
Yes.
Like a working one?
Like people might see you in courts
over the coming weeks?
Yes, yes.
And you've chosen to do this, OK!
LAUGHTER
Off you go with your story.
My mother's a very conservative
Irish lady, and she is naturally
protective of me and of my
daughters, her grandchildren,
and she's always going on about all
the weirdos there are in the world
that the girls have got to avoid.
And one particular day my eldest
daughter, who was then 14,
wanted to go to the zoo
with a girlfriend of hers,
a little friend, but no adults, and,
of course, my mother thought this
was an appalling idea.
How could that possibly
happen, there's weirdos
everywhere at the zoo.
The 14-year-old, in the sort
of attempt to placate granny said,
well, you know, perhaps the Anaconda
keeper's a bit weird,
to which my mother, not realising
what she said,
grandma just turned
around and said...
"You make sure that if anyone asks
you to come and look
at his Anaconda, you say no."
LAUGHTER
That's a great story,
you can walk, you can walk.
No, flip me!
Oh you want to be flipped.
OK, there you go!
Well done.
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
If you'd like to join us on the show
and have a go in the big red chair,
you can contact us via our website
at this very address.
That's it for tonight -
please say thank you to my
guests, Bananarama...
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
Margot Robbie...
Reese Witherspoon...
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
Ryan Gosling...
And, Mr Harrison Ford!
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
Join me next week with rock
star Liam Gallagher,
legendary stand-up Chris Rock,
actor Idris Elba and
Oscar-winner Kate Winslet.
I'll see you then!
Goodnight everybody, goodbye!
I am a fine-tuned
moneymaking machine.