Our car
This programme contains
some strong language.
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
Thank you!
Good evening!
You're very welcome!
I'm delighted to tell
you we have a great
show for you tonight.
My sofa's attracted more celebrities
than a dodgy offshore tax scheme.
Yes, everyone's talking
about the Paradise Papers.
There have even been investigations
into the Royal Family's
financial affairs.
And you know it's bad
when they start probing
the Queen's loophole.
The papers also suggest Prince
Charles has money put away offshore.
Charles hasn't been able
to respond, as he's currently
out of the country...
Visiting his money.
Is he wearing a mankini?
In political news, Minister
for International Development Priti
Patel hasn't had the best of weeks.
On Wednesday she flew back
from Africa for a meeting
with Theresa May, and was met
at the airport by a taxi driver
holding up one of those signs.
Luckily, all these
ministerial sackings aren't
bothering Theresa May.
She's just carrying on with today's
cabinet meeting as usual.
LAUGHTER
And finally,
Donald Trump has been
visiting Asia this week,
whether they like it or not.
Turns out - not!
South Korean protestors have taken
to trolling Trump on Twitter.
Although interestingly,
if you Google the words 'Troll'
and 'Trump' you get this.
LAUGHTER
For Christmas!
And that's not the only
likeness of Trump that's
been spotted this week.
A woman in Tyneside noticed
Donald Trump's face
inside her dog's ear.
Earhole, arsehole.
You decide.
Let's get some guests on!
Later we'll have music
and chat from singing
sensation Kelly Clarkson!
She'll be performing her
new single 'Love So Soft'.
But first, she's one
of the UK's top comedians,
and now she's turned author
with her new book,
'How To Be Champion',
please welcome back Sarah Millican!
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
Hello!
Lovely to see you!
Sarah Millican, everybody.
He's gone from Khal Drogo in Game
of Thrones to Aquaman
in Justice League - it's
a first-time welcome
to Mr Jason Momoa!
CHEERING
Hello!
Good to see you.
And from Four Weddings
and a Funeral to Notting Hill,
Love Actually and Bridget Jones,
he's become one of our most beloved
stars, now playing a scene-stealing
villain in Paddington 2,
it's always a pleasure to welcome
the great Hugh Grant!
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
Very nice to see you.
Often people come in from superhero
movies and they're just
sort of like actors,
but you're it!
How tall are you?
I think 6'5".
6'5"!
Yeah.
Wow.
It's funny because my dad's
like 5'9" and my mum's like 5'8".
So where did you come from them?
LAUGHTER
Questions were asked!
Sarah Millican.
Very lovely to have you here.
Thanks.
Obviously I'm sure you enjoy
Jason Momoa's work.
But I know you are
a fan of Mr Grant.
Yes.
Hi!
LAUGHTER
Shut up!
Of course, isn't everybody?
CHEERING
No.
You're so nice but...
Lots of people hate me.
LAUGHTER
My son hates me.
He came to see Paddington 2
the other day and all he said
throughout the whole film is,
why is daddy in it so much?
LAUGHTER
My favourite is Sense
and Sensibility I love it.
I watch it...
Is weekly bad?
LAUGHTER
No, I watch it weekly too.
Do you really watch it that often?
It's one of my, it's a comfort film,
let's call it that, of three.
Do you want to know
what the other ones are?
Yes, very much.
Sense and Sensibility,
Muppets Christmas Carol,
regardless of what time of year.
And San Andreas.
Which is a disaster
film with The Rock.
LAUGHTER It's quite
a good mix of things.
Yes, mix it up!
Now, Jason, you've only
just got to Britain.
Yeah, I've been here
for probably a week.
OK.
But you seem to like it here.
You go out and about.
Yes.
I'm known for my shenanigans and...
Enjoying the scenery.
Yes.
We spotted you around
London with your widow
from Game of Thrones.
Yes.
Emilia Clarke posted this
picture of the two of you.
What a nice picture!
When was this?
Last week?
That was like three days ago.
I flew over to Belfast,
I got back from Belfast right now.
So Belfast in November.
Why are you wearing a vest, Jason?
LAUGHTER
Is it because
he looks like this?
This is the first time
I ever wore a turtleneck.
My mother's going to
be very proud of me.
But I'm going to be close to peeling
this off and getting the...
I'm fine with that!
CHEERING
I get hot!
Don't let us stop you.
Let's all go topless!
Come on.
CHEERING
But fans must
go crazy when they see
the two of you together.
I go crazy when I see her.
Do they want you to start
talking in, is it Dothraki?
Dothraki, yeah.
It's all nonsense but you do
speak some Dothraki.
I've been known to say a few things.
Go on then.
LAUGHTER
For the ladies...
OK!
Sorry, I know I love you but sorry.
Oh!
SPEAKS DOTHRAKI.
And for the gentleman...
Oh yes!
LAUGHTER
SPEAKS DOTHRAKI.
He's got so much more to say to men!
LAUGHTER
APPLAUSE
Listen, the first film we're
going to talk about tonight
is Hugh Grant starring
in Paddington 2.
It opens tonight and I loved
the first one so I think people
are kind of worried about this
but honestly, it's as good
if not better and you
are brilliant in it,
Hugh Grant.
Who do you play?
Well, I...
I got a letter with a script saying
we're making Paddington 2
and there's this part
of an extremely self
obsessed ex-famous actor now
fallen on hard times...
LAUGHTER
And I was a fraction hurt.
But it was a very funny script
and in a way it was therapeutic.
I have deep reservoirs of actual
narcissism and neurosis and anger
and hatred of others that
I was able to tap.
Did you base it on specific actors?
Well, as I said, a lot of it came
from me and in the way
a self-portrait but there
were actors from my past.
In the 80s I did theatre.
Remember that.
I remember that!
There were some
brilliant characters.
A wonderful old boy in the theatre
who, he was so good and the show
would start at 8pm but at 3pm
from his dressing room
you would start to hear
neemeeneemeeneemee,
maaaaaa,
maaaaaa, scrunchy mouse, loud lion!
LAUGHTER
Loud lion!
And as a result he had a wonderful
voice and he was just marvellously
smooth and seamlessly pervy.
He used to...
I was sharing a dressing room
with another young actor
and he always used to knock
on our door before the show,
pretending it was to say good luck.
But actually it was to
see us in our pants.
LAUGHTER
Different times!
Meanwhile, in Paddington 2...
LAUGHTER
APPLAUSE
Because you are Phoenix...
Buchanan.
And you are the little
bear's nemesis.
That's right, yes.
He's living a happy life
now with the Browns
wherever it is in London.
Notting Hill.
And one of his neighbours is this
used to be famous theatre actor
called Phoenix Buchanan.
And they end up wanting
the same thing in life,
they want this pop-up book
which turns out to be
a treasure map.
And it ends up with me
basically putting him
in prison trying to kill him.
It sounds very dark!
Putting him in prison...
There are dark bits.
Yeah, there are dark bits.
But it's all been very confusing
for me because Paddington Bear
is voiced by Ben Whishaw,
who I'm also working
with at the moment in a thing
about Jeremy Thorpe,
he's playing Norman Scott, my lover.
So I've spent all year
trying to either kill,
imprison or bugger Ben Whishaw!
LAUGHTER
Don't get them mixed up.
That's the thing!
It'll make the children cry!
Shall we look at a clip?
LAUGHTER
Have I done a bad job
of setting the film?
No, you haven't!
It's a sunny and lovely film!
But in all seriousness...
LAUGHTER
Because I hate my
films normally, I can't
bear to watch them.
But I will say, I can't find a flaw
in this one, it's really good.
It's so good.
It is so good.
I'm very proud of it.
Yes, you should be.
Very good!
This is a charming clip
of your character meeting the little
bear for the first time.
So, I'm going to ask
one of you to come up
here and open the fair.
Volunteers.
Anyone?
Eenie meanie minie...
Bear.
Let's have the young bear, why not?
Come, come young ursine.
Up here, my furry friend.
Very good, very good.
Now, your name is?
Paddington Brown.
Oh, well, of course
it is, you are my new
neighbour!
You live with Henry and Mary
and the great Mrs...
Now, then.
I suppose you know who I am?
Oh, yes.
You're a very famous actor.
Oh, poo.
Or used to be.
Now you do dog food commercials.
A man has to eat.
What, dog food?
Very, very funny.
APPLAUSE
I can't remember, have you done
this before in another
film, to act with...
I think children have gone to bed,
hopefully they have by now,
obviously the bear isn't there.
I'm sorry, what?
I must say, my 89-year-old father
came to the premiere the other day
and he did say to me halfway
through the film,
"Is that a real bear?"
Dad, it talks!
But it is very lifelike,
so I suppose...
But what was there?
Was there anything there?
Well, no, sometimes there's a stick,
sometimes there's a wonderful very
short actress, sometimes,
most frightening of all,
there's a bear's head on a stick.
It looks like a kind
of warning to bears.
And in this film, you know,
you kind of think, a light
children's film, but your range,
your range in this film,
the accents, the make-up.
It's a proper tour de force.
Well, yes, a lot of characters.
They've released stills
of some of them.
There you are, a homeless man.
Well...
Magwitch from Great Expectations.
Here you are as a train conductor.
Terrifying.
And then perhaps, most touching
and beautiful all, there you are.
LAUGHTER
Yeah.
Were you very involved
in creating the looks?
Fairly involved.
The big surprise is,
you never know which costume
is going to get you going.
Maybe that's age as well,
something about being a nun
was slightly arousing!
You don't know.
Yeah.
I had to wear handcuffs
in the Jeremy Thorpe thing the other
day and I thought, hello!
Still, life's to be lived!
Because, Jason, the characters
you've played have been so iconic,
people like to dress up as them.
So we've got a picture
of you and Emelia as the Drogos.
That's from the thing.
The Drogos!
What, you're Mr and Mrs
Smith Drogo, aren't you?
Yes, yes!
They're a lovely family!
The Drogos, haven't
heard that before!
You know, the Drogos,
the one with the Dragons!
They're coming over
tonight, the Drogos!
I hope they don't bring
that bloody dragon!
So that is, that's actual Game
of Thrones with professional make up
and costumes and everything.
So bear in mind, that's real thing.
This is just a couple at home
who have tried to recreate this.
Pretty amazing.
LAUGHTER
Is it like
looking in a mirror?
The attention to detail's
marvellous, isn't it?
I particularly like what they've
done with the room.
Oh, dear.
Jason Mamoa's film is Justice
League, ladies and gentlemen.
CHEERING
Yes, I know.
People have been waiting
for Justice League.
It opens next Friday.
This is a DC Comics supergroup
and this is your first real
go at being Aquaman.
We have sort of seen you.
Yeah, we haven't, so, it's,
we'll see if people like it.
They're all there, there's
the Flash, Wonder Woman, Batman,
Batman, Cyborg and you,
Aquaman.
Why?
Why, Aquaman, have you all been
joined together in this way?
The world as we know
it is going to end.
No!
Yes!
I hate to break the news to you.
Me and my friends kind of save you.
We're so grateful!
In terms of the superpowers,
you're all super heroes,
you've got superpowers,
so, Aquaman, water-based,
can breathe underwater, presumably?
Yes.
But what else can he do?
He can command the ocean.
He can, you know,
I basically talk to fish!
If you wanted me to, I don't know,
make you sushi, I can do that.
If we are next to water,
but the hand out.
Is that a superhero quality?
It sounds like Jonestown for fish!
He's got super-strength and...
That's good.
Bullet-proof.
That's nice.
Why would you put bullet-proof third
after home-made sushi super quickly?
And you've got your...
Hang on, it's a...
Quindent.
Not the trident yet, we don't get
the trident until a bit later.
Next movie.
I think the quindent is back there.
Is this the real
quindent from the movie?
CHEERING
Good reaction
to a fork, well done!
Is it heavy?
No.
Can I have a...
This one's the nice light one.
See, I can do that.
Aquawoman.
I could make sushi quicker!
Can I do something with it?
Yeah, go on, but don't hurt anybody.
I do break a lot of these.
OK.
Is it still in one piece?
Still in one piece, let's see
if I can get it right.
CHEERING
We've got a clip.
Because Batman is putting
together the Justice League.
Yes, Batman and Wonder Woman.
Batman's not known for playing well
with others and obviously
the world's in peril,
Wonder Woman helps get these other
characters with superpowers
to save the world and come together
to save it.
This is Batman trying
to get you involved.
So let me get this straight.
You do it stressed like a bat,
like an actual bat?
It worked for 20 years in Gotham.
If the fight comes, we'll need you.
Don't count on it, Batman.
Why not?
Because I don't like you coming
here digging into my business
and getting into my life.
People from Atlantis tell me to do
this, now you say do that.
I want to be left alone.
The way to help these people out
here in the middle of nowhere,
so you can just leave?
I help them because no
one else does.
You want to protect them,
you need to work with me.
Strongman is strongest alone.
You ever heard that?
That's not a saying.
That's the opposite
of what the saying is.
Doesn't mean I'm wrong.
You ever hear of Superman?
He died fighting next to me.
My point exactly.
It's ancient history.
Mankind's melting the polar ice
caps, destroying the ecosystem,
they had it coming?
Hey, I don't mind
if the oceans rise.
How about if they boil?
Dress like a bat.
You're out of your
mind, Bruce Wayne.
Ooh!
Good.
That's actually Iceland.
That's Iceland.
So that's cold, that water.
Yeah, that was cold.
It doesn't that like
it but that was cold.
You do look very relaxed.
But were you wearing
a thermal thing?
Yeah, you know, because I was out
there for a while so they have
a very thin wet suit that you put
on so you don't freeze to death.
OK, that's good!
They have a crane shot,
they went out in front of me
and I was walking out,
if you have a wet suit on,
the air gets trapped in there.
Just walking out and the bubbles
start coming up and right
when he gets to the level where it's
at, these bubbles come up.
Everyone thought I'd farted.
The camera's right there
and I started giggling
because of the bubbles.
And then I opened it up to let
the air out and then
all of the cold went in!
So my reaction was
like ha ha...ooh ooh!
LAUGHTER
Many emotions.
Not to dwell on this
picture too much, but some
of these tattoos are real?
Zack had the idea, he wanted
to put my tattoo, my family crest,
he wanted to put it everywhere.
Oh, OK.
These are just, are they...?
They are like stickers,
it takes quite a bit,
it's about an hour and a half
make-up to put them on.
There's like 20 pieces they have
to put on and it takes a long
time to get them off.
It's the same in Sense
and Sensibility!
LAUGHTER
Recently you celebrated your
birthday on the set...
You've already finished
the stand-alone Aquaman movie.
Two weeks ago I just
finished Aquaman.
Wow.
That's in Australia.
Here you all are
celebrating your birthday.
So this is your family,
I mean, not all of them.
I think the ones at
the front are your family.
Yes.
My babies, that's Wolf and Lola.
Because you live on a ranch?
Yes, we have around five,
six acres in California,
and a bunch of animals.
Nice.
It's kind of nice,
because there is no service,
so we don't have a lot of TV
so I don't get to see much
but we got to see the movie lately,
which was phenomenal.
Because I've never been
able to show my kids,
they've never seen the Wizard of Oz,
so I was worried, coming into it,
showing them Justice League.
But it was amazing, my kids can't
watch anything that I'm in.
My grandmother can't watch anything.
I'm like, don't watch
that one, you're going
to want to skip that one.
Eventually I'm going to do something
you're going to be able to watch.
It was really amazing
to be able to watch.
At least they could,
if they wanted to.
They might want to, but mine don't
even want to watch me!
I begged them to.
They are sitting there
watching Dino Trucks.
I say, no!
What about one of daddy's films?
Shove in, lovely films
like the Pirates cartoon.
You can't get funnier
or nicer than that.
I shove it in the DVD
and there are tears and tantrums.
Back to Dino Trucks.
I have to say, Dino
Trucks is pretty good!
In terms of being a parent, Sarah
Millican, you decided quite early
this was not for you.
Yeah, I don't like kids, no offence!
I'm sure yours are
lovely but I'm glad
they're not here!
LAUGHTER
I was on holiday,
we went on two
holidays abroad when I was a kid,
Malta when I was four and Spain when
I was eight.
And when we were in Spain
when I was eight, my present I
got on holiday was a baby doll.
But it was like this.
It was giant.
And I remember having
an inkling then
like what childbirth
was, I knew that it
came out of a part of
the
woman and I thought no!
I knew there was no hole
on me that would ever
manage that!
LAUGHTER
And the fun
thing about the baby
doll was that it had a dummy,
you took it out and it cried
and you put it back in and the baby
stopped
crying.
Brilliant.
This one particular
night, you know people,
women often think that the day
they became a woman was the day that
their period started.
Not for me.
On this one night we lost the dummy
so the baby was constantly
crying.
And I was bitten on the
nipple by a mosquito.
And it grew an actual boob.
LAUGHTER
So I think that's
the night I became a
woman because I was eight
but I wore a bra and my
baby would not shut
the
fuck up!
APPLAUSE
Hey, everyone,
Sarah Millican has
written a book!
APPLAUSE
A really successful book, How To
Be Champion.
You were number one
in the Sunday Times bestseller list.
I know!
Which must be such a thrill.
It was ridiculous.
I don't know why it was
but I'm really pleased it
was.
Of course.
It's a memoir, it's the story
of your life, but it also
contains advice.
And some of it's funny advice
but some of it's real
advice.
I just decided, there's something
really arrogant about
writing an autobiography
because you just think,
it's really odd to say to people,
well, I'm assuming you
all want to know all about me!
And people are, not really!
So I decided, because
I'm quite practical
and I like to fix things,
if I have problems I
like to work out how
to
make them better.
And I thought, I wonder
if some of the things that
have helped me might
help other people.
And it's interesting because some
of the people who have sent me
messages who have read it and enjoy
it, which is great, have like
skipped the divorce chapter,
because they're happily married!
And I think that's adorable
but I hope they put
that book on the shelf and they take
it back out in a few years' time.
LAUGHTER
When they might need it.
You never know!
It's a keeper!
It's like a reference book really.
And I don't want to
misrepresent the book in any
way because it is a really funny
book and there's lots of really
great stories, but you also, I came
away with the impression of someone
who struggles a bit with some
of the aspects of your
success and of your fame.
Yeah, I'm quite shy generally
so people don't really understand
how you can stand in front
of an audience and be shy.
But it's because there's a gap!
I'm on the stage and
there over there and all
listening and looking at me
which is what I like.
But I don't go to parties,
that sort of thing.
But what I find is,
the kind of oddness...
Social media is a major difference,
maybe it was different
before social media in that you can
be kind of attacked on social media
or even just...
I had a man wants send me
a message just saying, I've
just watched you put your bin out.
Which is not a euphemism.
LAUGHTER
But that's
the sort of thing that
was quite scary to see, that.
That is scary.
It's not threatening but it was
still a bit like, did he see
that I didn't put all the recycling
in the recycling bin?
LAUGHTER
And when you're quite
a private person, I find
that quite jarring a little bit.
Not being able to turn it off.
Yes, absolutely, and not being able
to put your bin out just
in your pants if you want to.
Fully dressed.
Because I have to say, I think
you have been really brave in
the way that you've
taken on the press.
Because I feel with the press you'll
win battles but in the end
they may win the war.
I mean, are you worried they are
just going to crush you, just find
something to finally
finish you off with?
LAUGHTER
Yes.
I mean, look, I think they've got
every skeleton in my cupboard.
There's a lot, but I think
they've had them all now.
Woohoo!
I mean you can't take that
line really, because
our lives are lovely,
they're basically lovely.
It's when people around
you, your family, your
innocent family, your
89-year-old dad gets
woken up in the middle
of
the night and asked questions,
that's when you get angry.
But we're all right,
we're all right, we're
rich, we get lots of attention!
LAUGHTER
I think it's
also the people who
have no recourse.
We have voices and loud voices.
That's it.
It is people who live
in a street in town and
in the papers and they've
got no way...
And these are the people.
My campaign, Hacked Off,
is entirely those people.
It's people who have lost children
in road accident and then
had their privacy invaded
by national newspapers.
It's all them, and it's not
a celebrity, poor me, organisation.
APPLAUSE
Very good.
Jason, because you have this
incredibly strong look, you know.
It's the forehead!
It's everything.
The caveman forehead.
It's a look, but you do
take your acting very seriously.
You approach each role and was it
Conan you were quite method for?
Yeah, I had some stupid idea...
You idolise actors, and when I was
growing up Marlon Brando
was obviously a huge one.
My heard in Streetcar
he got punched in the nose
so he could change his face.
And I asked a buddy to punch me
in the face and I had my nose broken
and broke straight on.
And in Conan there's a gigantic bump
in there and my wife was so pissed!
I hope I don't have a friend
who would do that for me.
I'll do it if you want!
LAUGHTER
Apparently I do!
You're been in so many films,
very experienced, but in real life,
didn't you pretend to be
your own agent?
I did.
I've never been very
good with being agented,
with agents and I fire them left,
right and centre.
I fired one poor man
who was a brilliant agent just
because I saw his anus.
LAUGHTER
Not just 10% of it?
It was ridiculous.
We were at some film festival
and his shower broke down
and he wanted to borrow my bath
in my suite and I said all right.
I forgot he was in there
and I walked in and he was
on all fours washing.
Who washes like that?
I've never heard of such a thing!
Anyway, the view was awful.
I don't understand!
He was on all fours?
Yes, with his bottom towards me,
this awful, soapy...
Flag of Japan.
LAUGHTER
I had to say,
you're a great agent,
I'm really fond of you but I've
seen your anus and you've got to go.
I did then invent an agent
for three or four years
called James Howe Ealy,
which saved a lot of money.
People would send me a script
and James Howe Ealy would say,
thank you so much for submitting
the script, I will get it
to Hugh as soon as possible
and get back to you.
But I got caught out in the end
because I used to do the emails
a bit drunk and I would say,
Hugh has read the script
and he really enjoys it
and he'd like to meet up.
"Best wishes, Hugh."
LAUGHTER
And then they rang one
time and I was sort of,
I haven't got a voice for James Howe
Ealy!
And for some reason I panicked
and I went with genteel
Edinburgh old lady.
It was pretty much Janet
from Doctor Finlay.
IN SCOTTISH ACCENT.
Well, hello now.
Shall we have a wee cup of tea then?
Ludicrous and unconvincing.
On the anus front...
I was recently, I woke up
the other day and I was lying
on the bed and I've got a little
dog, a little rescue
dog, adorable thing.
And he was lying on one of my boobs
which is tricky when they're
in a bra but very easy
when they're not.
And he pushed himself off
the boob and it really
hurt so I made a noise,
a noise of pain.
At the same time, unbeknownst to me,
my husband was bent over picking up
a sock off the floor,
fully naked with his anus
in much the same situation,
spread in my face.
And the noise that I made,
he thought I was making that noise
because of what I had just seen!
And the noise I made was this...
Aaah!
And I said to him,
I've been with you for 13 years,
I love you very dearly,
I would never make a noise
upon seeing any part of you.
I might do a face.
I might do a little wretch...
LAUGHTER
But it would be
entirely inaudible.
I love him too much!
Sarah Millican, very quickly,
you are also back on tour.
Control Enthusiastic.
It's 130 dates.
Yeah, it's sort of a year.
I have little gaps so I don't go mad
and I get to remind myself
what my husband looks like.
His face, hopefully
not the rest of him!
Not just his anus!
LAUGHTER
Who knew
I had an anus story?!
It it's good to know.
Jason...
LAUGHTER
It's time for our
musical guest tonight.
This artist rose to fame as
the first winner of American Idol.
Since then she's sold
over 25 million albums
and won three Grammys.
Now she's back with
a brand new album.
Here performing 'Love So Soft'
it is Kelly Clarkson!
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
# Every kiss is a door
# Can I knock on yours
# Can we knock a little more
# If a touch is a key
# Keep on twistin', keep
unlockin', keep on turnin' me
# Let me in
# I wanna be closer to you
# Let you under my skin
# If I let you in
# You gotta be careful with it
# Let me tell you again,
hey
# Love so soft
# You ain't had nothin' softer
# Break it, then you buy it and it's
sure gonna cost ya
# Love so soft
# That you can't rub off
# You gon' love it,
if you try it
# Gotcha hooked,
now you're caught up
# Love so soft, so soft
# If a thought was the truth
# We'd be doin' all the kinds
of things I know you wanna do
# But I need, need to know
# Will you protect me, respect me
if I let you close
# Let me in
# I wanna be closer to you
# Let you under my skin
# If I let you in
# You gotta be careful with it
# Let me tell you again,
hey
# Love so soft
# You ain't had nothin' softer
# Break it, then you buy it,
and it's sure gonna cost ya
# Love so soft
# That you can't rub off
# You gon' love it,
if you try it, gotcha hooked,
# Now you're caught up
# Love so soft, so soft
# If you want this love,
gotta hold it tight
# Never let it go, baby,
let it give you life
# If you want this love,
gotta hold it tight
# Never let it go baby,
let it give you life
# Love so soft
# You ain't had nothin' softer
# Break it, then you buy it,
and it's sure gonna cost ya
# Love so soft
# That you can't rub off
# You gon' love it,
if you try it, gotcha hooked,
# Now you're caught up
# Love so soft, so soft
# Love so soft, so soft #.
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
Kelly Clarkson, and her
singers and her band, oh!
So good to have you back.
Good to see you, Kelly.
Lovely to see you.
Come and meet the guests.
Jason.
Sarah.
Hugh.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you as well.
Very good.
So, now, that song...
This show, you get to drink!
Whoo!
The greatest.
The new album, it's
called Meaning Of Life.
It's out now.
There it is.
Yeah, just come out.
That song's obviously on it.
Now, this is, I was
amazed by this fact.
You win American Idol 15 years ago.
This is your first album
beyond that contract?
Yes.
That's nuts.
Insane.
I know, I know.
It was successful, though.
We had a very successful
arranged marriage.
I was in a competition,
you sign a contract.
It changes your life,
there are pros and cons.
But you've sold 25 million albums,
you've won all of those Grammys.
Doesn't that give you a bit of,
I can win a fight now?
Well it gives me, that's
not even my best work,
that's why I feel so excited
about this album.
This album is like so much
better than those.
I love those, I love singing them,
I don't have a problem,
I love all my hits that I've had.
You are keeping your good ideas back
for after the 15 years?
No!
Really restrained.
A drawer of amazing songs.
Here they are!
People will always be, like,
are you nervous about this record?
Every time I'd have a new record,
I'm like, no, because I haven't
really, I hadn't felt like I'd
done my best yet.
I haven't been able to really nail
a record how I wanted to.
Atlantic Records was
amazing to work with.
This is a proud musical
footprint for me.
Great that after 15 years
you get to feel like that,
you get to feel, right,
let's get started.
Yeah.
It is, it's cool too because I think
15 years into any career,
whatever your vocation is,
it's exciting to have
something fresh going on.
You're a very different person
than you were 15 years ago.
Oh, I don't know about you,
but I hate my 20-year-old self.
All my 20s I'm like, she's annoying!
She's annoying, she was very
egocentric, dramatic.
I'm still a bit dramatic!
I feel like, my life,
especially having children,
you know, we have four kids,
that's a lot of selflessness.
I think perspective changes.
I think the last time you were here,
Kelly brought her daughter.
River, she was young, yeah.
The happiest baby I've
ever encountered.
Yeah and now...
Miserable!
LAUGHTER
She's super happy
and all of a sudden, just super not.
It's really fun!
LAUGHTER
You didn't mean
the word fun, then!
It's like, take the wine
in a bathroom and cry it out.
I don't want to kill her!
I still love you!
She's super great, though.
Sometimes she's like this
little unicorn, she's very
magical and infectious,
in a good way.
And nearly extinct.
No, it's fictional,
it was never a thing.
Extinct!
Am I wrong?
Is it a real bear?
But isn't that the song,
Love So Soft, that she likes?
She does but she can't
say her Fs yet.
So it sounds like her
mother's an alcoholic
because she says "love so sauce".
A very drunken love
in our household.
It's fun to hear her
sing all the songs.
Well, you did very well tonight.
Thank you so much.
Congratulations on that album.
Kelly Clarkson, everybody.
APPLAUSE
That's nearly it but before we go,
just time for a visit
to the big red chair.
Who is there?
Hello!
Who are you?
I'm John.
John, lovely, where
are you from, John?
I live in London, originally
from Northern Ireland.
Northern Ireland!
Whereabouts in Northern Ireland?
Bangor, just outside Belfast.
Bangor's lovely.
A seaside resort.
Oh, yes.
But you live here now?
I do.
And what do you do here?
I try to make it easier for people
with disabilities to bank.
To what?
To bank!
LAUGHTER
My career guidance officer
never suggested that to me.
I can't wait to hear his story now.
Off you go, sir.
So I got up one morning as usual,
getting myself ready to go to work
and from getting out of bed,
the 20 feet or so to
get to the bathroom,
I was in excruciating pain around
the rectal region.
What?
His bumhole.
I get it!
I'm concerned.
I know what it is.
Doctor Clarkson's very concerned!
I think he should go
to the ER and that point.
I did go to the doctors,
got seen straightaway.
He says, can you remove your
trousers and underwear and lie down
and think happy thoughts.
So he rummaged about.
And then he asked me a question,
do you like asparagus?
And pulled out and asparagus
tip from my anus.
Bizarrely, I hadn't eaten
asparagus for months.
What?
LAUGHTER
I'm slightly offended!
Answers on a postcard.
What the hell was that about?
Comes on national television
and talks about anuses like that.
Wouldn't it be harder to get
in and get out because they're sort
of weird at the top.
Oh, my gosh!
Also, did someone break into his
house and insert some asparagus?
Because if it was cooked, surely
that wouldn't hurt you, would it?
I don't understand.
We've got questions,
you shouldn't have tipped him.
Get him out here!
One more.
OK, here we go.
Hello.
What's your name?
I'm Jane.
Jane, where are you from?
From Marlow in Buckinghamshire.
Lovely, full address!
And what do you do?
I'm retired now but I was a practice
manager at a health centre.
Oh, OK.
Medically based.
Maybe she can explain the asparagus!
No-one can explain the asparagus.
Twitter's going to go crazy.
All right, off you go
with your story, Jane.
So I'm a woman of a certain age
and I got to a menopausal state
when things were going wrong
with my body etc so I had to mention
it to a friend that I was not coping
particularly well and she said,
I've got a great gadget for you.
It's a magnet.
She gave me the magnet and said,
you put it in your pants,
it's the size of a 2 coin.
Did it vibrate?
Where are we going with this?
LAUGHTER
This sounds like a job for Aquaman!
He can breathe underwater!
Oh, my God!
Sorry.
We interrupted, you've got
a magnet in your pants.
I toddle off to work and I get
into the office and I saw these
metal filing cabinets in the office
so I thought, I wonder.
So I lurched myself forward at one
of the metal cabinets and attached
myself to the cabinet,
to the hilarity of my
office colleagues.
And then my boss came
in to try and find out
what the noise was and of course,
there I was, attached to a filing
cabinet by my pants.
That's my story.
It's a trigger finger.
You wanted to save the nice lady?
Yeah, I liked her story very much.
Did you?
I find you harsh!
Well done, everyone.
If you'd like to join us on the show
and have a go in the red chair,
you can contact us via our website
at this address.
That is it for tonight.
Please say thank you to my guests.
Jason Momoa!
APPLAUSE
Kelly Clarkson!
Sarah Millican!
And Mr Hugh Grant!
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
Next week is Children in Need,
so we'll see you the Friday
after that with pop star Kesha,
actor John Lithgow, Strictly
judge Shirley Ballas,
the hilarious Will Ferrell,
the always entertaining
Mark Wahlberg and, for the first
time, Oscar-winner Mel Gibson.
I'll see you then!
Goodnight.