This programme contains
some strong language.
Good evening everyone -
I'm Saoirse Ronan, and you're
watching The Graham Norton Show!
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
Thank you so much. Too kind. Good
evening.
Good evening.
Hello and welcome.
Everyone well?
I know why you're excited.
This week it was announced
the Spice Girls are back!
Victoria has already been
practising her singing at home.
I wonder what requests
the audience will be shouting
out at the first gig.
I'd go with "Stop Right Now,
Thank You Very Much".
But what else has been
happening this week?
Well, despite there being doubts
over her leadership,
Prime Minister Theresa May was out
and about having fun.
Here she is playing ball with a dog.
"Leave, leave" is what
everyone is telling her.
If Theresa were to quit,
some Conservatives would like to see
Jacob Rees-Mogg put his hat
in the ring.
It would look better
there than on his head.
Jacob Rees-Mogg,
the man of the people.
He wants to drag the Tory party
kicking and screaming
into the 18th century.
He doesn't have a job
in the Cabinet at the moment,
but earlier in his career
he was the Minister for Silly Walks.
Supporters claim Jacob embraces
the Churchillian spirit.
Although, it's not actually
Churchill he reminds me of.
But first - this award-winning
comedian is the new face
of Saturday night TV,
hosting All Together Now on BBC1.
Please welcome the Mouth
from the South - it's Rob Beckett!
This duo are the stars
of the ground-breaking sitcom that
became a global hit - now,
after 11 years away,
they've made a happy return
to our screens.
Please welcome Will and Grace
themselves - Eric McCormack
and Debra Messing!
APPLAUSE
It is like television has come to
life!
And she's a Golden Globe winner
and triple Oscar nominee,
who's wowed us in films
like Atonement, Brooklyn
and now the critically-
acclaimed Lady Bird.
My Irish eyes are smiling,
it's Saoirse Ronan!
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
.
The bonding and yeah. This is good.
Good fake show business helloing.
We are just pretending. We were
making out backstage. Before we do
another thing huge congratulations
on the Oscar nomination Saoirse.
This is the third one. I know. I
another one. You must be like
whatever. Yes. Good luck to the
person reading out the nomination,
Americans do struggle with your
name. They can't get it. It. Eric,
Debra did you practise? We had a a
practise, you were going to be a
joke in the opening scene on Will
and Grace. Why wasn't I? Because we
couldn't get it right. It was cut.
It was a joke about how hard it is
your programme your Netflix, she
said, what is that access we like so
much? I said Saoirse Ronan, so the
whole thing was... SER... I was
almost on Will and Grace. Then I got
cut! Now, when you hosted SNL you
came one a handy way to tell
Americans how to say your name I
did. Can you do it? It goes if I can
remember
remember it, it's... Simple as can
be, see Saoirse.
Am I the only one that is more
confused The whole week that was the
only thing I kept thinking about
because it is so difficult to say.
It was in my head... So that is what
I had in my head for the whole week.
Is Talking of awards,
congratulations, you won the Golden
Globe. Will and Grace has been
nominated for 29 or 30 Golden
Globes. 29. Never won once. We are
the biggest losers. No-one has lost
more than us.
We got to a point...
APPLAUSE
Thank you! You guys. We got to a
point after about season three where
the show was nominated, lost, lost,
and one, I think it was when the
show lost or Shaun lost, Max, went,
yes! And the cameras got confused
and went to us though we had lost,
we started to do it every
nomination. Every time anyone lost
we could have another drink of
champagne. They put a big thing of
chocolates on your plate. I would
wait until I lost. I would open up
the box and eat the whole thing. Or
Shaun lost, Max, went, yes! And the
cameras got confused and went to us
though we had lost, we started to do
it every nomination. Every time
anyone lost we could have another
drink of champagne. They put a big
thing of chocolates on your plate. I
would wait until I lost. I would
open up the box and eat the whole
thing. I was like "Doesn't matter
now." 29 unused acceptance speeches.
I thought like, I can't, I can't
reference Al Gore, that makes no
sense. But now, I feel you are not
taking it that seriously. I think
this is you guys at the Golden
Globes.
That is not how winners behave. That
was the last ones, we got in front
of the press. We weren't even
nominated, we were there because it
was our last season, the press
didn't care I said I'm dropping my
pants. They still didn't care. They
took that picture, look at Shaun.
No-one cares.
They are looking away, whatever. Now
Rob Beckett. You, welcome to the
world of show business, working the
red carpet at the NTAs. You didn't
bring up my award. I was comedian of
the year in bath. It meant a lot at
the time. Runner-up in bath. Are you
saying barf? I knew this was going
to happen. Bath. You know Bath. Near
Bristol? Oh, Bath! You were on the
recarpet with your new friend Geri
Horner, Spice Girl. Did you enjoy
working with red carpet with her. It
is interesting, when you are walking
on the red carpet with a Spice Girl
no-one cares about you whatsoever to
the point where the photographers go
get out of the photo Rob. They get
more money for one of her, I devalue
a photo.
They are earning less money, It is
interesting, when you are walking on
the red carpet with a Spice Girl
no-one cares about you whatsoever to
the point where the photographers go
get out of the photo Rob. They get
more money for one of her, I devalue
a photo.
They are earning less money, so
stand there and go "How much? " To
get out of the photo.
APPLAUSE
Big film tonight is Lady Bird. It is
out 23rd February and, Saoirse, this
was men to be an art house kind of
indie film, but it, defied all
expectations it is a big hit. It is
mad. It has done so well, it came
out in November, yes, it was a tiny
little film, it is Greta Gerwig who
did Mistress America, great films
but very small ones and within the
industry people really respected
her, but this has become this big
sort of commercial hit, and I don't
know, just the way young people in
particular have reacted to it it was
a tiny little film, it is Greta
Gerwig who did Mistress America,
great films but very small ones and
within the industry people really
respected her, but this has become
this big sort of commercial hit, and
I don't know, just the way young
people in particular have reacted to
it is amazing, girls going "I feel
like somebody gets me now." Oh. It
is really nice. Everyone is calling
their mam after the film because
they are feeling guilty. The movie
is doing great in America. Your mum
arrives in America and wans to see
it She wanted to go and see it and
she was proud, and it was doing
well, and I was like mam, it is
doing really well, let's go and see
it with a real audience, it will
probably be sold out, we will see if
we can get in there. So I got us
tickets to a 4.00 screening or
something like ta in LA, it was keep
your head down. There is posters
everywhere, the film is doing well,
all that sort of stuff. We go into
the cinema, there is a total of six
people in there. All on their
phones. Nobody was interested at
all. I was like keep your head down.
At the back, there was a girl
texting for the first ten minutes of
keep your head down. There is
posters everywhere, the film is
doing well, all that sort of stuff.
We go into the cinema, there is a
total of six people in there. All on
their phones. Nobody was interested
at all. I was like keep your head
down. At the back, there was a girl
texting for the first ten minutes of
the film, I was like "Get off the
phone." Then her friend turned up
late. She loved it. And I think the
other six people loved it. They are
all going that girl from the film is
in the cinema. Trying to spell it!
LAUGHTER
. Off the phone." Then her friend
turned up late. She loved it. And I
think the other six people loved it.
They are all going that girl from
the film is in the cinema. Trying to
spell it!
LAUGHTER
. "Scheme is here. We have a claim
from Lady Bird. This is a great
scene, you and your mum played by
Laurie Metcalf, she is
Oscar-nominated. Yes. She did. This
is the two of you having the
argument in a car. I want to go
where culture is, like New York, at
least New Hampshire where writers
live in the woods. You can't even
pass your driver's test. You are not
even worth state tuition. My name is
Lady Bird. It is not. You should go
to City College, and then to jail,
and back to City College and maybe
you would learn to pull yourself up
and not expect everybody to do
everything.
That is such a great film.
Thank you.
I remember you did make it into the
show because there was a scene, you
and I were driving, and you're
driving me to a place and I act like
I am common and I get the door up
and she goes easy Lady Bird. It's
there. That's the only reason I am
here. I love the reason, twice...
There is not a big budget film.
Watching it there is a sense you did
just throw yourself out of a moving
car. It is a wonder I survived. No,
we had a rig round the car, so just
do a drop and roll. It still must be
scary. It was amoving car, it was a
moving car and there was nobody
round except us and it was at the
end of the film. They could have
left me there if they wanted to. But
no, I... Your own mum you have a
great relationship with but cars are
the one place you and your mum... We
don't see eye to eye in the car. I
don't know about you guys but it
feels like pressure is just immense
when you get in the car with someone
that you really love, and we get on
so well, in our normal life, and
then we get into the car, and
something happens, and like we learn
to drive the car at the same time,
we share a car, and because of our
love of Barbara Streisand we called
her that, whenever we are driving
her round she is the co-pilot. She
has a great sense of direction but
when we get in the car she is like
you are taking the next left. I will
check the mirror, indicate, she is
like, what you doing? You turn me to
-- told me to turn left. I meant the
next left. We have got into full
blown arguments but like in the
confines of Barbra Streisand. You
park Barbara and you are fine. Yes.
Rob, you had to drive, is it your
dad? My dad was a lorry driver, then
a cab driver, so proper, you know,
loves a bit of driving. I am rubbish
at it. He is always driving. And I
passed an automatic. It couldn't get
my head round gear, I thought I'm
busy, I don't want to change gear, I
think my dad is ashamed of me I am
not a proper driver. I picked him up
from the hospital, he had a cataract
operation, he is half blind. I can't
get into this space, and it was one
of the most IMAX lating things that
has happened. He pulls me out the
car, parks it blind.
LAUGHTER
So degrading! I had never seen a
blind man Parque car, it is quite a
sight! So you are 23 now, the odd
thing for you is that because you
have grown up being on screen, you
have never had to do the awkward
teenage thing. I did, but it was on
camera. Really didn't notice it! I
think I can speak freely, we have
probably all had slightly awkward
teenage years. Eric McCormack, you
posted this picture, so it is not
like I poked into your house to find
it. How old were you in this
picture?
LAUGHTER
That was my Bay City rollers phase!
I was 15.
I was 15. Oh, my God, you look 32!
You look younger now! You have grown
into yourself. I haven't yet figured
out how to pluck the centre, there
is a good amount of hair there. Who
was the guy who played the
Incredible Hulk?! And a little David
Cassidy! I was just about to star in
my high school production of
Godspell when I did that. Such a
short fringe, so long at the back,
so precise. It is like a Farrah
Fawcett flip. Let's calm down,
because we have got a picture of
you, Debra, I think it is a
particularly American thing, some
American girls to look about 45.
LAUGHTER
You look like the headmistress! I
mean, that hair, it has got life in
it, doesn't it? That is solid. It
has got its own postcode. What was
that photo for? It was a high school
graduation photo. Did you think you
were supposed to face this way, then
suddenly it is over year?! I grew up
general Rhode Island, and I think I
knew I had to find some drama in my
life, I think I felt OK, I am here.
Perfectly lit as well. Cos that is
more than one light. Oh, yeah, they
went all out in Eased Greenwich,
Rhode Island. I feel like in
Lewisham they didn't.
LAUGHTER
That is just one light.
I understand there are a lot of
questions! I like to refer to these
as the bad years. I think... Well, I
know what that is, I am 15 years of
age, I am on an Easter I can't that
I am too old for, let's be honest.
-- Easter egg hunt. I caned them!
This feels like an anxiety dream, it
is awful, innit? I just smashed the
Easter egg hunt, it looks like
police evidence, doesn't it? The
glasses! Let's talk about the
fringe, you were talking to him
about the fringe?! We are the same
age in those photos!
age in those photos! It was
different times! Made in Hollywood!
Can we put those two next to each
other? Easter egg hunt, Easter egg
serial killer? Looks like a porn
star!
star! Ladies and gentlemen, Will &
Grace is back, yes!
APPLAUSE
There they all are, it is on Channel
5 every Friday at ten o'clock, and I
mean, it is one of those things, we
knew you had been away, but 11
years, was it really 11 years?
The method of it coming back is so
bizarre, no-one was talking about
it, go on. No, you know, I had been
campaigning for Hillary Clinton, and
we were talking about trying to help
her, and then it turned out that our
entire set had been stored
pristinely on a college campus of
our executive producer, for ten
years. Emerson college. They got a
call, we need you to move the entire
set to storage, we need to do
something is, so he realised, I have
the entire set of Will & Grace,
maybe there is something I can do
with it, and that is when he wrote
the four of us and said, would you
guys want to do a seven minute
little film on YouTube to try and
help Hillary? Within ten minutes, we
have all said yes. We came back and
did it, and we really thought it was
going to be just a one-off, we said
goodbye, how lucky, ten years later,
we got to play with each other
again. 7.5 million viewers, they
were like, wait a second! May be...
They flew the entire set across the
country, really expensive, and we
did this thing in secret, nobody
knew, except the crewmembers. Even
the people that showed up, the
invited audience of 100 people, they
were not told what they were about
to see, and when the curtain parted
and it was that set and the four of
us in costume, it was very awesome.
So it came from a pro-Hillary place,
when Trump one, did that put you off
bringing it back?! It was like, OK,
ten minutes didn't work, what if we
do a whole season?! That was rough.
Yeah. That was rough. It is still
more rough than ever, it is
embarrassing to be here from America
at the moment, but refreshing! But
the idea that Hillary had won, we
could have taken some small benefit,
if we had come back... We would just
be happy. But now it feels like we
are the visitors somehow. In terms
of restarting it, rebooting it, how
much discussion was around...
Because you ended up in that last
episode, you ended up in a very
different place to where you started
this series. Oh, yeah, we had kids,
it was 25 years in the future, and
we were like, how will we do this?
Oh, it never happened! The first
scene of the first series, the ninth
series, which just started here, we
wrote and off was a dream.
LAUGHTER
The idea of them having kids and
making the show about that, can we
just be gay?! We have got a clip,
this is from next week's episode,
the two of you discovering that you
are sharing more than an apartment.
You two didn't know about this? You
told me not to tell. I meant don't
put it on Instagram, you have been
living together, what have you been
talking about for three days! Now we
all know what we know, we know. Sure
do. I had a lovely night with you.
And, Grace, and equally lovely night
with you the night before.
LAUGHTER
APPLAUSE
And am I right, that is Megan
Mullally's husband?
It is, we have all had him! Huge
success, and then you had those
incredible celebrities, star cameos
and things. You were in scenes with
Madonna. And she didn't even know
who I was. I have heard that. She
came in late to the first
read-through, she kept her
sunglasses on, and she sat down, she
sort of talked like that, I think it
was a vaguely Sacramento accent, I'm
not sure. Sorry I am late, she
started reading the script, and she
said, listen, Jack, which one is
Jack? Sean Paul went, hi, I am Sean
Hayes, hi! Most of the scenes were
with Megan, but she came to us and
said, I'm sorry, I don't member your
name. Finally, I said, she was into
Kabbalah, and I said I am... And she
went...? That is my Kabbalah name!
How about that?! And literally, for
the rest of the week she called me
that, and that night we have a
tradition where we hug and kiss each
other right before we go on, and he
said, have a good show, Deb, and
Madonna turned on him and said, that
is not a name. And that is when he
informed her that my name was Debra,
and when the episode was over, I got
six dozen roses that said, the
Debra, thank you for a great week,
Madonna. So the same thing, on
Friday, this is the third time, my
name is so easy to remember, it is
the one at the very beginning of
every single episode of the show you
are on! So same thing, I got a giant
box of roses which a card I just
found the other day, which said, if
my husband would let you, I would
start to your name on my arm,
Madonna. So all is forgiven! Well...
Not sure! You have opened up a rift!
My thing was shit! If you have seen
a picture... Were you responsible
for getting Elton John on the show?
I mentioned my high school
production of Godspell, you know who
starred in it with me in 1979? David
furnish, we grew up together. Good
trivia! We lost touch for a number
of years, but when I ran into him,
he told me he was dating Elton John!
We were never close, with Elton, but
one day David phoned, this is before
Elton did the show, and he said, I
am in town, my wife said, come over
to the house for dinner. He said we
will be there, I think Elton John is
coming to our house for dinner. Sure
enough, they show up, both in velvet
tracksuits, and they sit down, and
I'm trying to be cooled, the four of
us have dinner, I kid is six months
old, and we have a new piano, I had
just enough wine and I said to
Elton, you know you're going to have
to christen the piano. He walked
into the next room, he sat down, he
looked up at me and said, what would
you like me to play? And this is my
moment, I am not going to say Rocket
Man, like some schmuck, but I say, I
have seen that movie too, and he
said, oh, fuck off, I don't remember
that song!
that song! So he came on, he was
himself, it was such a funny scene.
Talking of hanging out with big
musical stars, Ed Sheeran, the
Galway Girl video, did you know him
already? I didn't know him, but we
have a lot of mutual friends,
friends from Suffolk, which is where
he grew up, friends in New Zealand
and things like that, and I was out
one night with my friend in London.
And the casting agent who was
casting for the video just e-mailed
me and said, do you want to be in an
Ed Sheeran video? I was like, yeah,
all right! It was going to be on my
birthday, the 12th April, just so
you know! And yeah, I did it, it was
brilliant, and he filmed the whole
thing, he had a camera on a raid,
and we just ran around Galway for an
entire night, and because he is...
He is huge everywhere, but he is
beloved in Ireland, everyone loves
insomuch, so all of Galway just
followed us around from place to
place. The tattoo in the video, he
got that really tattooed, gril.
Yeah, that is my handwriting. I was
very nervous about it, so I
practised for about half an hour
before they tattooed it onto him.
And that is what you came up with?!
I can't change who I am! You did
better than that! That is like from
a nightclub! Did you mean to do the
bad spelling? It wasn't my idea to
do the bad spelling! I have been
saying to people that I just miss
spelt the word girl, but I didn't,
the tour manager in Dublin, we had
had a few drinks during the show, he
did two shows in Dublin, and the
tour manager was saying, you know
what would be a gas? If you miss
spelt the world girl and tattooed
something else onto him! So we got a
tattoo artist to come in at 12
o'clock at night, during a birthday
party that was being had in the
town... You can't get good ones that
time of night! The emergency ones
aren't so good! They just kick your
door in like a locksmith. But he
came in, he was terrified, this poor
fella, having to tattoo Ed Sheeran's
arm, the arm he plays the guitar
with. I have been told to spell it
wrong!
Was there a Galway grill that
benefitted from this? Probably.
Talking of working with ginger
musical icons. That is the greatest
segway... That is incredible.
Who knew that we would have two of
them. Spice Girls Geri Horn e did
you have meetings with her
beforehand, how does it work? We
were supposed to meet for a cup of
tea. It never happened because there
was a short time, so I met up with
her at the studio, she is so lovely.
Have you broken it to her that she
wasn't your favourite? She was. She
was. OK. She was my favourite. OK.
She was my favourite but I dressed
up as Baby Spice for a school
assembly because I was a blonde one.
There was a ginger kid, so I
couldn't have nicked it off him. We
had the egg hunt picture but not the
Baby Spice picture. I was saying did
we get that I was cute when I was
about eight, at 15 it went wrong.
Debra, did ginger spice do great
things for red heads all over the
world? I don't know. Did she? I
don't know. You know what, in
America, red heads on television, it
is a equated with being funny. I
Love Lucy Carol Burnett. And you. I
was a dark auburn, and when I got my
first comedy, my TV show they were
you have to make your hair redder. I
was like, why? They were like it's
funnier.
LAUGHTER
. It is more clown-like.
I am like Ron nabbed McDonald, what
are you talking about? I guess that
is the rule in America. Rob's new
show is the single competition All
Together Now. We are two weeks in.
It is going well. It is a really,
well I just think it is is a big
hearted show. It is a lovely watch.
Talk us through the premise.
Premise. Is more like a game show
with singing, instead of the classic
two or three judges there are one
hundred who have worked in the music
industry, they are all miced up,
Geri is in there, she is the leader
of them. When someone comes out they
start singing, if the judges like it
they stand up and singalong. If they
don't they stay seated. I have the
PR patter down. They stay sited! And
then, I come out and tell them what
score they got. I take the mickey
and mess about which doesn't
normally happen, it is so much fun,
it is warm hearted and silly. It is
a joy to make. It looks as if it was
fun. This is a clip... I knew it was
decent because all the camera crew
are enjoying it. I have not seen
cameramen smile for about 15 years.
This is a clip of tomorrow night's
show. It is the end of a
performance. You will see.
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
Oh yes.
Oh my God. Sorry, sorry.
I think I'll just take the stairs
next time. Lily. Lily. You stood up
for everyone so far. You know you
don't have to, you... I know, I
understand the premises of the game.
APPLAUSE
Lily, she is from Romania and lives
in the East End and sings Cockney
songs in her local pub, she is
amazing, her and Geri got on so
well. You get snippets of Geri
chatting to all these people. The
running round. Yes. I just think if
I was you I would have gone no. I
won't be doing that. Different
points of our career, Graham.
Give it a few years and I might be
be like, I'll go down the stairs.
Can I have a stairlift, is that OK?
It was pretty tiring. I have done
proper job, I used to work in the
flower market. Chatting to people
about a song on my feet isn't bad. I
actually sold you a bag of compost.
What do you mean? Colombia road
flower market. I carried it for you,
you gave me a tip. Thank God gth
Imagine that. Always tip, ladies and
gentlemen.
This could happen.
It's Graham Norton! That is the only
bag of compost I've ever bought.
I even sort of remember it.
That was my first job selling bags
of sheet in the street. In the
morning in East London. Brutal.
Anyone want a bag of sheet? Two for
a fiver? I'll carry it to your car
for 50 pence. Running up shiny
stairs, that is... It is nice. It is
weird being recognised. It is weird
in south-east London. The same look
you get where someone thinks you're
famous it is the same one as if they
want to chin you. Just like that.
APPLAUSE
Listen, it is time to meet our music
act.
This singer shot to fame
as the Bearded Woman
in The Greatest Showman,
for which the soundtrack album
has broken all records.
Here performing the
Oscar-nominated This Is Me,
it is Keala Settle.
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
# I am not a stranger to the dark
"Hide away", they say
# "Cos we don't want
your broken parts"
# I've learned to be
ashamed of all my scars
# "Run away," they say,
"No-one'll love you as you are"
# But I won't let them
break me down to dust
# I know that there's a place
for us
# For we are glorious
# When the sharpest words
want to cut me down
# I'm going to send a flood,
going to drown them out
# I am brave, I am bruised I am
who I'm meant to be, this is me
# Look out cos here I come
# And I'm marching
on to the beat I drum
# I'm not scared to be seen,
I make no apologies, this is me
# Oh-oh-oh-oh
# Oh-oh-oh, oh-oh-oh,
oh-oh-oh, oh, oh
# Another round of
bullets hits my skin
# Well, fire away cos today,
I won't let the shame sink in
# We are bursting
through the barricades
# And reaching for the sun
# We are warriors
# Yeah, that's what we've become
# Won't let them break me down
to dust
# I know that
there's a place for us
# For we are glorious
# When the sharpest words
want to break me down
want to cut me down
# Going to send a flood,
going to drown them out
# I am brave, I am bruised I am
who I'm meant to be, this is me
# Look out cos here I come
# And I'm marching
on to the beat I drum
# I'm not scared to be seen,
I make no apologies, this is me
# Oh-oh-oh-oh
# Oh-oh-oh, oh-oh-oh,
oh-oh-oh, oh, oh
# This is me
# Oh-oh-oh-oh
# And I know that
I deserve your love
# Oh-oh-oh-oh
# There's nothing I'm not worthy of
# Oh-oh-oh, oh-oh-oh,
oh-oh-oh, oh, oh
# When the sharpest words
want to cut me down
# I'm going to send a flood,
going to drown them out
# This is brave, this is bruised
# This is who I'm meant
to be, this is me
# Look out cos here I come
# And I'm marching
on to the beat I drum
# Marching on, marching, marching on
# I'm not scared to be seen
# I make no apologies,
this is me
# Oh-oh-oh-oh
# I'm going to send a flood,
going to drown them out
# Oh-oh-oh-oh,
oh-oh-oh-oh, oh-oh-oh-oh
# This is me. #
APPLAUSE
. Wow!
Amazing.
Stunning.
Come and join us. Wow! That was
incredible. Thank you so, so, much.
Come and say hello to everybody.
Lovely to meet you.
Wow! That was stunning. Which
haven't had a reaction to a
performance like that in ages? Is
that a good thing I counted, 100
standing up, you smashed it.
Seriously, fantastic, that of of
course is from the soundtrack of The
Greatest Showman. That is south now.
One of the next times you will be
performing that is at the Oscars. I
thought sorry darling you have to
hear that another time. Whateverle,
yes. How does that, I mean, when do
rehearsals start? No comment. I'll
get fired if I give you any
information. But I will tell you I
do get to sing it. Presumably
that... Does she win? I will get
fired. This is a special thing, here
you are, in this move I have, the
soundtrack is doing well, you are at
the Oscar, this was nerve meant to
happen, how to did you end up in the
film? It is Hugh Jackman's fault.
All his fault. I was hiding from the
world, in New York City for about 25
years and so, because the hustle is
the hustle when you're in a Broadway
show, you book one and try to find
another one, they were trying to
find a bearded lady for a reading
for the greatest show on earth,
which is what it was called at the
time. I said yes, I will do it, how
much, great I'll pay my rent. I
ended up doing it two more times and
the last time ended up being the
green light that Fox gave for us to
do it. You were in the room. I did
it, and it was, the first time they
had heard This is Me. It was one of
the last two songs written for the
film. They said do you want to sing
it? I said absolutely not. Find
somebody else and I will sing
soprano or Alatoa. The story goes,
the director said what will it take,
I said you buy me a bottle of
Jamieson and I'll do it. He showed
up with the little black bag, pulled
the bag down and there was my
bottle. I was like... You're cheap!
I think you need a new agent.
I had no idea of the budget. We have
a surprise. Somebody heard you were
on the show and a famous Australian
sent you this message. No! Are you
having a great time with Graham. I'm
sure you are, hi Graham. I have one
little message for you, you took
this song through four workshops,
you crushed it so well, it became an
anthem for many, many people, round
the world, you sing it so well, that
you got yourself nominated for an
Oscar, and topped the charts and I
have four words for you, it's all
your fault. No, it's not! How sweet.
Is
APPLAUSE
Oh, God. So wonderful.
How did you know what he was going
to say? I tell him that, I told you
when I first sat down it is his
fault. This is the only reason why I
was in this film, was because of
Hugh Jackman and him alone, he
continued to believe in me when I
refused to to. Refused to. Fought so
hard to not believe in myself and he
said stuff that, come on, let's go.
I should mention, in this country,
they are doing special singalong
versions, good luck singing along
with that! But this is what happens,
you go to the singalong, some people
go by themselves, I am the only
person in the world to watch and for
the ninth time, and then they go
into a sold-out theatre, and this
person has been there for the sixth
time, and by the time the music
starts, your best friends, all
dancing and singing. That song will
be butchered at karaoke for years.
They all will! 23rd of February
around the country. I'm so pleased
for you, it is fantastic, what a
great story, great performance, good
luck to you at the Oscars, Keala
Settle, everybody!
Right, that's nearly it,
but before we go,
just time for a visit to
the big red chair.
Hello! Hi, Graham. I am Debbie. I am
from Kent. What do you do there? I
am an airline cabin crew member. Can
you tell us which airline it is? No!
Maybe it reflects on the story! OK,
well, it happened 30 years ago
almost, my youngest daughter was a
baby, just a few months old, and she
was still being fed in the night, so
my ex-husband had a particular
aversion to breastmilk for some
peculiar reason. Anyway, she woke up
in the middle of the night, I got
out of the cot and took her into bed
with me, feeding her nicely, the
right side started to leak profusely
and was squirting. All over his
face, it woke him up, and he
went...! Get it off me! And I
thought, that is not a very nice
reaction. So the next day I made him
apple crumble with some very
special... Well done! Well done!
APPLAUSE
Ex-husband, he was her ex-husband,
yeah...
And then the marriage went tits up!
If you'd like to join us on the show
and have a go in the red chair,
you can contact us via
our website at this address.
That's it for tonight.
Please say thank you to my guests.
Keala Settle!
Rob Beckett!
Debra Messing!
Eric McCormack!
And Saoirse Ronan!
Join me next week with
singer-songwriter Camila Cabello,
brand-new Lara Croft
Alicia Vikander,
rising British star
Daniel Kaluuya,
and from I, Tonya
the Oscar-nominated Allison Janney
and Margot Robbie.
I'll see you then!
Good night!
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE