This programme contains
some strong language.
Good evening, I'm Will Ferrell.
And I'm Mark Wahlberg.
Welcome to the Graham Norton Show!
Hello!
It's me!
Hi!
Oh!
You're so lovely!
Thank you.
Hello!
Hello, good evening to you all.
You're all very welcome.
We have got a great
show for you tonight.
Not only have we got four -
count 'em - four Hollywood hunks
ladies and gentlemen.
They're back there, they are.
But also joining them later,
the new Strictly head judge
Shirley Ballas will be here!
I know!
Speaking and that.
Here's Shirley in action.
Look at that!
So sexy.
She's even got Bruno interested.
Strictly has got some amazing
professional dancers.
There's some - Pasha,
Aljaz, Giovanni.
God knows what they'll do
after Brexit, but anyway...
They'll be dancing with brooms!
And of course there was the usual
trip to Blackpool this year.
You can always tell
when Strictly's been to Blackpool.
There's a tell-tale sign outside
the hotel, when they've washed
off their fake tans.
Let's get some guests on!
Later we'll be meeting
Shirley Ballas and we'll have music
and chat from pop trailblazer Kesha.
Yeah!
But we start tonight with four stars
from the new hit comedy
movie Daddy's Home 2.
Our first father and son
duo - one is a double
Oscar-winning actor and director,
the other is the star of Boogie
Nights, The Departed and Ted -
please welcome Mark
Wahlberg and Mel Gibson!
That's them, that is!
Hello!
Very good to see you.
Hello.
You're just there.
That's them.
Have a seat.
And also playing father and son,
one is the Emmy-winning star
of The Crown and 3rd Rock
from the Sun, the other
is the comedy genius behind
Anchorman, Elf and Stepbrothers.
Please welcome John Lithgow
and Will Ferrell!
So sprightly.
Hello, I haven't seen you in ages.
Yeah!
Woo!
Wooooo!
We could just do
that all night long.
Some weeks, wouldn't it just be
lovely for 45 minutes, just whoop?
Wooooo!
Hello, welcome, all.
You are touring the world,
promoting this movie.
Is it fun, because it is
the father-son, father-son,
is it a bit like a family holiday?
Is it kind of stressful?
I wouldn't call it a holiday.
But these guys are great fun,
travelling as press companions.
But making the movie is easy
and promoting it is hard.
There's no doubt about it.
Don't say that, John!
Don't let light in on the magic.
We've saved you for last.
Don't think we've had any stress,
really, the four of us, right?
Why are you asking me?
I'm asking the group as a whole.
What did I do?
You didn't do anything.
There has been a lot of stress.
This is one of the few experiences
were everybody gets along,
it's been a lovely experience.
Usually you're shooting
a movie, people are running
right to their trailer.
You know, going off on the phone.
Everybody kind of hung
out, same thing.
We're promoting the movie, people
are happy to be around each other,
excited about the film as a whole.
So it's been nice.
Mind you, Mel Gibson,
some people watching this will be
very surprised to see you in a big
family friendly film like this.
Are you sort of surprised that
you've done that, gone back
into the heart of Hollywood?
Sure, after digging ditches for ten
years, it's been fun.
Quite frankly it's been
a lot of hard work,
personally, professionally.
And the work goes on,
as I think it does with most of us.
Was there a moment when you think,
you know what I'm going to give up
public life, I'm going to get
on with my own life?
There's a thing you've chosen,
a career and a calling.
Particularly in directing,
where you just have to get back
up there and express
yourself with storytelling.
That never went away.
All those years I was just writing,
conceiving different stories,
which I still have.
And back at the Oscars,
with Hacksaw Ridge?
Yes, that was nice.
APPLAUSE
I didn't get
the damn thing, but...
It won Oscars, it did win Oscars.
It was just bait.
It was just out of reach.
They gave it to someone else.
Ladies and gentlemen,
before we do another thing,
is there a doctor in the house?
Why, yes there is.
Dr Will Ferrell.
Woah?
I am a doctor.
Since you were last here?
Yes.
Who made you a doctor?
The University of
Southern California.
OK.
Which is my University
in Los Angeles.
I received an honorary doctorate.
They say it's honorary,
I think it's for real.
I performed 13 successful
surgeries since, and 100
that didn't go so well.
So I'm currently...
I have a lot of malpractice issues.
Yeah, yeah.
These things, you have to do
the inspirational speech.
What did you tell the young people?
I hadn't been put in
that position before.
Usually, I just make
fun of things, right?
That's easy.
But then you have to be earnest.
That was a difficult task.
So, I just told them
to keep your feet firmly planted
on the ground and reach
for the stars.
Which I read on the back
of a cereal box.
But then your speech took a very
unexpected turn, I think?
At the end?
Yes.
Yeah, I thought I would inspire
the graduating class by singing
a Whitney Houston song to them.
Which one did you choose, Will?
The theme from The Bodyguard.
I Will Always Love You?
I Will Always Love You.
That's lovely.
Yes.
You sang the whole thing?
I started thinking, do I just sing
a couple of lines or do I torture
the students and their parents
by singing the entire song?
I chose the latter.
He's not joking.
We have a little clip.
This is just a tiny clip of you.
Can I just say, you're rather good.
# And I...
# Will always love you...
APPLAUSE
That's good, that is.
That's not bad.
Did you see me look down
to try to remember the words?
Love...
You.
And John Lithgow, congratulations.
Not saying a doctorate is a joke,
but an Emmy is a proper award.
That is.
But I don't get called a doctor.
But you got the Emmy for the Crown,
for playing Churchill in The Crown.
Very good.
APPLAUSE
You were the only
American who snuck through
the net into that series.
That's right.
It was incredibly intimidating.
Everybody in England has his or her
own Churchill imitation.
They know his speeches by heart.
It is the most familiar face
and sound of the 20th century
in England, I think.
And here I was, this Yank,
coming over to play the part.
You have weird techniques
for getting the voice, didn't you?
Well, he himself had
a very weird voice.
If you really listened,
he had an extraordinary lisp that
came out of the back of his mouth.
Instead of the front.
And he had a very nasal sound,
as if his entire head was stuffed up
like a medicine ball.
And he had this strange honk,
which people don't really know.
Just every four or five
seconds he would...
HE HONKS NASALLY
To the extent his speaking voice
was really so bizarre that
if you actually duplicated it,
nobody would buy it.
So I had to figure out a hybrid.
Mel Gibson, this is an odd thing.
Obviously you're Australian.
As a young boy, you had
to learn to do the accent?
I had to, because I came
from the United States.
How old were you when
you left America?
I was 12, when I went to Australia.
You just sounded like an American?
AUSTRALIAN ACCENT:
I had to bung it on.
I used to use voice exercises,
like Barry Humphries.
You know, Dame Edna?
He wrote these songs called
Barry's Party Favourites.
He used to sing things like...
# As I walked down
the Earls Court Road,
into a pub I was lured.
# "Where do you come
from", said a nosy pom.
# As I downed the amber fluid.
# So I told him straight,
Australian, mate,
# I'm here and I'm
gonna get plastered
# Cos the beer is crook,
and all the sheilas look
# Like you, you pommy bastard!
APPLAUSE.
It goes on for verses,
but I won't bore you
with it.
And that's where your
accent came from?
It's a learned...
Yeah, had to learn it.
Talking of voices,
Will, you were saying
backstage, Mark, you do a very
good English accent?
He's a master mimic.
He just did a lovely,
fantastic version of
a high-pitched cockney woman.
At our premier.
Oh, my gosh.
50 minutes of material,
it was fantastic.
He does impressions of John Lithcow.
He does impressions of all of us.
He does impressions of everybody.
What are you talking about?
I haven't seen your
impression of me.
Dusty!
Dusty, give him the stick, Brad.
Well done.
Daydies...
Daddies?
Daydies?
Daddy's Home 2.
I should at least
get the name right.
Daddy's Home 2.
It's already, congratulations,
a huge hit stateside.
Now it's open all over
the country here.
Obviously the two of you are back
as warring dad and stepdad.
So, you've involved grandparents
this time, grandfathers.
We kind of pick up where we left
off in the first one.
Mark and I are co-parenting kids
together and everything
seems very copacetic.
Along comes beautiful
Dawn Whitaker, here.
Brad and Don were very emotional,
emotionally available to each other.
Very progressive in a way
that we talk to each other.
Sloppy, sentimental.
Wherever we greet each other
in public, we give a nice kiss.
Kiss him!
There it is, right behind you.
That could be CGI.
We did it.
I don't remember.
I want these people
to see it in the cinema.
For real.
You want them to pay.
Well, that would help.
The casting does seem perfect.
The four of you as a kind of father
and son, father and son.
We think so, sure.
I assumed the dysfunctional
purveyor of tough love.
Whereas I am just sloppy,
sentimental, brimming
over with emotion.
Is that you?
Well, it's a sort of
extreme version of me.
I'm a little bit sentimental myself.
I am, too.
You're emotional?
That's what connects us.
You're always crying.
I found myself crying
on a commercial airline flight
watching The Parent Trap.
My wife looked over to me
and said, what is going on?
I'm, like...
You know what's going to happen,
you know they're all going
to get back together.
I couldn't help it.
Tears were streaming down my face.
Snot, everything.
Apparently, you made
yourself cry on a plane?
I was watching Terms Of Endearment
for the first time in many years.
A movie that I was in.
A sort of weird
version of narcissism.
To sob at your own performance.
I'm so darn good!
Great release, right?
You're breaking my heart.
Damn you, John Lithgow.
You did it to me again.
I mean, Terms of Endearment is...
That's so upsetting.
It's a completely
no-fault tear-jerker.
It never fails.
Mark Wahlberg, I've heard you say
that as you get older
you are getting more emotional.
You do more boo-hooing?
Yes.
No, there's more.
Apparently even Disney's
got to you now?
Do tell.
Didn't you cry watching
a film with your kids?
Or maybe you weren't
watching with your kids,
maybe you were just watching it,
I don't know.
I get very sentimental.
The biggest ads that get me now,
yes, Shrek makes me cry.
All of those films make me cry.
Well, I'm in it.
I didn't know you were in that.
Until the other day.
I was Lord Farquaad.
Very, very moving performance.
Let's just leave it at that.
We've got a clip.
This is the four of you.
Mark, your character, his parenting
is being called into question.
Did you touch the thermostat?
Did you turn it up?
Of course not.
Did somebody fiddle
with the thermostat?
Yes, it's 85 degrees.
85!?
Do you have any idea how much
even a few degrees can
impact the gas bill?
Of course I do, it's unthinkable.
Dad, what's going on here?
Why is it so hot?
Someone fiddled with the thermostat.
What!?
Who would do that?
What do you think you're doing?
It's roasting in here.
I like to sleep with my window open.
Hey, kid.
Are you allowed to touch
the thermostat at your mom's house?
Pssht, duh.
What is going on?
Adriana, she turned
off the thermostat.
Said she fiddles with the thermostat
in your place any time
she damn-well pleases.
Is that true?
Tell me that's not true.
Oh, criminy, Dusty.
You might as well give her your
wallet and your 401K
while you're at it.
Do you let the kids touch
the thermostat at your house?
What?
No!
The thermostat is a sacred covenant.
I can't believe we're
even talking about this.
This is madness!
APPLAUSE.
Do the Brits call it a thermostat?
Because in Ireland, you call it...
Immersion.
The immersion.
No, they were just messing
with your head in Ireland.
That's an immersion heater.
That does the hot water.
They were implying that
heats the entire house.
No, they said just the water.
They did?
Yeah, you weren't paying attention.
I wasn't listening.
Daddy's Home 2, was the whole
thing filmed in your
stomping ground, in Boston?
The whole thing was
filmed in Boston, yes.
Which most people think,
oh, that's so cool.
You get to be home.
I'm, like, well, I live
in LA for a reason.
It's always the person,
John, I went to school
there, I went to Harvard.
Oh, love it, yeah, great experience.
Yeah, you went to Harvard.
Come to Dorchester for a while,
you're not going to love it.
A lot of people show up unannounced,
uninvited, that sort of thing.
Even with all of you there,
was Mark by far the most famous
person in this film in Boston?
Oh, yeah.
He's a folk hero.
You hear people from across
the street yelling his name.
And they know him.
And they all want money.
Hey, Mark!
Mark!
It's me, Little Anthony!
It's so weird, Mark.
This guy, Little Anthony,
he's yelling your name.
He's like, no, I actually know him.
But they'll expect
jobs, parts in movies.
Trying to figure out other ways
to exploit the production.
Other opportunities to create.
We were shooting a movie,
The Perfect Storm, George Clooney.
I had a bunch of friends visit,
show up in Gloucester.
We were kind of standing
around between set-ups
and all the equipment
is there and everything.
They're looking at
the Panavision camera.
"Woah, what is that?"
I said, it's a camera.
They said, that looks expensive.
Said, yeah, it's expensive.
They said, we should steal that.
Like, how much is that worth?
I'm, like, $250,000.
"Oh, we're throwing
that in the trunk."
I'm, like, what are you
going to do with it?
Are you going to sell it
to the guy in the corner store
for, like, 50 bucks?
The guy's going to be walking
around, filming his kids
with a Panavision camera?
Yes, that was a very,
very real incident.
There's lots of adult
laughs in this.
But it is a movie for families.
Then there are lots of kids in it.
We hear a burgeoning romance
between the Ferrell clan
and the Wahlberg clan.
Is this true?
Well, uh, Mark's daughter...
"Uh, uh, uh" - what?
Spit it out.
My oldest son told me
Mark's daughter requested
to follow him on Instagram.
Oh, now it's following him, huh?
Or vice versa.
Yeah, uh-huh.
Don't know how it works.
What did you call my daughter?
This is starting to sound
like the Montagues and the Capulets.
You know what, I did
come to grips...
It burned white hot for one second.
I did come to grips with the fact
that it is inevitable at some point
she will have a dating life and be
involved with somebody.
And if there were
ever two parents...
That would spawn a child but I think
would be polite, kind, thoughtful,
respectful and worthy of my child's
time, it would be from Will
and his lovely wife, Viv.
They are spectacular.
So, I decided I wouldn't do
anything to the kid,
but I'll crack Will's fucking head
open as quickly as that.
He's just joking.
He - he's just joking.
That's why I'm sitting over here.
Daddy's Home 2, clearly,
the name suggests it is a sequel.
Here's the thing is this true,
Mel Gibson, that there might
be a Lethal Weapon...
Would it be 5?
5, 6, I don't know, I've lost count.
Another one, anyway.
Another one.
Is it going to happen?
I'm not sure, but I met with Danny
and Donner, the director.
We watched him in a stage play.
It was very good.
We started incubating the idea.
It may come to pass, we're not sure.
We swap ideas.
But have you got the germ
of the idea of what would bring
them back together?
Sure.
I think we'll call it
Flaccid Weapon or...
Maybe Lethal Haemorrhoids.
We have to mention Braveheart,
everybody's favourite film.
APPLAUSE
The Scottish accent
in that, how hard was that for you?
It was difficult, but I was up
there and immersed among people
who all needed subtitles.
"What did you say?"
They'd have to repeat it.
Eventually it kind of worked
its way into my lexicon.
Is it true that Sean
Connery helped you?
At dinner one night he did.
We were having...
We were at Andy Vajna's place,
and he's Hungarian.
He made goulash.
Now, imagine Sean Connery
saying that word.
He said, "I want some bread
rollsh wi' ma goulashh."
Fantastic.
I've never forgotten it.
"Goulashh"?
"Goulashh".
Makes you just want
to say it, right?
"Goulashh!"
Talking about iconic roles, ladies
and gentlemen, John Lithgow...
I did not know this until I was
reading about you earlier.
Star Wars, Yoda.
You played Yoda, but on the radio?
That's right.
I...
You didn't know this?
What is going on?
What you talk about onset?
How did we not get into this?
It's a little piece
of Lithgow trivia.
Oh, OK.
About a year after Empire Strikes
Back came out as a movie,
George Lucas produced it
as a radio series.
And he got Mark Hamill,
and Billy Dee Williams,
and Anthony Daniels.
But Frank Oz didn't want to play
Yoda merely on the radio.
I was rehearsing a play
with John Madden that time,
John Madden the film director back
then was a big-time radio director.
But he was directing me in a play.
And he shared the fact that he just
couldn't find anyone.
I said...
AS YODA: Oh, impatient is he.
LAUGHTER
He hired me on the spot.
It was the quickest job I ever got.
Ever the opportunist!
If you care to to find it,
by God, that's me as Yoda.
Oh, my God.
It makes me cry every
time I hear it.
APPLAUSE
Right, let's meet our next guest.
She is the queen of Latin
and new head judge on Strictly.
Dancing the cha cha chat
show anecdote, please
welcome to the floor,
Shirley Ballas!
She's here!
Wow!
Look at you.
Hello!
That's Will.
Much hugging, much hugging going on.
Will, John and Mel.
And Mark.
Marky Mark.
OK, lovely.
She's working the sofa.
I'm working the sofa.
Have a seat, do.
How glamorous.
We all feel a bit
underdressed now, Shirley.
Can I borrow your jacket?
LAUGHTER So now...
Shirley is basically had judge
on our Dancing With the Stars.
Do you all watch
Dancing With the Stars?
Oh yeah.
John I believe.
The rest, no, I don't.
A cursive glance.
So listen, congratulations.
Thank you.
Because it's Shirley's first year.
She's never done this before.
APPLAUSE Never, no TV.
The show is bigger than ever.
Were you worried before
you kind of get out there?
Well, I do, I get
butterflies, because I've
never done any TV before, so...
Just going from being
a dance teacher and
travelling the world teaching
competitive dancers to dance to
suddenly being the head
judge on Strictly was
a little overwhelming.
What happens?
Because, so, you know, you're
Shirley Ballas, you're a dance
teacher, you're getting on with your
life, you're pushing your
supermarket trolley,
nobody knows who you are.
And then on the Sunday
or the Monday suddenly 11 million
people have seen you.
What happens to your...
Presumably everyone
in the street knows you now?
No, because they go around
with a cellphone like this.
So I feel pretty safe
when I go on the train.
They just have their cellphone
or their earphones in.
I think maybe three,
four, five maximum people
have recognised me.
You're kidding?
No.
Aww, do bother if you see her.
LAUGHTER I'm OK.
So now your son was sort of pivotal
in you getting this job.
Yes, Mark, he's on
Dancing With the Stars.
And...
There he is, there he is, look,
one Dancing With the
Stars.
Yes, with Kim Kardashian.
How many times has he won?
He's won it twice.
And my foster son six times
and my foster daughter twice.
So ten times in all.
Holy moly!
I have ten mirror balls in my house.
APPLAUSE That's impressive,
that is impressive.
So your son is on
Dancing With the Stars.
So what, does he get
wind that Len is...
Wind?
LAUGHTER Do a lot
of dancers get wind?
He looked odd in that picture...
A lot of dancers suffer from wind.
They do.
It gets trapped.
It's all that holding it in.
The diaphragm.
So your son, does he hear
about Len stepping away?
He did.
OK.
He got wind...
Len was stepping away
and he suggested that I go for the
job.
And even though I've
done no TV or anything,
just thought it
would be a good idea.
So I did and I was fortunate
enough to get the
position, which has been amazing.
It's thrilling.
And here's an odd thing.
You were at an advantage
on the first week.
When the celebrities walked down
the stairs, apparently,
you could tell who could dance.
I can tell by the way people sit,
if they've got good posture, or if
they...
LAUGHTER If they're
using their core.
If their feet are...
Thank you, Marky Mark.
By the way, that...
I raised my son with
Marky Mark the whole time.
Lovely, thank you, darling.
Feet slightly turned
out at five to one.
Very nice there.
And good posture.
Yes, I can tell them
by the way they walk,
if they're fluid and flow.
Now you're going to
get locked in that
position.
Better relax and breathe
at some point.
Actually it's interesting
Shirley, because we have
a couch of men who have quite a lot
of dance experience.
And I know we've shown
you some clips of their
dances.
We would show them on the show
but we can't afford to.
But we showed you...
We showed you backstage
so now will, obviously
great dance work in Blades of Glory,
but in Old School, you did your own
choreography, didn't you?
Yes, a beautiful ribbon dance.
We all remember the ribbon dance.
Yes.
Look at that air, look at that lift.
Yes, I did have a little look
and I thought he did very,
very well with his ribbon.
His left arm had
a lot to be desired.
Really?
And it was a good job
your ribbon didn't have
feet, because you tripped over
a little bit in the middle, didn't
you?
You were a little bit off-balance.
Let's say lost your
core a little bit.
I did that because it's a comedy.
LAUGHTER
Now, let's look at Mark Wahlberg.
Obviously in Boogie Nights you did
do boogie, you were on the dance
floor.
Now...
This is a terrible question, but...
Was it in there all the time?
Or...
Yes.
Were you dancing around it?
No, we would have just, like,
a bird seed bag at that
point.
Pantyhose with birdseed.
You could see it
dangling around my knee
there.
Is that it?
Oh my god, I do see that.
I thought that was...
Yes.
That's why they call
it pole dancing.
Shirely, were you impressed
by his pole dancing?
What was the birdseed bit?
I missed that.
Have you seen the film, Shirley?
I've seen the film.
Remember that bit at the end?
Yes.
That's in there.
It's birdseed in a, in a tight...
OK.
LAUGHTER Because I was
going to say I really
liked the way he was able
to thrust his crutch, you know,
he had great movement,
he had beautiful with
them, very coordinated, absolutely
coordinated for a dancer.
LAUGHTER And was really,
like, rocking it
with his pelvic thrusts.
OK, so Mark's winning so far.
Mel Gibson in What Women Want.
Now, I'm no judge,
but you looked like you really
knew what you were doing.
Did you rehearse and train
for ages to do that?
Yeah, had a couple of lessons, yeah.
I mean, you were doing
tricks and things.
I mean, was that all you,
or was it a body double?
Oh no, that was me.
It took a long time.
They say it is one take,
but it was 18 times
within a single take.
Oh, OK.
Were you impressed, Shirley?
Well, your 18 times paid
off, because he had...
Had a little piece where he had
his hat on the end of
his foot and flicked it,
put it on his head,
and caressed that hat.
It was just beautiful the way
he twisted it and then threw it...
With that beautiful
hat rack, swung it
around.
Fantastic.
You were amazing.
APPLAUSE
So all great dancers on the couch,
but, but, but, on the couch
there is only one...
Denier of dance?
Only one Primo Ballerino,
and that is
John Lithgow.
I give you Primo...
Here he is with the New York Ballet.
LAUGHTER
It looks like they're moving
scenery, but that is you up there.
That's right.
But did you dance
or were you just...
Oh no, I absolutely danced.
I soloed with the
New York City Ballet.
Now, while we are talking
about dancing, we have to
talk about one of the greatest
dance movies of all time.
Footloose.
I know!
You, John, you played
the fierce Reverend...
Yes.
Who banned dancing.
I heard you tell a story,
a really sweet story, about when you
were on the set of...
Of Third Rock From the Sun.
Yes.
There was an episode
of Third Rock where the
aliens ended up performing
in a circus and there was a tall,
handsome young guy who was playing
the circus strongman.
And after rehearsing
for a couple of days he
took me aside and he said...
I have to, I was choosing
my moment to tell
you a story.
I come from a small town
in Louisiana where my dad was a
Baptist minister and he
would let the kids dance
or listen to rock and roll.
Footloose came to town,
I went to that movie,
and you were my daddy.
And the next night I took my dad
to that film without telling him
what it was about.
At this time tears were
streaming down his face.
He said, I just have to tell you,
because of your performance I was
the first one of six children that
got to go to his high school prom.
Aww.
Now I never took
Footloose that seriously.
I mean, that was always
my teenybopper film.
Yeah.
It's just, it's
the best evidence I've
ever heard that you just never know
what you're throwing out there.
That sounds such...
I love that story, it's so sweet.
APPLAUSE
Now, Shirley, you were saying
in your previous life
you were a dance teacher.
Have you knocked that
on the head now?
No, I still do that.
Oh, you will very soon.
That will become tedious
to you really quickly.
Will Ferrell, you have
a love of dance, I know.
If Shirley volunteered to show
you a couple of simple moves...
Well...
Yes, of course.
I can already tell she doesn't
believe in my ability.
I believe in your ability.
I mean, everyone got rave reviews.
You have that funny left arm.
I had the bad left arm.
You could make up for it now, right?
Yeah.
What could you show him that
would be very quick?
I could show you a Cucaracha.
OK, fine.
You're playing Hero,
the music, right?
OK, yes.
Because that's a rumba.
OK.
That's a sensual dance.
Hold on, I'll be doing
a Cucaracha or rumba?
Which is it?
The action we're going to use
is a Cucaracha, but the dance
we are going to do is the rumba.
I am totally lost.
Close your eyes and try not
to get too excited down
in the nether regions.
OK.
How about if you could just go
side, replace, close?
If you could just do that for me?
Side, replace, close.
I love that I'm the only one
that has to do this.
Me too, I love it.
Side, replace, close.
You're not supposed to say
it out loud, right?
No, no, no.
But whatever I do...
Side, replace, close.
There you go.
Oh, yes.
APPLAUSE.
That little hip going,
we'll have a bit of that.
So, no matter what I do,
you're going to do that.
My left arm is acting up.
Are we ready for the music?
Yes, we're ready for the music.
Let's play the music.
Why are you looking at me?
Are you ready?
I'll start you.
Can you keep that rhythm?
Probably not...
Doesn't matter what I do.
I just keep doing that?
Beautiful.
Oh, my God, they're
doing this so well.
The Cucaracha!
Beautiful.
Come and sit down.
Never too early for
a 10 from Shirley.
Beautiful.
Right, it's time for music.
You rocked that shit,
bro, you killed it.
Oh my God, you were just doing it.
That's my boy!
Beautiful.
Right, it's time for music.
This award-winning hit maker is back
with a number one album, Rainbow.
Performing Learn to
Let Go, it is Kesha.
# Been a prisoner of the past
# Had a bitterness
when I looked back
# Was telling everyone it's
not that bad
# Til all my shit hit the fan
# I know I'm always
like telling everybody
# "You don't gotta be a victim
# Life ain't always fair,
but hell is living in resentment
# Choose redemption,
your happy ending's up to you"
# I think it's time to practice what
# I preach
# Exorcise the demons inside me
# Woah, gotta learn to let it go
# The past can't haunt me if
I don't let it
# Live and learn and never forget it
# Whoa, gotta learn to let it go
# Had a boogeyman under my bed
# Putting crazy
thoughts inside my head
# Always whispering,
"It's all your fault"
# He was telling me, "No,
you're not that strong"
# I know I'm always
like telling everybody,
# "You don't gotta be a victim
# Life ain't always fair,
but hell is living in resentment
# Choose redemption,
your happy ending's up to you"
# So I think it's time
to practice what I preach
# Exorcise the demons inside me
# Whoa, gotta learn to let it go
# The past can't haunt me if
I don't let it
# Live and learn and never forget it
# Whoa, gotta learn to let it go
# I'm done reliving my bad decisions
# I see now maybe there's
a reason
# Why, I, I, I, I, I,
I been through hell and back
# Yeah, honestly, it's
what made me who I am
# Holding on to wasted time
# Gotta learn to let go in life
# So I think it's time
to practice what I preach
# Exorcise the demons inside me
# Whoa, gotta learn to let it go
# The past can't haunt me if
I don't let it
# Live and learn and never forget it
# Whoa, gotta learn to let it go
# Hey-eh-eh-eh, yeah
# Learn to let go, learn to let go
# Learn to let go, learn to let go.#
Kesha everybody!
Come on over.
A hat for the couch.
Beautiful.
Hello!
How are you?
Good.
If you could just move up a bit.
Mark, Mel, John, Will...
If you all squeeze up
there's room at the end.
Now, Shirley, did you
watch Kesha walk over?
Is she a dancer?
Yes, yes she's got rhythm.
Oh God.
Excellent, very good.
Now, Kesha, that is of your
new album, Rainbow.
Yeah.
And huge congratulations,
this is out now.
First since 2014 but already it's
been number one in America, right?
Yes.
My fans were the best.
As you know.
We've had them on here before.
And they're the best.
Here, they took it to number
one and that does feel
good, I'm not going to lie.
But they did that, so...
Listen, on this album
there are collaborations with
all sorts of people.
One of our favourites,
Dolly Parton is on here.
She's the best.
We got one "woo".
Dolly Parton, now, she is connected
to you via your mum, is that right?
Yeah, I met her once
at the chiropractor when I was ten,
it's the only time I've met her.
Sure she does have back problems.
Anyway...
LAUGHTER
We didn't
actually get to be in the
same room recording the song,
but my mom wrote a song
that she recorded, like,
a billion years ago.
And we recorded it separately cos
of technology on this album.
But it's a famous song,
Old Flamea Can't Hold a
Candle to You.
Old Flames Can't Hold
a Candle to You.
Your mum wrote that?
Because your mum is credited
with lots of the songs on here.
Yeah, we write a lot of songs
together, which is kind of like
weird and twisted, because we write
songs about eating men.
Yeah.
But also love songs.
So your mum is around for the album,
is she around for the tour?
Yeah, she comes with
me most everywhere.
She flew out this morning
though, so she's not here.
Is that annoying, great?
Super fucking annoying.
You're like bye...
Can you imagine?
It sounds awful.
I mean, I love my
mother, but, yeah...
Me too.
You know.
Christmas is coming.
That'll be fine.
That was fantastic
performance, thank you for
bringing all that, that
glitter and stuff with you.
Congratulations with the album.
Thank you very much.
Right, that's nearly it,
but before we go just time for
a visit to the big red chair.
OK.
Who's in the big red chair?
OK, hello.
Hi, what's your name? I'm Tutu.
Tutu?
OK.
And where are you from, Tutu?
Originally from Ethiopia,
but I live in Reading at the moment.
Now, can anyone hear Tutu?
Yes, I can hear you.
So it's working in one direction.
Who did that?
LAUGHTER
Wow.
I just wanted to show
her how to work it.
I can't, but this is going to be
a trying red chair segment,
ladies and gentlemen.
OK, OK, let's try one more.
Hello.
Hello-hello.
What's your name?
My name's Darren.
Darren, lovely.
Where are you from, Darren?
I'm from London and a run
a gay travel company.
A gay travel company?
Yes.
You should be booking.
Yes, I, I...
I'll give you special service.
I love my gay travels.
Erm...
The gay airport and the gay plane.
LAUGHTER
What was your
name, John, was it?
Darren.
John's my boyfriend's name,
how did you know that?
Deep.
OK, Darren.
Off you go with your story.
OK, so I used to be a journalist
and my old boss was a bit lonely,
couldn't get any men in her life,
so I thought for her birthday I'd
get her a special present,
which was a vibrator.
I decided to give her the vibrator,
she put it in her handbag
and forgot that it was there.
Next morning she had
to get up for a meeting.
Where was the meeting,
Buckingham Palace?
Totally forgot she had
the vibrator in her bag.
Good story!
Gets to security and has
to go through the metal
detector and the airport
security style scanner.
Comes upon a screen showing
this huge vibrator.
She suddenly realises,
suddenly realises it's in there,
looks all sheepish, at the security
man, who sees it, says to her...
We'll just let you through,
but that's how she smuggled
a vibrator into Buckingham Palace.
Good story, you can walk.
One more?
One more, one more.
This is the last one,
this is the last one.
That was a good story.
OK.
He's just being carried away.
Who is this?
Look who's back!
Tutu two.
Hi.
So now, before you were so rudely
interrupted, you were telling
us a very conjugated
where you were from story.
No, I come from Ethiopia
originally, but I came to this
country 20 years ago.
OK.
Where do you live?
I live in Reading.
Reading, lovely.
And what do you do, Tutu?
I run my own cafe called
Tutu's Ethiopian Table.
It's called that?
OK.
So, Tutu, off you go
with your story.
20 years ago I used to work
at Thames Water with 40 people
on the team and I used to do data
entry in the computer,
people's details.
And I was stuck on what I'm doing
and I asked my colleague, I said,
who's our team leader to ask,
because I was having a problem.
So he told me, go
and ask Ginger Minge.
So at that time I don't
understand languages,
so I went straight to the person
and I said, hello, Ginger Minge!
Now I know what that means.
Yes, I'm sure you do!
You can walk, Tutu, go on!
Yeah!
Very good.
We would have missed that story.
Well done, everyone.
If you'd like to join us on the show
and have a go in the red chair,
you can contact us via our website
at this address.
That's it for tonight - please say
thank you to my guests - Kesha...
Mark Wahlberg...
Mel Gibson...
John Lithgow...
Will Ferrell...
And Shirley Ballas.
Join me next week with musical guest
Pink, actor and writer Stephen Fry,
pop star Robbie Williams,
actress Carey Mulligan and living
legend Sir Elton John.
I'll see you then!
Goodnight.