This programme contains
some strong language.
Good evening, everyone.
I'm Dwayne Johnson and you are
watching The Graham Norton Show!
CHEERING
Hello, good evening!
Oh!
Thank you very much! Thank you so
much! Hello, everybody! Great show
for you tonight.
I tell you, my sofa is hotter
than a royal wedding invite.
Still waiting.
LAUGHTER
There's been so much speculation
about who will be on the guestlist.
But unfortunately it's
private information.
If only there was someone
that could find out?
Oh, yeah.
That's Facebook boss
Mark Zuckerberg at this week's
Senate hearing in America,
looking into Facebook's
misuse of private data.
That lady to his right really seems
to be appreciating the senators'
forensic grasp of technical issues.
Control board dillied?
Fun fact - did you know Zuckerberg
is currently worth $64 billion?
I know!
Minus the $2 he spent
on that haircut.
Because he's only five foot seven,
Mark sat on a booster seat
during the questioning.
LAUGHTER
Aww, I feel a bit
bad revealing that.
Sorry, Mark, have I
breached your privacy?
In the end, Zuckerberg did apologise
for the misuse of people's data.
Well, I say he apologised,
he sent the senators this.
LAUGHTER
But back to the wedding!
Harry and Meghan have decided not
to have an official list
of political leaders attending.
Which makes sense -
cos if there's one thing Theresa May
and Jeremy Corbyn have in common,
it's that they both know
how to ruin a party.
LAUGHTER
Let's get some guests on!
Later, we'll be joined
by a true rock legend -
Roger Daltrey will be here!
CHEERING
He'll be chatting and singing
a track from his new solo album.
But first, he's starred
in The Office, Sherlock, The Hobbit,
and the megahit Black Panther.
Now he brings us the truly
terrifying Ghost Stories.
Welcome back to Martin Freeman!
Hello, sir!
CHEERING
Martin Freeman!
She's the Oscar-nominated star
of Moonlight who made her mark
as James Bond's Moneypenny.
Now she's back in action
in the monster blockbuster Rampage.
It's always a pleasure
to welcome Naomie Harris!
CHEERING
Oh, waving from a distance! Hello.
Lovely to see you.
And saving the world alongside
Naomie, this man has gone
from kicking ass in the wrestling
ring to become the biggest
action star on the planet.
What more can I say?
It's Dwayne "The Rock" Johnson!
CHEERING
Hello, guys.
I saw Martin at the end and I was
going to say, move up, but the couch
is sort of full. This is as close as
I get. Yeah, you have built it.
Dwayne Johnson, do you have your
phone on it? Yes. You could be
getting a call at any time.
Absolutely, any day, any minute,
we're going to give birth to a baby
girl, and I can't wait.
CHEERING
Yeah, we! We are giving birth. Are
we? We are. The contractions with
having our... Your rough handling it
remarkably well. You already know
it's a girl. -- you are handling it.
Yes, three girls. I try. Keep
trying. That's the fun part! Let's
try for a boy. You've chosen a name
already. Right
already. Right now, it's Tia, that's
first choice, but you never know
when a baby is born, suddenly, it's
something else.
something else. Tia, it screams for
a second name. Like Maria?
LAUGHTER
When you save Tia, I just hear
Maria. What are you going to do with
the phone? Will you just disappear?
In God! That would be so exciting,
and the two of you would be so
jealous! -- I'm gone. I'm expecting
something very important as well.
FedEx delivery. I'm getting some
shoes delivered and they are lovely.
You don't want to miss them. I don't
want to be out, I'll have to go to
the post office. Red since I last
saw you, your fantastic performance
in Moonlight.
CHEERING
Now, Moonlight at the Oscars, it is
now the stuff of legends, the end
when they read out the wrong name,
and we've talked about it on the
show before, and Warren Beatty has
been here and we asked him about it,
but you ended up on stage, you went
up... Eventually. It took a while
because I was sort of glued to my
seat in shock, and our producer
dragged me on stage. Is it a nice
way to win, to have disappointment
first and then, oh, yeah a! In a
way, because there's never been a
moment before or since at the Oscars
like that, so it's quite cool, and
everybody remembers it. On stage,
you were looking at the audience,
and this is a great picture of Matt
Damon, shell-shocked, but I don't
think anyone is quite as concerned
as Kate Hudson.
as Kate Hudson. You seem really
taken. I really was. Meryl Streep
seems less bothered. Meryl Streep is
composed. I thought I was seconds
away from getting up on stage and
kissing somebody is asked, --
somebody's arse, and I thought we
were in the middle somebody tried to
hijack something. She had already
said yes to Rampage, and I was like,
don't mess with my girl. Black
Panther, how not is that, Martin
Freeman? Yes.
CHEERING
Bigger than Titanic? I'm not sure,
but it's done very well and we are
very proud. I bet you are! Sort of
taken on this extraordinary life
beyond the movie. It feels like a
moment. It's lovely to be part of
it. I heard you talking about going
to the Premier and it wasn't like
anything you'd experienced. Sky it
was like football matches, properly
vocal, witty much every fifth line
was pretty big chair. People were
hungry for it, and it was more than
a film. I am a big believer in its
still having to be a good film
because, if it's just important, and
it's not a good film, who cares? It
has to be good, and the director was
clever. On the poster, yourself and
Andy Serkis slightly stand out.
Apparently the cast had a name for
the two of you. Because we had, we'd
performed in The Hobbit before, so
we were known as the Tolkien white
guys.
LAUGHTER
That is a good joke!
That is a good joke! Right, Glen
Johnson and Naomie Harris, bring us
the monster movie Rampage, out now,
and it is proper escapist, family
friendly son. -- Dwayne Johnson and
Naomie Harris. Gigantic monsters, us
trying to save the world without
being eaten. Who do you play? I play
a geneticist called Kate Caldwell,
responsible for creating a virus
that infects Dewayne's character's
best friend, a silverback gorilla,
and I feel guilty so I want to come
up with a cure. And you play, a
primatologist? Villa yes, a
primatologist, and I used to head up
a coaching unit, and my best friend,
as Naomie said, is a gigantic albino
gorilla called George. There he is!
At a matter of fact, he was inspired
by a real gorilla, the only albino
gorilla ever found, and passed away
in 2002, called Snowflake. You went
to Barcelona? Yes. I went to see
him. -- I went to see him. Oh, wow!
That was inspired by Stoker, you
met. You thought you'd be working
with cardboard cutouts and things.
Yeah, I did. One to seven, and then
the director would call from the
sidelines, and get number two, the
building is falling down, number
three, the alligator is coming
towards you, and that's all we had.
But the man was George. Yes, we had
an actor who played the gorilla, and
he was fantastic. Added that work
call? -- how did that work? George
is enormous. In the movie, all of
the animals on normal size before
they become infected with the
pathogen.
pathogen. It was an amazing process.
As the gorilla group in the movie,
we'd continue to put Jason on stands
where he got higher, so every moment
in the movie, we were always acting
opposite a human being. You could
look him in the eye. Yes, bearing in
mind it was on a crane. So you
couldn't actually see his eyes! Is a
clip of the two of you trying to
escape what is, essentially, a very
large dog. How do we get off this
roof?
roof? Maybe we don't have to. What?!
We do!
We do! Come on! Leave it, there's
detail on this helicopter. We're not
going to fly, we're going to crash.
-- there is no detail. OK, we just
need to get enough grip to stay on
top of the building as it falls,
like riding an avalanche. No, I
don't know! Very good. The life of
an actor, I love this, you've worked
with tough guy James Bond but also
with "The Rock". In terms of
toughness, who is tougher? Oh, my
God! You finished one film and you
are hoping to do the next.
LAUGHTER
I'm going to go with James Bond. But
this one messes with crocodiles in
his spare time! Do you? Yes! Well,
it's an alligator. I lived in
Florida -- I live in Florida, in the
Everglades, and there's an alligator
sanctuary, and about six to eight of
us pulled one out of the water and I
could get on it hold his jaw
together. When you say a
sanctuary... I feel so safe here! !
Alligator farm. Alligator pond. Very
quickly, I don't know if you guys
talked about this, but you in the
next James Bond? Yes, I don't think
she knows this. In You Only Live
Twice, my grandfather was a baddie.
He looks like you, he really does.
This is him... He was a proper
wrestler. He was. And you can see
him doing proper wrestling moves.
This next bit, I think it's pretty
clear that wall is made of paper.
LAUGHTER
. Sean Connery does something
extraordinary. That's a very light
sofa. Yes!
APPLAUSE
Was he the high chief?
His wrestling name was,
his real name, was high chief Peter
Meyerbeer, and he was a high chief
of Samoa, and the actually started
his career in England.
And he was trained
English-style, and at that
time, in the 60s, I believe,
English style wrestling was...
There was a lot of
what's called shoot
wrestling, which eventually became
an MMA, so it was a very tough style
of wrestling here in England,
and yeah, that's how he was trained.
And we got that picture of him.
Is this him as a wrestler,
because that is
his wrestling gear,
or is that him as a chief?
That is him as a pro wrestler
but wearing his high chief gear.
And is it true that in Moana,
your character was based on him?
Sure, correct.
So a lot of the details of that
character was based off of my
grandfather with the long hair
and the very big build and tattoos.
And in Polynesian culture
and Samoan culture,
to become a high chief,
you
have tattoos 360 degrees
from your knees all the way up
to your bottom of your test.
Everything.
And it's hard-core
and they do it with
that.
Yes.
Everything Everything?
Not everything.
Well...
That's what I heard.
I heard everything.
It's lifted, and then you...
Oh!
Because you've been
in that film now, do you
get children wanting you to delight
them as your character?
All the time.
Like, its constant.
Oh, will you sing a song?
Sing your song, sing your song!
And I do it and then
they cheer and then
I say OK, well, have a good day.
And they say, sing again!
Constant, constant.
He has a great voice, though.
You should sing.
CHEERING
Because it's the last day.
I can't.
I don't know...
That looks like a man who wants to.
All right, let's see.
CHEERING
You want some music?
# Listen, I could go on and on.
# I could explain every
natural phenomenon.
# The tide, the grass, the ground.
# Oh, that was Maui messing around.
# I killed the meerkat,
I buried its guts, spread
# it on a tree, now
you got coconuts.
# What's the lesson?
# What does it take away?
# Don't mess with me
when I'm on a breakaway.
# And the tapestry here on my skin
is a map of the victories
# I won.
# Look where I've been.
# I make everything happened.
# Look at that Maui
just tickety toppin'.
CHEERING
Thank you.
That so impressive.
So, Martin, you're going to be in a
scary film. Yes, it is very similar
to those olds Hammer horror films. I
would watch TV on Saturday night
with a double bill of those horror
movies. I guess it borrows a bit
from those, but all-new original
stories, based on the play by the
same director. We will talk about it
in a minute, but first year is a
taste of what to expect.
taste of what to expect. You're
telling me you actually saw that
happen? It is my understanding that
April to ago it is an evil spirit or
an angry spirit. Is that true? There
is no evidence to support that. The
guys at the hospital took a scam,
but they didn't want to show us.
They said there were distortions on
the screen or something. Right in
the middle of this Chinese thing.
Yeah, so the scan.
Yeah, so the scan. A bit chilly.
Sorry, I... Have you ever killed
anything, Mr Goodman? Certainly not.
Nothing you'll admit to it, anyway.
APPLAUSE
They are clever chaps, the
directors. Andy is brilliant in the
film as well. I really like it. It
is enjoyably scary. It is a proper
horror film. No, it is not three
hours of someone getting a hole
drilled into their skull or
something like that. It's quite a
smart film, I think. It's weird
because as a film... This is a genre
you recognise, but I didn't see it
in the theatre. Did you? Because
apparently people were really
freaked out. I know a few people who
are scared witless by the play. I
didn't. I have done the play, the
Woman In Black, and getting a live
reaction, a live, terrified reaction
from the audience is amazing because
you are so used to having it on the
TV or maybe a film, but when you can
occasionally elicit that reaction
from a lot of people in an
auditorium, like a live theatre, is
so enjoyable because people are just
terrified. Can you not think of
wanting to go somewhere in a room
and in the dark and wanting to be
terrified? It's important, I think.
It's enjoyable. It's weird, because
I don't know where the pleasure is.
You leave like, "I'm still alive!" I
know some people, friends of mine,
who could barely there to watch it
or they just look at the floor when
there are scary bits coming. And
weirdly, or unusually, your
character is very likeable. You're
normally quite a nice guy. I have
played nice guys. I suppose I play
people with empathy. But this guy is
not bad. No, he's quite obnoxious
and selfish. He's not a nice man.
There are three ghost stories and
then Andy, who I am in a scene with
there, he played somebody who's
life's workers to debunk the
supernatural. He doesn't want anyone
to believe in anything. Your
character? No. I am one of those
people who say, if you believe in
the supernatural, what the hell
happened to me, then? So I explained
the police in the supernatural
because of the terrible has happened
to me. -- explained the belief.
You're not seeing it. Do you have
down ghosts? Now he has to make a
remake wordy hands down ghosts and
kills them. This film is not for
you. No,. I don't watch any horror
films. The last one I watched was
Jolt and that was enough for me. Was
at a similar thing, did you watch it
to young? No, I was old and I was
still scared. I just can't do horror
movies. Poltergeist? Conjuring? None
of them. I refuse. I knew there was
a skier coming so I was watching you
to see if Dwayne would flinch. He
was waiting for the hunting. That
monster is so close, why doesn't he
shoot it? It's in his face now. Oh,
he's missed an opportunity there.
But some things do frighten you, or
you don't like. Roller-coaster is?
Well... I have a thing of getting
strapped in. You know with
roller-coaster 's that happy buyers
that come down and locks and things
like that and then compression on my
chest and shoulders and it just
hurts to freak me out. I'm not being
weird, but would you even fit in one
of those? Maybe that was the
problem. It's just comes out to
hear. That's probably the problem. I
guess it developed in my mid-20s
when we were down at Universal,
Florida, and it came down on me.
Maybe I was a little bit, but I felt
it press so it just coloured me and
that was that. Have you had people
or things pressing on your chest?
You were wrestling. I could push
them off. Whereas you can't. Any
irrational fears in your life?
Well, I think my fear's rational.
Choking.
I think choking is a
rational fear, isn't it?
I mean...
Maybe not.
Well, are you scared
of choking all the time?
Not all the time.
You know something?
I'm going to open up
to you because it's a bit
like therapy and I've had two
gin and tonics.
Every time I have an avocado,
every time I cut through an avocado
and I see the stone,
I envisage that stone
being lodged in my windpipe.
And every time,
I think I physically go...
I can't stand it.
Is it quite debilitating?
I just don't have much avocado.
Otherwise I'd be doing
it all the time.
No, I've got a real thing, though.
I've got real thing about choking.
What if you're in
a hotel on your own?
It could take days to find you.
Well, has it happened to you?
Yes, I've choked
to death many times.
What is this?
No wonder you're scared of it.
No, it has.
It has happened to me.
Oh, you have choked on food?
Yeah.
And it's scary.
Did somebody dislodge it?
One time they did, actually.
I did that show Never Mind
The Buzzcocks, and one time I'd
had too many crisps.
Because I'm a pig,
and I like eating crisps
as quickly as possible,
so I hoovered these crisps down,
and they weren't ready to go down.
And they got lodged
and so I had a beer in my hand,
and I was like doing that.
And people were going...
And so I had this beer and so it
all came out and thank God someone,
an actor called Andy Smart,
who I've known for years,
got behind me and did
the Heimlich manoeuvre,
and I was very, very grateful.
Because, as I understand it,
if you can still breathe or talk,
then it's in the safe pipe.
Or cough, or...
Yes.
And you're not going to die.
But it feels very scary when you've
got something lodged in your throat.
That's happened to me a few times.
Last time that happened to me
was at Andy Serkis's house.
Wait a minute, that's
happened to you a few times?
Yes.
Stop wolfing food down!
Graham, it's fucking crisps!
What do you want me to do?
I'm not going to chew that shit.
I just devour crisps.
What are crisps, like a doughnut?
Potato chips.
Oh, oh...
Yeah, yeah.
It seems unlikely, doesn't it?
Yeah.
And also they're a bit jagged.
Do you swallow them whole?
You would think not.
No, I do definitely
chew, but not enough.
I'm in such a hurry to get
that crispy flavour.
To get that cholesterol.
Oh, I can't wait for your obituary.
"He'd been warned many times."
Now, I think you were asked if you
had any irrational fears or phobias,
so put up your hands if you've got
fears and phobias. OK, I'm going
into the audience. Here we go. Keep
your hands up. I'll start appear.
Oh, there's a lady up here. Hello.
Stand up. What's your name? Carys.
And what are you scared of? Crisps.
No! Argued as saying that? Why are
you is geared of crisps? I did it
cause when I was ten and one of
those girls had a multipack and they
spilled them all over the floor and
there was this crisp dust
everywhere.
everywhere. So it was just the crisp
dust that frightens you? Dust stand
the smell. So you have never choked
on a crisp. She wouldn't have the
chance! What's your name? Ahmed. And
what is your fear? It is very
serious. I have a physical fear of
kids wearing suits. I like that!
First confirmations, they are not
for you. It must be difficult at
weddings. Yarra. Actually, my sister
is getting married in July but he
said it would be OK and she would
make sure. The children would just
be in jumpers and jeans. My question
is, if you see a kid with a sit on,
what do you feel? My kids know about
my condition, so I was walking in
the street and then my daughter told
me to look and there was a group of
people and she said, " look!" And
there was a kid with a suit and a
bow tie. I was in the
middle-of-the-road and my daughter
was laughing at me. And you know
where this comes from? Actually, I
think it be a trauma from a movie
where there was a killer dwarf.
Children are getting the blame.
Children are getting the blame. Do
stand up to. What's yours now? Sheep
and goats. Mostly chic. It is the it
is the eyes. Have you seen the eyes
of a sheep? The pupils are weird. I
can't deal with it. Does anybody
know what he's talking about. Look
it up Google. They have the eyes of
a serial killer. So a sheep in
sunglasses, fine. And when did you
discover you were afraid of sheep
and goats? I went to Wales. That
will do it.
CHEERING
Children in suits is my favourite, I
accept that.
Right, time to meet our final guest.
He's the iconic front man of one
of our greatest rock bands, The Who.
They've sold over 100 million albums
and broken records worldwide.
Please welcome, for the first time,
the great Roger Daltrey.
CHEERING
There he is! Hey! Hello, sir, nice
to see you. That is Dwayne. Have a
seat, please. There you go. Welcome,
sir, how are you? Very well. Welcome
back to the world of music with a
new album, As Long As I Have You,
and that is out on June the 1st. And
I suppose it's not quite what people
will expect from Roger Daltrey solo
albums. Well, my solo albums were
always a hobby, but I've taken this
one seriously. I've gone back to
doing the kind of music The Who used
to do before Pete Townshend started
writing the songs, and I used to be
a soul singer but, at 17, 18, 19,
you can sing the words and the
notes, but there's not much soul in
their because you haven't lived a
life. It's been great to revisit
them with the years I've got my belt
now! Have you finished your memoir?
Yeah. And that out later in the
year? October. It's called Thanks A
Lot, Mr Micklewhite. To the
publishers know that? They know now!
He was my headmaster. I looked at
the other rock biographies and I
didn't delay publishing deals and
then write a book, I just wrote a
book and gave it to publishers. And
they liked it, and I was shocked,
because I didn't want to be under
the cosh of, we want more of that,
more of that. I wanted to write a
book about what it felt like to be
in the middle of that whirlwind,
what became the biggest band in the
world in the early, mid-70s, The
Who, massive. Of course, we were
street kids from Shepherd's Bush,
from around here. To deal with what
was loaded on us at 25 years old was
so difficult, because it was an
industry that we were making up as
we went along. Not to judge the
other members of The Who, but are
usually only one who any of it? Pete
remembers a lot of it. There are big
gaps that I don't remember. I've had
five quite bad concussions, so there
are big gaps. I was the only
straight one with three addicts.
Pete was an alcoholic, later a drug
addict, John was an alcoholic and
cocaine addict, and Keith Moon was
in anything addict. Even Vim. It
must have been hard, being that guy.
Somebody had to be straight, and it
fell on me. You're a fan of 9/11,
but you like the whole look and
everything? -- you are a fan of The
Who. The model being influenced my
entire life. Are you sorry you
didn't end up in music, because it
sounds like you like it more? I like
it more than anything. I can sing
but you would want to hear my album.
-- you wouldn't want. Lots of people
love The Who but, when it comes to
stereotypical archetypal rock bands,
people smashing guitars and wrecking
hotel rooms, throwing TVs out that
is all you. That wasn't me! That was
The Who who started that. Asda
mainly Keith Moon and Pete
Townshend. -- mainly Keith Moon and
Pete Townshend. Pete Townshend was
an instigator of quite a lot of it.
It was all done in jest but now when
I think that a lot of it wasn't
really very funny. There is one
thing we can talk about, because
we've got a clip, a moment of
madness. Was it your life prime time
debut on TV? Are you talking about
the Smothers brothers? It was the
biggest show in America in its day,
1967, and they invited us on, and we
were famous at the time for breaking
up our instruments with My
Generation, and we did the rehearsal
and, on the same show, two of the
biggest stars of their time were on
in the whole of the film industry.
There was Betty Davis and Mickey
Rooney. Anyway, unbeknownst to us,
we used to have this kind of thing
where the drums went boom and smoke
came out, just a relatively tame
little thing, and Pete broke his
guitars, and it was theatrics to go
with the noise the guitar made while
it was being broken, like an animal
being slaughtered. When it came to
the take, Keith Moon and got the
pirate technician drug -- -- Keith
Moon had got the technician drunk
and gave him some dollars and he
overcharged the canon and it went
off like a hand grenade.
off like a hand grenade. People got
hurt, didn't they? Solo Keith Moon
etiquette of shrapnel. It comes out
and he's holding his arm, with a
piece of drum. Pete's hair caught
light, and if you see him, he's
doing this. Betty Davis immediately
passes out at the side of the set
and Mickey Rooney catches the Ed
Slater on, going, yea! This is, as
described, some people finishing a
song, expecting an explosion, but
it's a lot bigger. You can see the
camera work... Anyway. I get blown
out shot, by the way. Wedge anyway.
Anyway.
# It's my generation, baby
LAUGHTER
APPLAUSE
That insane! Well, let's hope that
doesn't happen tonight.
Roger, would you like to go
over to join your band?
They are ready for you over there.
CHEERING
Performing As Long As I Have You,
it is Roger Daltrey!
# Born in darkness
# But I fought my way up to the sun
# I had a lot of battles
# Some I lost and some I've won
# But let me tell you, girl
# You ain't seen nothing yet
# Ain't nothing in this world
# That I can't get
# As long as I have you
As long as I have
# Long as I have
As long as I have you
# As long as I have you
# Oh won't you give me
mountains to crumble
# And I'll turn them to sand
# Let me put this world
# In the palm of your hand
# Find some teardrops
# But I sang my way out of the blues
# Had to learn to stand up
# Even when they scared
me out of my shoes
# But let me tell you, girl
# You ain't seen nothing yet
# There's nothing in this world
# That I can't get
# As long as I have you
# Oh, won't you give me
mountains to crumble
# And I'll turn them to sand
# Let me put this world
# In the palm of your hand
# Say you love me
# And I know that
half the battle is won
# Don'tcha worry about nothing
# In your mind the best
is yet to come
# But let me tell you, girl
# You ain't seen nothing yet
# There's nothing in this world
# That I can't get
# As long as I have you
# All night, all night
# All day, all day
# But let me tell you, girl
# You ain't seen nothing yet
# There's nothing in this world
# That I can't get
# As long as I have you
# Oh, won't you give me mountains
to crumble... #
CHEERING
Oh! Roger Daltrey, everybody! Come
on back. Let's hear it for the band
as well, ladies and gentlemen! That
band are amazing! That was
fantastic, Roger. Take a seat beside
Martin. We are nearly out of here.
That was terrific, really grateful I
tell you, we are all energised now.
-- really great. Time for a quick
visit the red chair. Who is there?
What's your name? I'm Phil from
Surrey. What group that was good,
I'm Phil from Surrey. What do you
do? I work in the public service.
Tax? Police. Are you plain clothes?
I am tonight. Study his face!
I am tonight. Study his face! My mum
bought herself a circulation
boosting machine that passes
electricity through your feet to
boost blood circulation. She is 80
foot I would read to her house, she
got out of the shower, she had her
dressing gown on, she was on the
sofa and iPod, I'll not this up to
90% to make it work properly. -- and
I thought. My mum put her feet on
the machine, I turned it on, I had a
shriek from her, she fell back onto
the sofa. She kicked me in the jaw.
Her legs went ten to two.
LAUGHTER
I think that scared us all a visual.
Have I? I hope I have. One more? OK.
Oh, the glamour! Hello, what's your
name? Sakena. What do you do? I'm a
patient advocate in mental health.
In half American, or Iraqi. I grew
up in New Zealand and I used to work
in a major art gallery, and this was
at the time
at the time when The Hobbit was
being filmed because Ian McCallum
came in. I shook his hand and then
he started going to a part of the
gallery where you need a ticket, so
I said, do you have a ticket and he
said, no, I don't. I said, sorry,
you shall not pass. I quite liked
that!
Well done, everyone.
If you'd like to join us on the show
and have a go in the red chair,
you can contact us via our website
at this address.
That's it for tonight.
Please say thank you to my guests -
Roger Daltrey...
CHEERING
Martin Freeman...
Naomie Harris...
And Dwayne Johnson.
Join me next week with musical
guests Calvin Harris and Dua Lipa,
hot from the kitchen Mary Berry
and Claudia Winkleman,
actor Maxine Peake,
Episodes star Matt LeBlanc,
and Dr Strange himself,
Benedict Cumberbatch.
I'll see you then.
Goodnight.