Hi, everyone, I'm Margot Robbie.
And I'm Allison Janney.
BOTH: Welcome to
the Graham Norton show!
Hello! Hello.
Hey!
Oh,
thank you very much.
Thank you so much.
Hello, hello, hello.
And welcome to you all.
Now, I hope you all had a happy
Valentine's Day, did you?
CHEERING
Oh! I did. Thanks for asking.
Yes.
I was woken up in the morning by
my loved one, holding a red rose,
desperate to hump me.
LAUGHTER
True story. Hasn't it been chilly?
I say it's been chilly.
It's been cold, hasn't it?
Cold! Yes.
Colder than a Sex In The City
reunion.
And that's chilly!
But perfect weather
for the Winter Olympics.
Have you all been watching?
ALL: Yes.
Mm. Me neither.
Erm...
Ooh! Pyeongchang!
LAUGHTER
I didn't know there were six
Olympic rings.
Now...
there have been dangerously high
winds at this year's Olympics
and as we learnt recently,
even the lightest of winds
can cause devastation.
Yes.
Let's get some guests on!
CHEERING
Later, will have Latin pop sensation
Camila Cabello!
CHEERING
But first, he's Oscar-nominated
for his role in the critically
acclaimed Get Out,
and now he's starring in Marvel's
latest megahit Black Panther.
Please welcome Daniel Kaluuya!
Yay!
Hello, sir. You're very welcome.
Really good to see you.
Daniel Kaluuya!
This Swedish actress won an Oscar
for her role in The Danish Girl
and now she's kicking ass
as Lara Croft in the brand-new
Tomb Raider, it's Alicia Vikander!
Oh!
Hello, lovely woman. Hi.
Come in, come in, sit down,
Alicia.
She shot to fame as CJ
in The West Wing,
now she's earned her first Oscar
nomination for her standout
performance in I, Tonya, it's a
pleasure to welcome Allison Janney!
CHEERING
You're like a gift,
like an African gift!
Come in and sit down.
Also Oscar-nominated for her
starring role in I, Tonya, this
Aussie actress is about to become
one of the biggest players
in Hollywood. It's Margot Robbie!
CHEERING
Whoo!
Hi! Ah, so good to see you.
Mwah, mwah.
Come in, sit down.
Hello, everybody. I tell you,
this is a weekend and a half.
It's BAFTAs of course, this weekend.
Are you all going to the BAFTAs?
I am. Yeah. Yeah.
I'm not.
Oh, God!
That's awkward(!)
But we've got to celebrate this
sofa, because it is extraordinary.
So Margot and Allison, both BAFTA
and Oscar-nominated for I, Tonya.
SOMEONE WHOOPS
A round of applause, yes!
And Margot,
you're kind of wearing two hats,
because you produce this
movie as well.
Yes. Which is a big deal.
It's a lot of work, yeah!
And obviously, it's a skating movie.
There's a lot of ice skating in it.
So do you do... I mean, how much
of it...? I was so impressed.
All of it. All of it.
You did all of it?
I mean, you must have...
I am competing at the
Winter Olympics this season.
No, anything really impressive was
not me. Everything else was me.
But you must have done it
since you were...
No, I grew up in Australia,
there's no ice on the Gold Coast!
And Allison, there you are,
you got armfuls of Emmys
when you played CJ in the West Wing.
Yeah. Because everyone loves
the West Wing.
But this is weird, I didn't know
that people somehow got confused.
They thought that CJ was real.
They wanted so much of that show
to be real.
I mean, we would go on trips from LA
to do exteriors in Washington,
we'd go through the airport
and people would refer to
Martin Sheen as Mr President and
he was happy to, you know, do this.
He loved being called Mr President,
I think people...
CJ was such a great, such an iconic
female role on television,
this incredibly smart woman
operating, you know, at her
best in a male dominated arena
and, um, I got offers for jobs
in Washington...
Really?
..a news station and somewhere
as a political pundit,
I was like, "Are you aware that
I'm an actress and this is just...
"I play CJ on TV, but I cannot..."
You know, "I'm not going to run for
office, I can't be a pundit."
But it was extraordinary to me
and it also made me
very shy about meeting people,
because I'm so not CJ.
Of all the characters
I've ever played,
I would most like to be like CJ.
Well, good luck this weekend with
the BAFTAs. Thank you.
And the Oscars. Thank you.
Now, Alicia Vikander, there's a
sort of smug glow around Alicia,
cos she's WON an Oscar.
The others are just hopefuls
thus far. Alicia's got one.
I still don't believe it, really.
For The Danish Girl,
but have you actually been united
with the Oscar yet?
This has been a question that
has been returning, but I haven't.
I only had one night with Oscar
and then...
I had to go back to work, I left LA
and I said to my friend, "I think
it's too heavy,
"I can't carry it in hand luggage",
so her daughter...
Can I just say...
I want a bigger level
of gratitude than that.
"It's too heavy,
I'm not taking it home."
No, it's just because I've been on
the move for quite a few years...
I have a lot of shoes in my bag....
So where is it? Just at a friend's
house?
I get updates from my friend's
daughter, because she has Oscar
in her room, so sometimes I get a
little photo of what Oscar is up to.
Not a lot, I imagine.
Daniel Kaluuya,
what an amazing year you've had.
Cos this time last year, you know,
this was not going to be the year
that was coming.
This is amazing.
No, I was just chilling out.
I was chilling...
And then this film came out,
I was like,
I was doing this indie horror
and...
No, it's been life-changing. Yeah!
And a lot's happened!
So, Oscar-nominated for best actor,
but also the BAFTAs this weekend.
Come on, you've got to get something
- you're nominated for Best Actor
and Rising Star. That would be
too cruel to give you nothing.
I mean, it happened to
Craig David at the Brits.
Do you remember when Craig David...?
He was nominated for six Brits and
it didn't come home with nothing!
If he can go away with...
He had six!
This is two, innit?
That's a good attitude to have.
But David came back. He came back.
It took about 20 years,
but he came back!
So that's the plan, man.
20 years later, I'll go,
"Yo, you've got to give me
something, man."
You've had some practice now
with the big celebrity,
because of obviously
the Golden Globes... Yeah.
So who did you meet
at the Golden Globes?
Er, how long have you got, man?
Just like, so many.
Did you meet these guys
at the Golden Globes? Nah.
I met... I met her before at these
awards, Governors Awards, and she
was really cool and we just spoke
about stuff, it was really nice,
and then, erm...
Then I met... I met Oprah.
Good story!
You were really nice. She was a nice
person. It was cool. It was nice!
I couldn't believe he was English,
because his accent was
so flawless in Get Out
and I was like, "Oh, my God."
And any time I meet
anyone who's English,
I'm just immediately like,
"I love London, I miss it!
Do you live there?"
Ah! I do! So you talked about
London. We talked about London.
No, I met...
This is what happened, yes?
I met Denzel...
Ooh! I met Denzel
and Oprah at the same time.
It was like a segue, just...
I don't know, this African American
excellent segue of Black exc...
I don't know what happened.
Denzel came up to me with
an English accent, like,
"Cheers, mate" and I'm like,
"What's happening?
"How do you know who I am?"
And then he went to his wife, like,
"He thinks I don't know who he is!"
And then he goes, "Come and meet
Oprah!" And I was like...
Let's meet O!
Then I just hugged her.
I hugged her so tightly.
She felt so good, man.
LAUGHTER
It's not even a joke, she felt good.
Apparently, she smells...
She has an amazing smell. She smells
amazing, Graham. I swear...
Oprah is just premium. Premium.
Can the rest of the couch...?
You must have all met Oprah,
does she smell amazing?
I've never met Oprah, but when I do,
I'm going to hug her for sure.
I didn't smell her.
I met her at the Golden Globes,
but she was too far away.
You've got to inhale deeply.
Inhale deeply.
We're all going to be following her
around, sniffing...
Now I know why there was suddenly
such a nice smell in the room.
Yeah, she was really cool.
It was really surreal.
Now, the film about
Tonya Harding, I, Tonya.
It opens here next Friday.
Margot, you're the best person to
tell us the story in a way,
because when you read the script,
you didn't know it was a true story.
No, I didn't.
I think probably anyone born
after 1990 might not know who
any of these people are,
because I didn't and I got the whole
way through the script
thinking, "This is obviously not
REALLY based on true events,
"because it is so absurd."
And then I went on the internet
and was like,
"Oh, my God, this all happened
"in precise detail" that our writer
captured, right down to the
moments, like Allison's character
wearing a fur coat with a bird on
her shoulder
doing an interview -
like, that actually happened,
you can look it up on YouTube.
There was a lot to go off,
thankfully, for us.
And the central story is about her
and this...
Her rival, Nancy Kerrigan.
Well, that's the story the world
kind of new,
but the film explores what her life
really was like and the main
relationships in her life were with
her husband Jeff Gillooly
and with her mum, LaVona
and the other ones we focus on.
Of course, the Nancy Kerrigan
incident comes into the film
later in the film, but you really
start off and see how
she grew up and what those really
messed up relationships
were like and how it affected
the person she became.
And I guess there's
lots of footage of Tonya,
both on the ice and off the ice,
she was an ice skater.
But not so much of the mum,
so how do you go about that?
Do you care about accuracy if
you don't have to? Well, exactly.
It was kind of liberating...
I would have felt a little
intimidated
if I'd had to have met the real
woman and I was kind of freed
of that responsibility, so I looked
at all the existing footage.
There were a couple
of documentaries,
and I just watched them
over and over and over again
and listened to the incredible
stories that Tonya...
My friend Steven Rogers
who wrote it,
he interviewed both Tonya and Jeff
Gillooly,
her husband and they disagreed
on absolutely everything except
for LaVona, who she was and how
she acted and how she treated Tonya.
So I had those stories
and then I got to make her up
myself. I got to create her.
You know, you see this in the film
and kind of think that can't be
what she looked like, but then you
see the footage at the end...
Yeah, when I read the script,
I said "Steven, how the hell...?
"This wig and the fur coat and the
bird and the alcohol -
"how did you think of this,
you know, specific look?"
And he said, "Wait, let me just send
you a little documentary",
then I looked and that's what this
lady wore, that's what she chose.
Cos in this country, we do think
Deirdre Barlow. Anyone else?
I'll tell you something.
The thing...
The breathing tube,
that was my idea at the last minute,
because the bird handler said,
"You can't smoke around the bird"
and my character smoked in every
scene in this movie
and then we had to shoot this
direct address that I do
and the bird handler said no,
and Craig Gillespie, our director,
said, "Well, she has to smoke,
"she smokes in every scene",
and I asked the prop department
if they had one of those...
I thought, "Well, she must have
"emphysema if she smoked her whole
life", so they did,
they had the breathing tube
and the can of oxygen you see is on
the couch next to me
during that scene.
And then the bird became fascinated
with the breathing tube
and kept pecking at it, the entire
time I was doing the scene.
I tried to just not let it bother me
because we only had two hours to
shoot that scene and
I was not going to let that bird
stop me from telling my story.
It was... Amazing.
Listen, we've got a clip
from I, Tonya.
This is Tonya on... I think it's
her first date,
or an early date
with her husband-to-be,
but they're not alone.
Are you a gardener or a flower,
John?
It's Jeff.
In a relationship,
there's a flower and gardener.
Um...
You don't need to...
I don't know, I mean, I...
I just thought...
I'm a gardener who wants to be a
flower, how fucked am I? Mum! What?
You two fuck yet?
LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE
That was actually...
We were doing coverage of Margot
and Sebastian and I was off-camera
and sometimes, when I'm off-camera,
I like to give the people on camera
something different to get them...
a reaction,
and that was not LeVona's line,
but I was trying to shock them...
Not in the script at all.
It wasn't in the script and I just
was like, "You two f... yet?"
To get this reaction out of them,
so then Craig was like,
"We've got to turn around,
we've got to get you again."
I was like, "Oh, no."
Did you even know that we were meant
to have our first sex scene
later that night?
When you said that? No.
Oh. OK, because it was very evident
in my mind, "Oh, it's the first one,
"I hope it's not weird or anything
like that", so you saying that...
was like...
caught me so by surprise and my face
went so red
and Sebastian choked on his drink
and I was like...
It was so good, it got such a good
reaction. But this mother,
I mean, she is a monster,
but it SORT of comes from a good
place or a...
Um, well...!
Yeah. In her mind, yeah.
Brings the results. Yeah.
The ends justify the means -
in her mind,
she wants her daughter to have this
opportunity to be this incredible
skater, she knows her daughter has
undeniable talent
and she wants her to succeed
and have the things in life that
come along with the talent
that she has and in every way,
she was crossed by either the figure
skating community not embracing her,
saying she needed a fur coat and
they didn't have money to buy
a fur coat,
they didn't have money to...
So she was very frustrated
and knew that her daughter was
motivated by being shamed or
needled by saying, "You can't do it,
you suck, you're terrible."
It would motivate her to go out
and skate better, so yeah,
she's not going to win mother
of the year, but I think her...
Her heart was in the right place.
Um...
LAUGHTER
Cos Daniel, your mum's quite
into the tough love, isn't she?
She's a beast, man.
Amazing love and care,
but she don't care. She's...
It's the reason why...
I remember, there was a time...
I did my first play at the
Royal Court and then like,
it was press night, so I was like,
"Mum, this is the casting director,
"this is the woman who... The reason
I got in the room",
this, that and the other,
and she was like, "When are you
going to give him another job?"
LAUGHTER
I'm thinking, "This woman's going to
ruin my career right now."
INDISTINCT
She was just like, yeah...
The casting director was like...
"When are you going to give him
another job? He's not going uni."
"He's not going uni.
"He's ruining his life.
You have to give him a job."
"You've made him not go uni... You
have to give him another one. When?"
She was like, "Oh, there's some
stuff coming up."
She was answering, as well.
And then like, I took her to the
Get Out Premiere
and was in the car, chilling,
everyone was, "Good film, yeah..."
And then like, I was like, "Mum,
"what do you think about my
American accent?"
She was like, "Nearly there."
LAUGHTER
Oof! She's raw.
But this is the woman you're
bringing to the Oscars with you?
Yeah, I have to, man.
That could go horribly wrong,
I feel!
That's the fun bit!
I want her to meet random people.
She met Snoop Dogg the other day,
it was amazing.
She told me off all my life
for playing Snoop Dogg out loud,
and when she met him, she started
giggling. I was like, "Look at you!"
"Look at you." I took a picture.
It was amazing.
I want to meet your mum, it'd be
awesome. I'm going to come say hi.
It's so funny you're all going to be
there. We can all hang out again.
Yeah. You'll be at home watching.
Now, here's the thing - Alicia, your
mother was an actress. Yeah, she is.
Is. But she was not a pushy mother,
she was sort of the opposite.
Yeah, I think anyone who's
been in the industry knows how
tough it is, so she was more like,
"Are you really,
"like, really, really, really sure?"
You know, when I started out.
I danced for many years
and I think she had seen me
being on that route for quite
a long time, but, you know,
it's her biggest passion,
so I just saw her do what she did...
Didn't she tried to stop you
going to auditions?
Yeah, I mean, when I was...
My first audition,
I was probably six or seven
and had been in the theatre where
they had this poster up that they
were auditioning for young kids
for this musical.
I wanted to go and she was like,
"No." That was it.
Then I had to have a fit and scream
and lock myself into my room
for some time and then finally,
she agreed for me to begin
my career!
And did you get the part?
I did. Oooh!
GOOD screaming child.
Talking of difficult children,
Margot, I don't know if you
were a terrible child, but do you
know the story I'm talking about?
Like you do not win any awards
for being a good daughter.
There are many stories where
I don't win awards.
I was not a great daughter.
I am forever in my mum's debt
because I was...
such a brat and I feel
really bad about it.
Tell us the story about when you
were on your computer
and she wanted your help.
Oh, yes. Yes, OK. I...
I was on MSN, obviously, the most
important thing at the time...
God is in the details!
And we moved out, like, out in
the sticks
and often snakes would
get into the house
and you know, it wasn't a big deal,
but you'd have to chase them around
and get it out,
it was time-consuming and annoying.
My mum yelled out and said,
"Can you come help me?
"This snake's really big,
I can't get it on my own.
Can you come help me?"
and I was like,
"I'm so busy, Mum. No, I can't."
Just being a brat, and she was
like, "Oh, I just...
"Are you sure? Please?"
And I was like, "Be gone."
And, um...
And then she WAS gone, like,
for like, ten minutes,
and I was like, "Oh,
"she's been gone for ages."
Then I got up from the computer,
I could hear this, "Mm! Mm!"
And I was like, "Oh, God, what's
happening?" and I see Mum,
she's made it halfway down the
stairs and the snake,
she'd tried to pick this big
python up
with a broom and a stick,
but it had
wound its way up around her arm
and was going around her neck...
trying to choke her.
I love Australia, but I would never
be able to live there!
No, I'm painting a bad picture,
it's really not bad, but...!
Anyway, it wasn't a poisonous snake.
But they do... They do strangle you!
I felt so bad.
How did you get it off her?
You've just got to give it
something else to climb on,
so get a stick or something, it
starts weaving its way around that
and you can transfer its weight...
Good to know. That is a top tip.
Or you just grab it behind its
head... They hate that.
Well... You just don't want it
to bite you!
Was your mother OK?
Yeah, she was fine.
I felt bad
and I tried not to be such a brat.
When Mum asked for help in future,
I kind of did it. A lesson learned.
A lesson learned. Very good.
Right, let's move on to Alicia's
film tonight. Tomb Raider.
It opens Thursday, March 15,
and you are the new Lara Croft.
Obviously, not like Tonya Harding,
you're not a real person,
but people have such a clear vision
of who this woman is.
Mm-hm. You must feel a kind
of similar pressure.
Yeah, my breasts are not as pointy
as the first version.
No, I mean, yeah, she's been with us
for like, what is it? 20, 22 years.
And, I... Yeah... I actually...
I'm, like, a HUGE fan of Tomb
Raider. Great!
I am so excited to see this. I was,
you know,
we grew up with MSN... Yeah! I also
grew up in that time where there was
none of my girlfriends who played
video games and I kind of kept it...
I was kind of ashamed of doing it.
But I was at my parents'
friends' house
and their kids had a PlayStation
and I went there and remember
I walked into the room and saw
it was a female protagonist in a
video game,
and I had never seen that
and, er, yeah. I was a bit too
scared to play the whole game
when I was about ten, so I mostly
spent time doing the tricks
and her learning her moves in
the Manor,
but no, I was a big fan
when I was a kid.
Daniel, are you a big gamer?
Do you play a lot of games?
No, cos it ruins my life.
It just ruins me.
It's time consuming.
I've got things to do, man. I
just...
That's a good answer.
I kind of realise that now,
when I did it, because I did play
the games before I did the film
and I was like, "Wow, I had way too
much time when I was a child."
Listen, we've got a clip.
This is you as Lara Croft
and I believe in this clip
you've just raided a tomb.
HE GRUNTS
Ooh! Don't worry, he didn't die.
Was he OK? He's fine!
How long did you have to
train for that? So I...
Um, I did about four months
before I started to shoot
when I got into...
Your arms are, like, ripped.
Yeah, so that's the thing.
It takes four months for me.
I had never lifted a thing
with my arms. I did ballet.
Not even an Oscar.
Two hands! That's why you need two
hands.
"I can't bring that home."
So it takes about four months to...
I remember my trainer told me,
"They're really underdeveloped."
I was like, "Oh, really? OK."
But then four months later,
you know, he managed.
I told him, "I don't believe you."
But, yeah...
You have to do it, because it is
non-stop, this movie.
So then it takes three weeks
for you to lose it all.
That is the sad bit.
Three weeks to lose?
Three weeks to just go out of shape?
Yeah!
I thought I was going to stay like
this! That's not fair.
To get muscle and then to lose it.
Crazy. So unfair. That's not fair.
LAUGHTER
Terrible. And now, because you're
Swedish, how does that work?
Obviously, you're married to an
Irishman now, so...?
Are you learning Irish phrases?
Irish is actually quite close.
A lot of people think I'm Irish
because in Sweden, I guess
we have the same Rs.
Yeah.
Bit of a connection, there.
And is he learning Swedish phrases?
I wish it was...better.
Yeah. Actually, one thing he likes
is...
He came to Sweden and learned
that it's a lot of Swedish sayings
that are very commonly used and it's
one of those things,
when it's my own language,
I didn't really think about
how weird they are, but
he learned about them and was like,
"I'm just now going to use those."
It's like saying in Swedish,
"Well, now you're taking a poop
in the blue cabinet."
What?!
Yeah.
That's like a very common thing.
Or, "Yeah, you can't just expect
to walk in,
"sliding in on a shrimp sandwich."
I actually saw politicians when
I was back home in Sweden
use that in a debate. In Swedish.
I was like, yeah, that's how...
You can't come in here and
slide on a shrimp sandwich?
Yeah, because shrimp is very,
like, flashy
in a socialist country, having
a shrimp sandwich is very fancy.
So you can't just have
your privileges and walk in,
slide in here on a shrimp
sandwich.
We have an Australian one -
"We're not here to fuck spiders."
LAUGHTER
What does that MEAN?!
Let's get on with it!
It would be difficult
to try and fuck a spider...
In Australia,
you COULD find a spider to fuck!
LAUGHTER
Now, I feel bad that we're
talking about this,
because of what we're about to
show, which is so sweet.
I mean, diabetics
shouldn't watch this. Ah.
This must be your first
appearance on television?
Yeah. It's so funny, because
I've been watching your show
since I moved here and I thought,
"If I ever get on the show..."
I was like, "What is he going to
find?"
From my... Because you're
all about finding those clips.
So how old are you here?
I'm seven or eight.
It's funny, because I hadn't seen
this clip until...
There was actually somebody
working at a TV channel
I guess in Sweden during the Oscars
who had gone down
and found a VHS of this tape,
because I only have my vague memory
of this as a child and I have
never seen it until two years ago.
Well, this is amazing.
This is Alicia on...
Presumably it's Junior
Stars In Your Eyes? Mm-hm.
So this is Alicia on
Junior Stars In Their Eyes.
When she comes out of the smoke,
you won't know who she is.
APPLAUSE
Hey, how are you?
AUDIENCE: Aw!
SHE SINGS IN SWEDISH
CHEERING
APPLAUSE
She won!
You're very proud. Actually...
Little thing about the job that
I locked myself in the room,
that I begged to
go to the audition to,
that was the musical,
that was not my part,
but that was the woman playing
my mother in that musical,
so I mimed her song.
Looked up to her a lot.
But she's a famous Swedish...?
She's a very famous singer.
Swedish person. Now, Daniel's film
is the latest hit from Marvel,
Black Panther. It's out now.
And, I mean, this film is
doing such amazing business.
It's sort of beating
everything before it, isn't it?
Yeah, but I have a theory.
I have a theory.
It's that I think there's some
artist that said, "Don't pirate it."
They always said, "Don't pirate it,"
so loads of people are just
not pirating it, and they're
going to the cinema to watch it.
And also, it's an experience. Yeah.
It's something to watch with
people.
Because it's quite wild.
And, but also, without doubt,
it's the best reviewed
Marvel film of all time.
I mean, these reviews are crazy.
Yeah, it's nice. It's very nice.
Yeah! OK, so tell us about the story
and who you play in the story?
Erm, the story is about T'Challa,
who's the Black Panther,
whose dad dies in a
previous Marvel film,
and he has to take over the throne,
because the dad was
the King of Wakanda.
He's taken over the throne and
he has to be the king
with these powers and
has the responsibility,
but there's new enemies coming in.
But Wakanda is this place,
and I play W'Kabi,
who's the leader of the Border Tribe
that protects the border.
Because nobody is
allowed to be in Wakanda,
so that it keeps its
resources within Africa.
So this is a fictional African
country that keeps its resources,
so it's like one of the
richest countries in the world.
But in order to do that, it needs
to be protected and no-one knows
about it outside of Wakanda,
and we have to keep that secret.
Listen, we've got a clip.
This is you and some of the other
tribal leaders discussing a problem.
Ulysses Klaue plans to sell the
Vibranium to an American buyer
in South Korea tomorrow night.
Klaue has escaped our
pursuits for almost 30 years.
Not capturing him is perhaps
my father's greatest regret.
I wish to bring Klaue
back here to stand trial.
Wakanda does not need a warrior
right now. We need a king.
My parents were killed
when he attacked.
Not a day goes by when I do not
think about what Klaue took from us.
From me. It's too great
an opportunity to pass.
Take me with you. We'll take him
down together, side-by-side.
I need you here,
protecting the border.
Then I ask, you kill him where he
stands, or you bring him back to us.
You have my word.
I will bring him back.
CHEERING
And...
But, of course, it is
a superhero movie. Yeah.
And with superhero movies
come those costumes,
you get the superhero costumes.
So you must have been very excited
to think, "What's my costume?"
Yeah, and then I had to wear it.
I had all this armour. I looked like
an African Jedi,
so I had all this armour and stuff.
And then I had to have a blanket.
It's flippin' Blanket Man.
Like, because we
shot it in Atlanta,
and it was so hot!
It was just so hot.
But I had to act really cool,
because I'm in a superhero movie.
So we were like, "Yeah, yeah."
But, like, just sweat...
My make-up was going all over my
eyes and I was blinking like this.
It wasn't a sexy moment for me,
I tell you that.
Now, a lot of the reviews
are talking about how this film
is kind of a game changer.
I mean, was there a sense amongst
the cast and the crew that you were
doing something kind of important
when you were making this film?
Yeah, because it's an
African superhero movie!
I've never seen that in my life.
I felt that on set.
We had this waterfall scene
and it's basically Chad,
T'Challa's getting the coronation.
And then everyone
starts singing, like...
Hundreds of extras start singing
and drumming. I just got chills.
I was just like, "I've never..."
My inner child was like, "Oh,
my God, if I saw this as a kid,
"I wouldn't feel such a weirdo."
You feel weird when you grow up
because there's nothing
that looks like you on TV.
And this is, like, 90% of the
cast have an African accent,
including Andy Serkis.
It's like, everyone's like,
you know...
It's just this kind of...
When I first watched it,
my inner child was
so happy that this exists.
Yeah, I think the reaction
from people is going to be amazing.
I mean, this movie will have
such a life. Yeah, congratulations.
Thank you. Yeah, seriously.
CHEERING
Now, talking of game-changing
things, Daniel,
we must mention your last movie,
for which you are Oscar-nominated,
Get Out. AUDIENCE: Whoo!
Yes, look at you clapping!
How many times have you seen this
film? I've seen it three times.
You've seen it three times?
Two times. I love it so much.
One of my West Wing, Brad...
Bradley!
Yeah, I just saw him in the
picture. I was going to say.
I love that guy, man.
Him and Catherine Keener
are all... And Jordan Peele.
I love all... They're all amazing.
It's a great movie.
I have to say, I avoided watching
it,
because I thought it was going to be
a proper horror.
Because the poster made me think
it was like Saw or something.
But it's so funny and great
frights, it's brilliant.
But because you were
filming Black Panther,
were you aware of how big
the movie was getting?
I kind of ignore things. I kind of
pretend things are not happening.
But it came out on my birthday.
It came out on my birthday
and I was out. My girl
was there, who's in Atlanta.
And I was like, "We've
got to watch it, innit?"
And we went to the hood, in Atlanta.
Like, we wanted to go
right to the heart of it.
Because Jordan really had people,
African-American black audiences,
in mind when he wrote this.
And we were just
sitting there. I snuck in.
With my hat low, snuck in. And I was
sitting there at the back,
and then the reactions were just
crazy.
There's a bit when I'm trying to get
out of the house
and this woman goes, "Get the
girlfriend, get the girlfriend!
"Get the girlfriend, man!"
Or they'd be like, "He's stupid!"
It's funny, man. It was funny.
It was good times, man.
But, yeah, I was so...
Then I just went back to set,
so I just ignored.
I didn't know it was a thing
until I came back here.
Yeah, but I like the story.
Allison Williams, your co-star, she
gave you a bit of a complex on set.
She didn't. It was
the make-up woman. Oh?
She's cool, but... You're talking
about the kissing, innit? Yes.
Yeah, so I was...
I was doing the kissing scene.
I don't know if you guys...
No-one in England does this, yeah?
Doing a kissing scene and just
before it, they would give me...
A mint. A mint. Yeah.
I was like, "Cool. Why are you
giving me...?" I didn't know.
I had my co-actor, suddenly
before a scene like that,
they came up and gave a mint,
and I didn't know if I was going to
take it as a, like, a nice thing
to do or is it just like,
"Oh, my God, he thinks my breath is
horrendous."
Yeah! Have to have a little rinse!
I took it. I took it. I was like,
"Oh, yeah, cool."
And we did another take, she gave
me another mint. I was like...
"I fixed it!"
The first time, I fixed it.
You're giving me it again,
have I got a problem? Like, have I
got a chronic problem!
Every time she gave me it,
I was like, "What?"
Then she didn't talk to me
for the rest of the day
because I was like, "Why are you
giving me mints?" But, you know...
So, in England, we don't do that?
No. Really? It's just method.
It is what it is.
Australia? Mints, no mints?
No, it was a thing that
I discovered in America.
I was like, "Wow, everyone's
considerate about..."
I tell you what's worse
than mints is someone...
I'm not going to name
names, because...
But someone I had to kiss
insisted that before we kiss...
..either he or I had to
put Neosporin on our lips.
What's that? Really?
We're in England!
Neosporin, like... Well, it's
kind of... Is it like Vaseline?
..an ointment, an antibacterial
ointment, to heal.
It's something you put on.
People put it around their noses
when they fly, so they don't get
sick. It's like Vaseline, right?
It's not Vaseline. It's got...?
Is that Vicks? Vicks?
Oh, is it like hand sanitiser? No!
Just Google it! Look it up.
It's called Neosporin.
And you have to put it...
On the lips, so you don't
pass any germs or anything.
It was really... Everyone's
so germophobic in America.
..creepy. I guess it's an American
thing.
ALICIA: So, definitely
no tongue, then? Yes.
I didn't know that one time.
Apparently it's bad etiquette to put
your tongue in. I didn't know that.
Someone told me, yeah?
I was just doing it, because I
thought, "We're keeping it real."
Suddenly... They were like...
Someone was saying,
apparently if you fancy them,
you put your tongue in. Yeah.
That's what someone told me,
and I was like, "Oh, shit, I've been
sticking my tongue in."
I think someone told me
early on, thankfully.
"Don't stress about it, but no
tongue." And I was like,
"Oh, got it." I always say to other
people.
"It's all cool, but no tongue."
But why wouldn't someone
tell you that? Why wouldn't?
Well, someone should have told you
that before you put the tongue in.
No, but this is, like, years later.
I found this out after
a random conversation.
Someone said you're not supposed to
put your tongue in.
I was like, "What?"
My life's a lie.
Actually, I have to say,
and I think it's probably
very good advice for actors.
Because you got kissing tips
from a great, Allison?
One of the greatest. Yes.
One of the greatest,
Meryl Streep, I had to kiss
in a movie called The Hours.
And she was not happy with the way
a certain scene was being lit,
and we had to kiss and she said,
"I'm going to do you a favour.
"You're going to thank me
for it later."
Can I demonstrate on you? On me?
Yeah. Of course you can. Yes,
please. No tongues!
Do you want a mint?
Oh, yeah, I need a mint.
Or a pineapple. OK. All right,
where's the best camera angle?
There's loads of them, loads
of cameras. That one's probably...
There we are. That's our camera?
That's our camera right there.
OK, so, you know,
I have these nasal labial folds,
they call them, these here.
And they look better
when they're pulled back,
so she came in to kiss me,
and she went like this.
Hmm!
AUDIENCE YELP
I look fabulous!
I look 15.
Thank you so much. Oh!
So that's what she did for me.
And it did, she pulled
my face back and kissed me.
You can go watch the movie.
It's very funny to see that.
I'll watch it again, and now I
really want you to win the Oscar,
because I kissed you!
Right, it's time for music.
And since leaving
girl group Fifth Harmony,
this woman's solo career has
gone from strength to strength.
Here, performing one of the
most popular songs of the year,
Havana, it's Camila Cabello!
CHEERING
# Havana
Ooh na-na
# Half of my heart is in Havana
Ooh-na-na
# He took me back to East Atlanta
Na-na-na
# Oh but my heart is in Havana
# There's somethin'
'bout his manners
# He didn't walk up with that
how you doin'
# When he came in the room
# He said there's a lot
of girls I can do with
# But I can't without you
# I knew him forever in a minute
# That summer night in June
# And papa says he's got malo in him
# He got me feelin' like
# Ooh-ooh-ooh
I knew it when I met him
# I loved him when I left him
# Got me feelin' like
Ooh-ooh-ooh
# And then I had to tell him
# I had to go
Oh na-na-na-na-na
# Havana
Ooh na-na
# Half of my heart is in Havana
Ooh-na-na
# He took me back to East Atlanta
Na-na-na
# Oh but my heart is in Havana
# My heart is in Havana
# Havana
Ooh na-na
# I know I was there
when I read the signs
# Welcome to La Yuma
# I know it was him when
he hugged from behind
# He gets me every time
# He's put in work
But it's in the streets
# He said girl can you ride?
# And this is the part
that my daddy told me
# He got me feelin' like
# Ooh-ooh-ooh
I knew it when I met him
# I loved him when I left him
# Got me feelin' like
# Ooh-ooh-ooh
And then I had to tell him
# I had to go
Oh na-na-na-na-na
# Havana
Ooh na-na
# Half of my heart is in Havana
Ooh-na-na
# He took me back to East Atlanta
Na-na-na
# Oh no!
# But my heart is in Havana
My heart is in Havana
# Take me back to my Havana
Ooh na-na
# Half of my heart is in Havana
Ooh-na-na yeah
# He took me back to East Atlanta
Na-na-na
# Oh but my heart is in Havana
# My heart is in Havana
# Havana
Ooh na-na
# Oh na-na-na
Hey-ee!
Na-na-na-na
# Oh na-na-na
# Hey-ee-ee
# Havana
Ooh na-na. #
APPLAUSE
Camila Cabello! Fantastic job!
How are you? How great was that?
Thank you! Congratulations.
That was so great. Come and say
hello to everybody. Hi, everybody!
This is Daniel,
Alicia, Allison, Margot.
Thank you so much. So wonderful.
Thank you so much. That was so good.
Thank you. I love you.
Everyone loves that song.
Oh, thank you.
We were very excited on the couch.
Oh, wow! Oh, thanks, guys.
It's hard not to stare at you.
You don't need that now.
OK, got it. I'm so used to it.
Do a mic drop, a mic drop.
There you go! Was it good?
Thank you. Killed it.
So that's from the album Camila.
Whoo, thank you! You say
my name right. Is that right?
A lot of British people
tend to say it another way. OK.
Camilla, but it's not.
No, but it's Camila.
I don't know why I had that example.
So, the album's called Camila,
which is out now.
So, here's the thing, I hear that
you are a fan of British television,
which seems very unlikely.
But you come here and you like...
You love it. Why are you booing?
All right, we all have to
watch it, I understand that!
The woman likes it. Let her.
No, I really like how they do the...
Erm, like ITV2 when they do the,
ENGLISH ACCENT: "Coming up next on
ITV2!"
I love that they're very excited
about what's coming up next.
You just watch that bit? Yeah.
Not the shows, just the thing.
No, just that, and
I go to the next channel,
and I wait for it
to come around again.
Yeah, but that's my favourite thing
about British television, I think.
Well, thank you for that
ringing endorsement.
"That was The Graham Norton Show."
I loved that bit!
No! So, tell me this.
You're doing your first solo tour,
which is a big, big deal. Yeah!
AUDIENCE WHOOP
Yay!
No, I'm really excited.
Are you paying them? I know!
My mom. Do they follow you?
Yeah, I'm really excited.
It's my first time
doing a tour by myself,
and I feel like that's the
best manifestation of songs.
Where are you going on your tour?
I'm coming here in June,
which is really exciting.
You're kicking off in Glasgow,
I believe? Yeah.
In at the deep end, OK. I know!
I'm excited.
And I feel like by the
end of it... Tough crowd!
..I'll have a good
British accent, I think.
Well, your "coming up on ITV2"
is very good. It's good, right?
Yeah, that's excellent.
It wants to hear it again?
Go on, then. AUDIENCE: No, no! OK.
"Will Camila do the
ITV2 accent again?
"We'll find out,
coming up next on ITV2."
Very good. Thanks! Excellent.
Listen, thank you so much
for that great performance
and good luck with the tour.
Thank you. Camila, Camila?
Yes! I don't want to get it
wrong now, after being so good.
No, you're killing it.
Camila Cabello.
Thank you so much for having me.
Nice to meet you guys.
That is nearly it for tonight.
Before we go, we've got time for a
quick visit to the big red chair.
Who's there? Hello, sir!
What's your name? I'm Steve.
Steve, lovely, and where are you
from, Steve? From Surrey.
What do you do in Surrey? I own
a cafe. You own a cafe, lovely.
Do you want to tell us what it's
called? Ockham Bites in Cobham.
OK, see, that's
marketing right there!
We'll cut that out, but it was a
nice thing for me to do, wasn't it?
For a minute there, he thought
it was going to be on BBC One,
but it's not.
OK, off you go with your story, sir.
OK, many years ago, my father
emigrated to the south of France
with his family and
his pet parrot, Jasper.
They stayed for about five years and
then decided to come back to the UK.
My dad couldn't be bothered with
all the pet passport things,
so he smuggled Jasper back in
his car, in the boot of his car.
About five months down the line,
the parrot got very ill,
my dad had to take him to the vet
and one of the questions of the vet
had was, "Has Jasper ever
been out of the UK?"
And my dad said, "No, not at all."
Anyway, the parrot had to stay
overnight and in the morning,
my dad got a phone call
saying everything's fine,
you can come and collect Jasper.
My dad went to collect the parrot
and after he paid her everything,
the vet said, "Are you sure Jasper's
never been out of the UK?"
My dad said, "Yes, why?"
"Because I came down this
morning and he said, 'Bonjour.'"
That's not true. That's not true.
That didn't happen.
Can we squeeze in another one?
OK, squeeze in one more. Here we go.
Hello! Hi. Hi. Who are you?
I'm Laura. Laura, lovely.
And where are you from, Laura?
I'm from North Wales but I live in
London. All right, what do you do?
I'm an outreach worker.
An outreach worker, OK.
Off you go with your story.
When I was a young, I used to
sweat a lot, just under my arms.
So I used to wear panty liners
to cover it up, which I think is
a great idea. I should have gone
on Dragons Den with it. Very smart.
But as I was walking
to this bar one night,
I saw an ex across the room
who I had dumped,
and he was there with a new
girlfriend, and I walked up
to him, thinking, "I best be polite,
be the bigger person."
So I went up, was chatting away,
but I started to get really nervous,
using my arms a lot
and was flapping around.
And as I lifted my arms up
and put them back down,
the panty liners
flew out of my arms,
swung around in the middle
and landed right in front of us.
With the two of them just looking
at them, and looking at me.
And looking at them,
and I just had to walk off.
Oh, shall we let her walk?
That's a yes! You can walk!
I really wanted to be flipped.
Oh, you want to be flipped?
OK, here we go.
There you go.
Well done, everyone. If you'd
like to join us on the show
and have a go on that red chair,
you can contact us via our
website at this very address.
That, sadly, is it for tonight.
Please say thank you to
all my guests. Camila Cabello!
Daniel Kaluuya!
Alicia Vikander!
Allison Janney.
And Margot Robbie!
We are taking a short break, but
we'll be back on your TVs in April.
Do join me next week for a look
back at some of the highlights
from this series.
I'll see you then.
Goodnight, everybody. Bye-bye!