Good evening, everyone.
This is Will Smith wishing
you a very merry Christmas
and saying welcome to
The Graham Norton Show!
AUDIENCE CHEERS
Hello! Hello, hello!
Oh!
Oh, aren't you kind?
That's so sweet of you. Hello,
good evening. Welcome, everyone.
Merry Christmas!
Yay!
Oh, we are feeling
festive, aren't we?
Yes, we are. So Christmassy.
Has everyone got their
Christmas trees up?
Have you, have you?
AUDIENCE: Yes!
All right!
I'm not the police.
"Yes, we have!"
Can you believe some people
are so stupid
they ordered a tree too big to fit
through their front door?
Yeah. Number 10, there.
Theresa, really - measure, measure!
But Theresa May did put a little
decoration on top of that tree.
Yeah.
I imagine she enjoyed ramming
that branch up its arse.
Now, did you all enjoy your
office Christmas parties?
Did you?
AUDIENCE: Yes!
"I don't remember."
Now, look, I hope you
remembered the golden rule -
the golden rule,
ladies and gentlemen -
don't have sex in the office.
Don't. That's not romantic.
Wait until you're somewhere
nice and cosy
and the mood takes
you and pop upstairs.
Yeah, ding-ding!
Room for a small one?
Hey, let's get some guests on!
Later, we'll have music from
former Keane front man Tom Chaplin.
Yes, he'll be performing
his new single, Midnight Mass,
a true Christmas treat -
but first, no Christmas
is complete
without this man's
festive food and cheer.
Here to talk about his
20th cookbook,
please welcome the award-winning
chef and restaurateur Jamie Oliver!
AUDIENCE CHEERS
Hello, sir.
Lovely to see you.
Very smart, very smart.
Jamie Oliver.
She's gone from soap star
to Doctor Who companion,
and now she stars as the Queen
herself in the hit series Victoria.
Please welcome Jenna Coleman!
AUDIENCE CHEERS
Very nice.
Jamie, Jenna, Jenna, Jamie.
And he's one of the world's biggest
movie stars
and one of our favourite
guests on this show.
It's always a pleasure to welcome
the great Will Smith!
AUDIENCE CHEERS
Yeah!
Well, hey, Merry Christmas,
everybody.
Merry Christmas!
Yay! Merry Christmas!
I almost wore that same jacket.
Really?
That would have been so
embarrassing. So embarrassing.
You would have worn
it better, I think.
You look Christmassy -
and, actually, the two of you
look like you're
going to do something together,
because your tie matches your dress.
We are performing tonight.
Yeah, blending.
I look like the driver.
"Where y'all headed tonight?"
So, welcome, all.
Are we all ready for Christmas?
Mm-hm. Yes, I'm very ready.
So excited, I can't believe it.
You're lying.
Presents and food and stuff.
Yeah, all that good stuff. Yeah!
We could talk about
Christmas for hours,
but I'm distracted by the makings
of a cocktail.
Oh, yes.
AUDIENCE: Ooh!
Who likes a cocktail at Christmas,
everyone?
AUDIENCE: Yeah!
Do you like a cocktail?
I like a cocktail.
Shall I endeavour? Yes, please.
What have you brought us?
I like to give Britain
a little tip every now and again,
so you need to find yourself
a sheath, right?
Now, this is... Whoa.
Just a minute!
Hold on, hold on -
I don't know if I want that drink.
If you go to the really posh
cocktail bars,
you get these incredible ice cubes
that they hand-carve.
Oh, no, no, no!
We go get a water bomb
and we just split it
and we peel it off
and we get a lovely round...
Ooh! Bear with me.
This is what they do
in the posh places.
Then we're going to make
a Christmas negroni.
I love this!
APPLAUSE
I think of myself
as a Christmas negroni.
LAUGHTER
Only you could have said that.
I couldn't have got
away with that one.
So, negroni, I want you to
think of it as medicine. OK.
Every one of us has
someone a bit boring,
a bit sort of dodgy
coming to the Christmas party.
There's always one.
So what you do is you take this
negroni, AKA medicine... Medicine.
..and it turns people that are
a bit problematic and boring
into interesting people.
What's going to happen? Whoa!
So, a negroni is... Yes!
What's Jamie trying to say?
I know, right?!
And he's pouring three drinks.
This is 20 mils of Campari,
20 mils of vermouth rosso,
which we've scented with a little
cinnamon and Christmas fare. Yes!
And then we have a little gin,
a little bit of clementine
to get you going. Yes!
Are you ready for this?
I'm like, come on, man!
Now, once you sip this, if you don't
become more interesting,
I don't know what's going to happen.
OK.
Go on. OK. Lovely.
Take one, pass it down -
it's like school.
Yeah, go on.
Oh, we have four, we have four.
We have four.
Cheers. Merry Christmas!
Merry Christmas! Merry Christmas!
Merry Christmas, everyone!
This is a bit like A Christmas Carol
and we are Scrooge,
because I'm like,
"Merry Christmas, everybody!"
It's like 600 Tiny Tims. Yes!
OK. Oh, come on.
Come on!
Oh, that is delicious.
The world's changing.
Hold on, I'll be the judge
of whether or not it's delicious.
No, I like that.
It has just enough Christmas in it.
Here's the thing...
No, that's very good.
You want a sip?
You want a sip? Hold on.
Here we go. Uh-oh.
I drank from this side,
so you can drink from that side.
You can drink from the other side.
See what you think.
Is this like feeding a gremlin
after midnight? How's that?
That's good, that's good.
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
Delicious. Yeah.
It's good, isn't it?
It's nice. Yeah. No, seriously...
Now, we've got our
Christmas cocktail...
HE MOUTHS
LAUGHTER
Yeah, a Christmas to remember.
That was the Christmas... Oh.
Jenna Coleman, you have almost
turned into a Christmas tradition
in yourself, in that you did the
Doctor Who Christmas specials...
Yes.
..then Death Comes To Pemberley,
which was on at Christmas,
and now this year, you have got the
Victoria Christmas special. Yeah.
Is it weird,
because you're at home -
does everybody have to stop
and watch you on telly?
I think my family thought this year
was going to be a break...
..and now it's
the Christmas special.
Do you watch it or do
you kind of Sky Plus it
and then come back to it?
My grandma will always watch it
unless Wimbledon's on,
and then I get Sky Plussed
all of the time...
..and then we usually go 50-50,
so you kind of get
the drunk games room
and then my grandparents
watching the telly. Aww.
Or it gets to, like, the heat
of the moment
and Matt Smith is about to die
on Doctor Who
and suddenly my niece Millie
will do a little dance
in front of the telly.
Get out of the way! I'm going to put
this down, in case...
I'll hold that for you, darling.
Absolutely delicious,
but I'm so scared what might happen.
OK. There we go.
Actually, it's hitting me already.
I'm like...
Girl, that's a pretty
dress you've got on!
Has that got a little kick to it?
Yeah. No, no, it's a glow.
It makes everyone nicer.
Let's start with our first
Christmas treat -
Will Smith's movie Bright.
Now, this started
streaming today on Netflix.
It's one of those films, it's like
nothing you've seen before.
It is when genres collide. Yes.
But you've got a very good way
of describing it to people.
Yeah, Bright is... It's out today,
that's right, I like that. So...
What the hell
are you all doing here?!
LAUGHTER
No, it's...
Sort of... Imagine Training Day,
if you saw Training Day,
so it's a sort of
gritty LA cop drama,
so it's like Training Day
meets Lord Of The Rings.
Right?
It sounds like he's making that up.
No.
They're like, "Oh, Will's stupid."
No, but...imagine that Lord Of
The Rings was 4,000 years ago,
but all of the creatures came
forward into the modern day,
so it's a modern-day
rough LA cop drama,
but there's orcs and there's
fairies and there's elves,
as if they've come in to society.
So it's really... It's essentially
about racism, right?
In a really interesting,
bizarre, fun action way.
It does take about five or ten
minutes to get your head round it...
Yeah, yeah. ..and then,
once you're in it, you're in it,
cos the world is so complete.
Yes, it's really bizarre.
Joel Edgerton plays an orc,
and he's the first orc on the
Los Angeles Police Department.
What's an orc? An orc. What is it?
Come on, everybody
knows what an orc is, Jamie!
LAUGHTER
Now, having said that,
I do know what orcs are,
but what is an orc?
It's the...
See, Jenna doesn't know either.
I don't know what an orc is.
It's the thing that
Joel Edgerton is in the movie.
Put the picture...
There it is, that's an orc.
That's an orc. That's an orc.
That's an orc.
Yeah, but a lot of them
have bigger teeth.
You'll see. Yes.
It's directed by David Ayer,
who wrote Training Day.
Yes, he wrote Training Day.
He did Suicide Squad,
so he's into that, you know,
really weird stuff.
It's a whole lot better than
I'm sounding right now, trust me.
You're going to love it!
Here's a clip to demonstrate
what we're talking about
and this is you and Joel Edgerton,
your orc partner,
preparing for a shoot-out. Mm-hm.
I'm running out of patience,
Officer Ward.
Let's give them the wand. What?
Look, we're going to get everyone
in here killed,
and then he's going to take
the damn wand, anyway.
I'm not giving that guy the wand.
Over my dead body.
He's going to have to kill me first.
So you want to die in a gunfight
in a nasty-ass titty bar?
I want to die.
Let's do it right now.
We're going to
titty-bar gunfight die.
Let's do it, right here, right now.
You ready? I just wish your
dumb ass was a better shot.
Let's go, on three.
One... Let's do it.
..two, three.
SCREAMING
Ooh!
APPLAUSE
I'm sure you are wearing some
make-up in this film...
I know, yeah!
Joel Edgerton's wearing a lot.
It was terrible.
Joel Edgerton, he had four
hours a day in make-up. Wow.
So he would do four hours,
and then I'd show up like this.
So, he would have the four
hours and I'd come on set
and go, "Hey, all right,
Joel, what's up?!"
He'd go, "Mm-mm. No."
So, yeah, I mean, I felt bad
taking most of the money.
LAUGHTER
Yeah.
APPLAUSE
You've got so many movies
in the pipeline,
lots of things coming out -
but, I notice, still no sign
of the Fresh Prince Of Bel Air
reboot that everyone wants.
CHEERING
They do! Man...
Make it for them!
I'd have to be Uncle Phil,
and that I wouldn't like.
I'm going to be 50.
"Come on, Aunt Viv!
I'm 50. I can't go out on my own?"
No, you did...
You did drive the fans wild,
because you posted this.
AUDIENCE: Whoo! Oh, yeah.
Did you bump into them,
or...was it a reunion?
So, every year,
Karyn has a charitable event,
and she hosts a lunch with the cast
of the Fresh Prince,
so we do that every year,
and it will be 10 or 12 people
from around the world
that have won this lunch... Wow.
..so, that's in Los Angeles,
and the people flew in
and we have the lunch with the fans
who gave the most to charity.
And you mentioned you
would play Uncle Phil.
A weird thing happened. Mm-hm.
You - I think you were in Africa,
and you bungee jumped.
I bungee jumped, yes. OK.
Some people filmed this
and then you filmed the rest -
so, here you are.
Yeah, I bungee jumped.
So, there you go -
and then you're filming yourself
on a GoPro or something...
GoPro, yeah.
..and people noticed that
if you freeze-frame it
at a certain point... Yes.
..you look remarkably like...
LAUGHTER
..James Avery! It's crazy, right?
Yes! Yeah.
You are never bungee jumping again.
Yeah, yeah!
It's all the blood
rushing to my head.
But that's really... Like, who's
going through it frame by frame?
I love it.
Right, Jenna Coleman's
Christmas treat for us
is Victoria, a Christmas special.
It goes out on ITV on Christmas Day
at 9pm -
and it's sort of perfect,
because so much of our Christmas
came from Victoria... Uh-huh.
..kind of that period.
Yeah, from Albert, really,
so it's before the Christmas tree
was even in England,
so there's a lot of, like, why
on earth would you bring a forest
into your home for Christmas?
It is an odd thing, but it's lovely.
It is an odd thing!
Yeah, and it was before Christmas
cards were invented,
so you kind of see Christmas
becoming the Christmas
as we now know it. Got it.
So, you get that side of it,
you get how they created Christmas,
but there's also this -
and this is true, the story
about her adopting the child.
Yeah. Yeah.
So, Victoria got an unexpected
Christmas gift,
which was a young girl
called Sara Forbes,
who was going to be sacrificed
and then got sent over
to Victoria as a gift,
and Victoria decided to educate her.
Sacrificed?
This was from Africa? Yeah. OK.
King Ghezo. King Ghezo. Of Dahomey.
To... Yeah... So,
he was going to sacrifice her,
and then thought, "Oh, no,
Victoria would love this."
I mean, it was unexpected!
And so difficult to wrap! Yeah.
There is a line, where she thinks
it's going to be a baby elephant,
and then she arrives into the room
and there is complete confusion,
because you're giving me
a little girl,
and she developed this amazing
relationship with this young girl
throughout her entire life,
and educates her,
she becomes part of the court...
Did you know the story? No!
I had never heard this story.
Never heard this story.
Extraordinary.
Well, we're going to watch a clip.
So, this is you and the girl, and...
Is there anything else you need
to tell us about this?
You didn't sacrifice her,
though, right? No, no, no.
Because I'm not going to watch that!
She lived a happy life.
Good. Well... Merry Christmas.
Here you all are,
in a very Christmassy scene.
Victoria, do you know that my
mother, she taught me how to skate?
Do you remember?
Ja. Ja, I remember.
Perhaps one day, we could
teach the Queen ourselves.
Harriet, may I? No, thank you.
Are you coming?
Would you like to try skating, Sara?
No, thank you, Your Majesty.
But it's quite safe.
I promise.
Victoria! Hurry! We are waiting.
I'm going to stay here with Sara.
Would you like to build a snowman?
A snowman?
I'll show you.
Awww!
APPLAUSE
It gets much more exciting!
It does get exciting, yes.
Presumably you didn't
film this in winter? No.
I mean, see... Because, apparently,
I do a lot of Christmas specials,
I'm in Christmas for, like,
six months of the year.
I've been having Christmas
since July.
Snow business. Really?
And it's really hard
to improvise in Victorian language
about a snowman, I've discovered.
Yeah.
Yes, making small talk!
The thing is, you just went
from school to Emmerdale. Yeah.
You didn't go to
drama school in between. No.
Straight in? Yeah, I didn't know
what I was doing.
Because it is one of those weird
jobs were people kind of think,
you learn it and then say it
and that's the end of it,
but there's a lot
of technical stuff.
Yeah, there's like, "Find your
light," and you'd be like...
Yeah, there really is,
"Find my light...?"
You had a problem with marks, as
well, hitting your mark. Oh, yeah.
I could never hit a mark,
because I'm not...
I am a good multitasker,
when you have to...
I mean, throw in a prop
and I'm totally lost... Yeah.
..but it would always be like,
"Hit your mark,"
and I did a couple
of days on Captain America
and it was the first film
I'd ever done,
and it was all, like, really big,
and obviously the set-ups
are massive
and all I remember,
I had obviously not hit my mark,
and I remember feeling someone
like slap the bottom of my leg.
"Go to your mark."
"You in MY mark, girl!
"That's my mark, move!"
What was the thing on Doctor Who
when it was another actor,
I think it was his first job?
Oh, yeah.
It was his first job
out of drama school
and you know what a sausage is,
right?
A sausage? Yeah. Like a...
LAUGHTER
You notice that she didn't ask me!
I'm jealous!
Yeah, like...
So, it's like 11 o'clock... Uh-huh.
Do you call it something
different in America?
We probably call it something
different.
Unless it's, like,
meat, then we... OK.
..we probably call it
something different.
There's obviously a big confusion
somewhere... Yeah.
..but...so, we call marks
that are raised, here, a sausage.
Yeah, we don't say
that in the States. No?
So, it's called a sausage mark.
Just don't do that. A sausage mark.
No, we call them raised marks.
Really?
LAUGHTER
Interesting.
Anyway, it was this
poor guy's first day,
and it was like 11 o'clock
and I was like -
we were setting up a shot, and I was
like, "Can I get a sausage, please?"
And I paid no attention, and then
someone came and brought a mark
and this guy was like,
"Oh, I'm so relieved."
He was like, "I literally thought
it was like 11 o'clock
"and time for Jenna's
morning sausage!"
Being a diva.
Sausage! Sausage!
Sausage, please. "Oh, man, listen,
"that girl don't get
her 11 o'clock sausage...
"We ain't going to shoot
nothing today!"
Jamie Oliver, famously,
you were plucked from obscurity,
you were just a sous chef,
and then you got your own series.
Now, I don't think I knew this -
so, series one didn't go that well.
Well, not the series.
The programme one.
Don't write me whole series off!
LAUGHTER
Yeah, it was the first one -
I actually never
wanted to be on telly,
so we did the first show
and it was terrible.
It was really, really bad.
AUDIENCE: Awww!
That was me before my face
grew into my lips, all right?
LAUGHTER
But, no, basically it was
really bad, and I think...
It's an interesting lesson to be
learned about mistakes, or failure,
or however you want to look at it,
because then we went back,
we had to re-budget the programmes
and, actually, that's when
I started to look off camera,
talk to the director,
have a conversation,
be myself, cut the music
to the music of my record collection
at home, and then be a bit more
documentary about it,
so, really, if it hadn't been
for that massive terrible programme
that you have never
and will never see...
It must exist somewhere,
has it not been...?
There's probably some
in the archives,
but I've just got a feeling that...
It was shot on tape,
which is terrible,
and it has aged badly
and, also, there has been a fire
at the production company
that owned it... That you started!
LAUGHTER
You know, I'm the same,
with the words and the sort of lingo
that goes with filming,
they used to shout, "Speed!"
And I'm just going,
"What is this drug problem?"
LAUGHTER
"Check the gate!"
"We haven't got a gate!
"There's no garden!"
Now, here's the thing,
the Fresh Prince,
that was your very first acting job.
Yeah.
You had never acted before.
Never acted.
So, presumably, you were doing that
thing of just learning on set?
Yes, absolutely.
Yeah, that was... I was very,
very focused on being successful,
so I learned the entire script
and I learned everybody else's line,
and I knew everything about it,
and, if you watch, like,
the first four or five episodes,
you can see, I'm mouthing
the other people's lines.
No way! Yeah.
I would be, like...
If you said, "No way,"
I would be like...
I was like, "Oh, my God!"
It's, like, people...
Nobody noticed,
because psychologically
you're looking at the person
who's talking, but it is terrible.
I can't bear to watch.
It makes me want to go back
and watch them now. I know!
Yeah. Going even further back,
before the acting, before
Fresh Prince, there was music.
There was music, yes.
I was going through my record
collection only the other day...
Oh, no. Tragedy. Oh, no.
..and this... Wow. ..unbelievably,
this is 30 years old.
That is 30 years old.
This is 30 years old.
Wow. DJ Jazzy Jeff and Fresh Prince.
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
How old...
How old was Will Smith here?
Yeah, I was 18 in that picture.
Like, look at my face - like,
what am I trying to accomplish?
LAUGHTER
I tell you what,
you want your 11 o'clock sausage,
that's what you want!
LAUGHTER
You had a hit record
while you were still in high school.
Yeah, in high school. Yeah.
The single from this album is called
Girls Ain't Nothing But Trouble.
Yeah! And...
It's not true, it's not true.
But it was the single that came
out in the last month
I was in high school,
so I was a senior
and had a record out
for probably about 30 days.
That is too much power
for one man to have!
Didn't they play it at your prom?
Yeah, it was...
That's awkward, though,
like, when you're in a place
and, like, DJs think that's cool,
if you come in
and they put your song on.
It just makes you look stupid.
You can't be, like, "Whoo!"
All of a sudden, you've got
to be like, "Yeah, yeah..."
And everyone is looking
at you, like...
"Is he gon' sing?
Is he gon' sing?"
It's an awkward moment.
DJs shouldn't do that.
Oh, very good.
Now, Jamie Oliver's latest -
it's 5 Ingredients,
Quick And Easy Food.
It's out now.
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
Now... Yeah. Yes!
It's the fastest selling book
I have ever done,
and that just means it's resonating,
and I am shocked at how
the young kids have got into it
because it's kind of like
cooking by numbers.
It's, like, making Lego
or something, you know? Yeah.
And, actually,
I even got jumped on...
..not jumped on, but I got
complimented by an 80-year-old woman
the other day, just saying -
and she was clearly a good cook -
just saying that she was using it,
and her shopping was easier,
because it was less stuff to buy
and all that kind of stuff. Yeah.
OK, so, obviously, you could have
made it six ingredients.
Yeah. Or maybe you could
have made it four...
I wrote it for four, originally. OK.
Yeah, and then I kind of...
You get back and you look...
Writing a book is quite
an emotional thing for me
for lots of strange reasons,
it's quite a thing,
and I'd done a good job on four,
but then I didn't feel I was giving
the British public what they needed,
which was a bit of magic,
so the fifth is the magic number,
you can give it a little bit
of a spank. Ooh, ooh!
Look at this!
Oh, you had a little flick
of the wrist, there, bam!
Bam!
Look, there's your five ingredients,
that's all that you need.
Boom, boom, boom, boom, boom,
ba-doom. Yeah. It's so clever.
And that's the 11 o'clock sausage,
right down at the bottom, there.
Yes.
LAUGHTER
A little bit of chorizo in there.
It's smoky.
I have to say, I have overheard
people talking about this book,
people you would never think
in a million years
would be buying a cookbook,
but everyone just believes,
"Five ingredients,
"surely I could do that."
I think it's in tune
with the public now
and the way we work and we live now.
Let me see!
Oh, yeah, have a look. Have a look.
Yeah, have a look.
It's delicious.
Not the book, obviously.
You look so handsome!
Thank you very much.
Photoshop!
Will Smith, do you cook?
Would you ever sit down and cook?
I do now.
Only five ingredients,
I can do this!
Jenna, do you cook?
Um, I... I... No. No.
LAUGHTER
I'm a hazard cook.
If you have to say "I" four times...
"I... I... I..." No.
No, you don't, you don't. No.
Can you sign this for me?
Mm-hm. I mean... I haven't got
a pen, but I could do blood.
You'd do blood? For Will Smith...
Actually, you know, I'm good.
We should mention,
Jamie's other holiday fare
is the latest edition of
Jamie & Jimmy's Friday Night Feast,
it continues next Friday
on Channel 4 at 8pm.
Whoo! Yeah. Oh, sorry!
Let's have a look at a clip,
here we go.
You only have to do this,
like, once or twice a year.
You can make a batch and freeze it.
Yeah.
And when you come back
from a gig, a few prawns...
You think I'm going to do this
when I get home? I hope so!
It's never going to happen, is it?
No.
I'll be doing this, "Hello,
is that the Thai takeaway?" Yeah.
LAUGHTER
Four, lemon grass...
..and for that... Ooh!
..we are going to give
it a little spank.
Did you just spank the lemon grass?
Yes, I did.
That's the name of
my new band, actually.
APPLAUSE
Not a lot of cooking.
There was a little.
And you do... You film
at the end of Southend Pier.
Yeah, it's a mile and a quarter
out to sea, you know,
you guys are coming in next year,
thanks for confirming that.
You do get great guests, though.
We did get great guests,
but, historically, it has always
been people that are real foodies,
that's why they would come out...
Right.
..because it's an hour
outside of London,
but it is a different interview,
a different vibe,
to cook with someone is
quite a precious thing,
and you're just sort of tuning in
to memories, moments,
and we had a really nice mix of
actors and singers and all sorts,
but this year, I did get
Luke Skywalker, Mark Hamill.
Oh! Yes!
And that was a moment for me,
because obviously he was a big
part of my childhood.
Yeah. You are a proper
Star Wars fan.
I am a proper... As is Jimmy,
so we were kind of fighting -
we were trying to get the lines in,
and steal each other's lines
to ask the question, but...
..it was the most brilliant,
and one of the hardest interviews
I have ever done,
because he's got so many stories,
so, like, they're just tangenting
all over the place... Yeah.
..and me and Jim
were trying to bring it back,
but it wasn't happening -
but it was great.
It's like you can't get
a word in edgewise.
Mm-hm. Yeah, I know how that feels.
LAUGHTER
Now, if you think Jamie Oliver's
exaggerating
about how much of a fan he is
of Star Wars, here's a picture...
This is you, this is Jamie taking
a couple of his kids to school.
Oh, yes!
LAUGHTER
Yeah! And that's a proper...
Just look how proud Poppy
and Daisy are, they love it.
It's tough being a teenager's dad.
I am trying to get better at it,
and I went to parents evening
and..."Stop being embarrassing,"
"I'm only breathing!"
So, after that, I'm trying
to calibrate my embarrassingness
and that, I felt, was appropriate.
And this is your proper...
That's not a... No, I bought that.
That's from Pinewood Studios,
legit mould,
massive chafing
around the growler, though, it's...
I mean, honestly, credit
to the real stormtroopers,
cos when you run with that,
there's chafing. There's chafing.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
In America, you would have been
shot and killed wearing that outfit!
When you wear that,
you do feel powerful.
Really? Yeah.
Like, what do you feel
like you could do?
Literally, a minute after that,
I just walked out into the street
and just stopped a bus...
..and then, also,
the hilarious thing is,
the bus driver is a similar age,
and he's like, "I'm stopping.
"This is not normal."
And then I go,
and he opened the door...
IMPERSONATES BUS DOOR
Even sounds right!
"Have you had any problems
with the rebellion?" He went...
Move on.
APPLAUSE AND CHEERING
Science-fiction fans,
they're a different breed of fan -
and you know this, Jenna,
after Doctor Who.
They always own you.
I mean, you will always be a part
of that world for them.
Do you still go to the conventions
and the comic cons and things?
Yeah. Or even, you know,
just around London,
and someone will be
sat next to you
and you will hear this faint...
# Dun-dun-dun, dun-dun-dun... #
LAUGHTER
It's a whole world I didn't know
existed before Doctor Who.
Didn't you have to sign
somebody's underwear?
Oh, yeah, er, no.
Well, I was asked to.
Oh, you refused?
Er... Yes. They said
it's bigger on the inside.
LAUGHTER
Brrrr-dsssssh!
It is the TARDIS reference.
Have you ever seen Doctor Who?
No, I have not.
It's bigger on the inside.
OK, got it.
All right.
I was like, well, that's not fun.
LAUGHTER
I get it, I get it.
Now, talking of
science fiction classics,
it is a year of anniversaries.
20 years since the original
Men In Black.
Oh, wow. Really? I know!
20 years. Wow.
APPLAUSE AND CHEERING
But in my head,
that's a new movie.
It's like, that's a new one, yeah.
That is great. Like, when people
say lines to you,
it's like... Like people...
You shouldn't do that. Like...
For the fans, we should, like, help.
Like, don't walk up to people
and say the line from the movie
because it is like, people
walk up and go, "Hey, Will!
"I'll make this look good!"
That's not how that line goes,
and it's just awkward.
HE FAKES A LAUGH
Yeah, man, only 73,000 people
said that to me in the last...
It's just like...
It just creates awkward moments.
We won't do that.
Cancel that idea,
we're not doing that.
I didn't realise,
Steven Spielberg, he produced it.
Yeah, Steven Spielberg
produced the Men In Blacks.
And so, the two of you, you would
go to screenings of this film.
Well, that was like a really...
That was one of my... I was
brand-new, I'm making movies,
I'm excited. And so they have
what is called test screenings,
where they will show the movie
to people before it comes out.
So I'm going in and it's my first
test screening for Men In Black,
I'm excited,
and we're in the back.
And, I'm like, "Hey, come on,
we got to get in and get a seat."
Steven said, "No, no, no, you don't
get to go in." "What do you..."
I want to see the movie,
I want to sit right in the centre.
And he's like, "No, no,
it's a test screening, the
audience can't know you're here.
"If they know you are here,
it will skew their opinion.
"They'll clap different,
so they can't know you are here.
"After the movie starts,
we'll let it get started,
"and then we'll go in
and sit in the back row."
I was like...
He wants to sit in the
back row of a movie.
Those people back there
are pissed right now.
It's like... But he said...
And we sat and I watched
Men In Black with Steven Spielberg,
and he explained the movements
of the backs of people's heads.
He was like,
you can learn everything
you need to know from the backs of
people's heads watching the movie.
And we sat, and now I can only sit
in the back of the movie theatre.
It's like, you get...
This is the best,
this is going to be awkward,
you can shoot the back.
Do we have to guess the reaction?
There must be some camera that can
see the back of your head, yes.
So, there's this one.
LAUGHTER
Right, and there is the dreaded...
And then there's...this one.
LAUGHTER
Yeah, you hate that one,
you hate this one.
Now, this is the holy grail.
This is the holy grail.
LAUGHTER
Right? Where you have them riveted.
And this is the bottom.
This is the absolute bottom.
LAUGHTER
APPLAUSE
That is the one.
You don't want that! That's
the one where it's all bad.
That's when it's all bad.
Well, listen, it is time
for our musical guest. It is.
He rose to fame as the leader
of British pop rock band Keane.
Now, he brings us
a solo Christmas album.
Here performing the single Midnight
Mass, please welcome Tom Chaplin.
WHOOPING AND CHEERING
# Down every road, we come
# Through driving snow, we come
# All running on empty
# But still dying to make it home
# In spite of everything
# To simple truths, we cling
# To follow the guiding star
of love in our hearts and homes
# So come on, all ye
faithful friends
# Glory to the bitter end
# We're coming up to midnight
# Sing ah-ah-ah-ah-ah
# Hallelujah
# Yeah, come on, all ye faithful,
believe
# Let's sing it out for
Christmas Eve
# Cos it's coming up to midnight
# Sing ah-ah-ah-ah-ah
# Hallelujah
# Step in, shake off the snow
# Safe in the fire glow
# Raise up our voices
# Send them echoing on and on
# Yeah, come on, all ye
faithful friends
# Glory to the bitter end
# We're coming up to midnight
# Sing ah-ah-ah-ah-ah
# Hallelujah
# Yeah, come on, all ye faithful,
believe
# Let's sing it out for
Christmas Eve
# Cos it's coming up to midnight
# Sing ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah
# Ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah
Hallelujah
# Hallelujah
# Down every road, we come
# Through driving snow. #
WHOOPING AND CHEERING
Beautiful!
Tom Chaplin, thank you so much.
And his choir.
Come on over, Tom.
Beautiful. So Christmassy.
Thank you so much.
Lovely to see you. Merry Christmas.
Come and say hello to everybody.
Jamie, Jenna, Will.
All shove up a bit.
Nice to meet you.
There we go.
Very good.
That is gorgeous.
Midnight Mass,
and that is off the Christmas album.
Oh, yes.
The Twelve Tales Of Christmas. Mmm.
Now, this is unusual,
because it's your second solo album,
and you've gone straight to
Christmas.
You know...? Yeah. Yeah.
So, you obviously love Christmas?
I do love Christmas.
I found it very inspiring
to write about, actually.
I mean, it's not your conventional
Christmas album.
I ended up writing
a lot about death.
I can imagine, yeah.
Nice and positive! Yeah!
People like to hold on till
Christmas, don't they?
But I think Christmas,
it's a time of reflection,
so it brings up all sorts
of feelings for us.
Obviously, people
we might have lost along the way,
but also joy and despair
and drunkenness and anger
and crying on the stairs.
Yeah, yeah, I get that.
Crappy presents we didn't want.
Now, talking of Christmas -
Tom Chaplin, what was the thing...?
So, one year,
you've got a turkey that was too...?
How can a turkey be too big?
Well, we only had
a few of us round,
and we left it to the last minute,
so ended up being the idiots
going into the supermarket
on Christmas Eve.
And there was one turkey left that
was for, like, 18-20 people.
So we cooked it up
and there was loads left.
And my wife, bear in mind,
was a vegetarian.
Strict vegetarian, all the time.
So she claimed she didn't want
to eat it.
So we cooked it,
it didn't get finished,
it got put in the fridge,
out in the shed.
And I went back there
a few days later,
and most of it was gone, and I was
thinking, "Where's it gone?"
And then I discovered my wife...
Loves a turkey sandwich?
..had suddenly become a meat eater.
Claiming that she, you know,
she didn't want to murder
this animal in vain.
But it was just greed, really.
Has she stuck with the meat?
It's kind of like going black,
you never go back.
APPLAUSE
Thank you, Tom, for putting us
in such a Christmassy mood.
It was really, really lovely, and
good luck with the album. Thank you.
Tom Chaplin, everybody.
APPLAUSE
OK, that's nearly it.
Before we go, just time for a visit
to the big red chair. Hello!
Hi there, gang.
Hey!
No, no.
Exactly, no.
Not tonight. Not tonight.
Not that attitude, not in here.
Not in the mood. Not in Graham's
house. Not in Graham's house.
No, it's not children's television.
Yeah, yeah.
What was he thinking?
OK, let's have another one.
Hello! Hello!
Hi! What's your name?
Marsha. Marsha, lovely.
What do you do, Marsha? Nothing.
OK!
Everyone wants to sit next
to Marsha at dinner.
Have you ever done anything, Marsha?
I have. You have, OK.
What did you used to do?
I have taught exercise.
Oh, yes?
And I've done make-up. Yes.
Raised children. Yes. Cooked. Yes.
What more do you want?
I mean, that is a full life. That's
a full life, yeah. Exactly.
Exactly.
I mean, it still doesn't explain
why you do NOTHING.
Anyway, off you go, Marsha,
with your story.
So, many years ago, I'd gone
into a very exclusive clothes shop.
GRAHAM GIGGLES
It's not funny! Yet.
So, I'd gone into a clothes shop
and went to try on some clothes,
and there was someone next to me,
in the next changing room,
and I recognised her.
So we spent the next half-hour
trying on clothes,
and we were very honest
with each other,
and I said to her,
"That's really nice on you."
And she said,
We were totally honest
with each other.
After about half an hour,
she came out of the changing room,
and I said to her,
"No, that's really not your colour.
"That just doesn't suit you."
She said to me, "This is what
I came in wearing."
APPLAUSE
That's good one. That is a good one.
You can walk. You can walk.
That was an actual good story.
Yeah. There was a punch line. Yeah.
And I didn't see it coming.
I thought she was going to be
a famous person.
I thought she was going to say,
like, Theresa May or something.
Yes. Yeah, in a kitten heel.
OK, one more, one more.
Hello! Hello!
Hi, how are you? I'm fine,
thank you. And what's your name?
It's Gemma. Gemma, lovely.
And what do you do, Gemma?
I'm a full-time mum. How many kids?
Three. Three, what ages?
18, 14 and 12.
That sounds like trouble.
Yes.
She's in the teeth
of the crocodile right now.
No wonder you
came out for the night.
All right,
off you go with your story.
It was my first-ever driving test,
and I was extremely nervous.
I was taking the test on my own car.
So I got to the test centre
and the examiner came out
and she checked around the car
to check it was safe.
She got into the vehicle with me
and she had a little look around
to check everything was OK.
She noticed that, on the front,
there was a little bag
with nuts and bolts in,
which she asked me to remove
and put in the back of the car.
I picked them up and I swung them,
what I thought between the seats,
and I smashed the poor lady
in the face.
I split her nose
and it was pouring with blood.
And the poor lady was searching
for a tissue this whole time,
and I ended up reversing
into a fence and failing my test!
Aw, bless. You can walk.
APPLAUSE
Well done, everyone.
If you'd like to join us on the
show and have a go in the red chair,
you can contact us
at our website at this very address.
That is it for tonight.
Please say a huge thank you to
my guests - Mr Tom Chaplain!
APPLAUSE
Jamie Oliver!
Jenna Coleman!
APPLAUSE
And Mr Will Smith!
We'll be back here on
New Year's Eve with a very starry
Hogmanay sofa, including
Hollywood heart-throb Zac Efron
and the great Hugh Jackman.
Have a very happy Christmas!
Good night, everyone. Bye!
APPLAUSE