This programme contains
some strong language.
Good evening everyone,
this is Mark Hamill saying,
Welcome to the Graham Norton Show!
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
Lovely to see you. Hi, hi. Hi, hi,
yeah. Hello, you're all very
welcome. Thank you. What a lovely
welcome. Wow - we should do this
again!
Great show tonight.
Yes, Luke Skywalker
himself, Mark Hamill,
is here for the first time.
There he is.
There's something about that
beard that makes him look
dignified and handsome.
Mark is here with other
members of the cast
of the new Star Wars movie,
The Last Jedi.
WOOO!
Sofa - Packed it will be.
Hasn't it been cold this week?
I said cold, cold!
In this weather, it's a good idea
to check on the old and infirm
to make sure they're okay.
Thanks for asking, I'm fine.
A lot of people have been
out building snowmen.
And some of them
really love Star Wars.
Look at the detail of that. BB-8
made out of snow.
Although, some people have been
messing about with snowmen,
putting the carrot in
an inappropriate place.
Come on guys, if 2017
has taught us anything,
you mustn't put your carrot in an
inappropriate place.
I don't know why they bother.
If you want to see something
round and stupid with an orange
willy, just turn the news on.
So, let's get some guests on!
Later we'll have music and chat
from singer-songwriter Mr Sam Smith!
He'll be performing his number one
hit, Too Good At Goodbyes.
But let's meet the stars
of The Last Jedi.
She's the breakout British
star of Game of Thrones
and Top of the Lake,
please welcome Gwendoline Christie!
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
Hello. Gwendoline Christie.
He's our favourite Stormtrooper
turned hero, and one
of our fastest-rising stars,
it's John Boyega!
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
Have a seat.
She stepped off the Orient Express
to board the Millennium Falcon
reprising her role as Rey,
please welcome Daisy Ridley!
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
Shimmers.
And he's the man who started it all,
40 years ago, now Luke Skywalker's
back to save the galaxy.
It's a great pleasure to welcome
for the first time, Mr Mark Hamill!
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
So nice to see you. Into the zone,
into the zone. Lovely to see you
all. Welcome, welcome, welcome.
Thank you. This week you had the big
London premier. Yes. You were all
there. You got to meet Royalty?
Yeah. I said after, you know, rour
Royal Highness and doing all that. I
said - can you settle this for me.
My more a Queen. My faither was Lord
Vader. My sister is Princess Leia,
doesn't that make me royalty in I
was hoping that they would agree.
William said, "well, absolutely. I
think that should make you royalty."
Harry said, "I think I need more
information." Here is the thing,
they are in the movie. Are you
allowed to tell us which
stormtroopers they are? You have to
compare with body type and figure it
out. I had one question for Harry
when I met him, whether he was going
to have Nigerian catering at the
wedding. I hadn't met them before
and I hadn't realised my dress was
slightly sheer. I was almost naked
when I met royalty for the first
Were they very time. Good with eyes?
They really kept the gaze up. The
party was in their house in
Kensington Palace. Is that their
house in I don't know. Into they
talk about the cottage. I'm like -
is it a cottage? That bit we know is
not true. Is there a function room,
how does it work? You walked pass a
canteen. I thought - is that where
we're going? They had a lovely thing
upstairs. That red throne room. I
wanted to pose photographs and was
dragged away by someone. Same! That
was your feet! I had resist the urge
to nic an ashtray. I think they
leave things out for people to
steal. Yes. Yes. It's the big
premier. The Boyega clan were out in
Force. Absolutely, man. You bagged
extra tickets. Aw, babies. This is
your nephew. Yes, little JJ. Is not
called JJ after JJ Abrams? No. He is
named after Jar-Jar.
APPLAUSE
Did you bring everyone to Kensington
Palace? No everyone came down to the
Palace as well. 30 minutes in my dad
was like - where is the proper food?
We had to leave real quick.
Gwendoline even if you weren't in
these films you would be at that
premier. Are you a proper Star Wars
fan? I have a Star Wars fan since
six years old. I've done my best to
keep away from you, Mark, not to
bother and harass you. You were in
Star Wars and also Game of Thrones.
APPLAUS
When those people see you, Game of
Thrones and Star Wars they must have
felt like a rdgasm? That what they
are called. Only occasionally
there's an omission. Eugl! Episode
VIII The Last Jedi. It's open
everywhere. Let's have a look, a
taste of the movie. Let the past
die. Kill it. If you have to. That's
the only way to become what you're
meant to be.
We have a spark that will light the
fire that will burn the First Order
down. AH! This is not going to go
the way you think. Fulfil your
destiny! Oh!
APPLAUSE
Very good. Star Wars is review
proof. Wow, the reviews have been
amazing. It's great. Must be
delighted with it all of you. Funny
being it and watch the trailers and
get the same goose bumps. It's still
Star Wars. Mark we find some
detachment to it, it hasn't been so
long for us. Experiencing that, it
gives you the goose bumps, man.
Mark, reassure everyone you are in
this film more than in the last one?
I can assure you in this movie my
part is twice as big. Two pages! I
appear and turned the page and it
said, "the end". I went what! ? Why
did they make me train for a year.
Did you train for a year? I went
twice a week. I drove to the gym
Carrie had the equipment installed
in her house. Numerous times she
would come to the door and said, is
it today"
it today", I'm not in the mood." I
rearranged my whole schedule. Never
late. Never missed a session. It was
probably smart of them because if JJ
had told me what my participation
was I wouldn't have been motivated
to stay object on the - if it tastes
good, don't eat it. I could have
been the size of Marlon Brandon. In
those robes no-one would know. We
find you on the Irish Crag. Up the
coast of Ireland. YEP! It's like a
big ad for Irish tourism. It looks
fabulous, it really does. You were
there to find him, Daisy? I was.
Yes. Or Rey was. Imagine if you had
been living there and was like,
"mark!" When I first read the
script, I was only in it for 20
seconds. I thought it would be green
screen. Go up the road to JJ's
studio in San Monaco and will be
done by lunchtime. Little did I
know. There are over 600 steps. I
asked - how long are you you giving
the crew to get up there? They said
45 minutes. I said gave me an
hour-and-a-half. It was brutal. A
big part of the movie is the Jedi
training. Right. It harks back to
when you got your Jedi training from
Yoda. There you are. You recreated
that with Daisy. We did. It went
viral. Here you are. Strong legs,
Daisy Ridley. Oh, yeah, I've been
working out a lot and also Mark too.
Fans will really like the porgs
which live on your island. That's
right. Oh, look at it! These got you
in trouble with Disney, Mark? A
little bit. There was a picture of
Luke surrounded by them. I riposted
the pictures with the
hashtag - wholesome porgogrophy.
Disney said - don't do that. It's
because the cape was o open.
Neighbourhood flasher! The fans have
gone big on them. They found the
images, they like them. They have
imagined them in other films.
Spin-offs. There is the classic -
PORG. That's good. What else, Alien.
And, oh, beautiful this. Titanic.
Wow. It's not just movies. They
imagined them appearing in art.
Nice. And even politics, ladies and
gentlemen.
APPLAUSE
Please.
John, did you worry at the end of
the last film. You knew were coming
back you signed for three, right?
Have you? Haven't you? Well can't...
The rumours are going to start. Oh,
man. Now you are starting a rumour
you are not in the next film. Yes...
See Star Wars... . At thes an
amazing film. In renegotiation. It's
in front of your very eyes. Le you
must think - in a coma. I wonder how
much I will have in the next film?
Yes. When that slash went up my back
they added extra leather pieces
flying around. I saw blood I thought
- wow, that mortgage is not getting
paid. But I'm back. You are very
much back. One of the things we saw
in the clip there, Finn and Captain
Phasma get into it. You have a big
fight. You have been saying how, I
guess it's ying and Yang. You were
in the outfit it must make it
harder. Not ideal. Hard to move in
the outfit let alone fight John. If
you had seen what she was doing and
the training she was ferocious. I
was like - can she actually see.
Every time I was swinging at her I
was just doing. You have to fight
her as though you can see. Lashing
out. My word, the strength, there
was a moment of contact. The power
with which John met me with, I will
never forget. Powerful moment. That
was me trying to save my own life,
Gwen am If I was a betting man, in
that fight, I would put money on
Gwendoline. You do have the
advantage. We talked about this. I
have a higher centre of gravity.
That's not an advantage. I have a a
contract on my side!
APPLAUSE
Can you do a face-off. The start of
the match. It only works if you
stand. Stand. I'm warming up my
knees. Don't do tippy-toes again.
Here we go, here we go.
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE. That is
impressive. One of the things you
have got to deal with is that
intense secrecy about the plot
details. John, I heard you were on
Radio 1 saying you could not keep
all the secrets yourself. You can't.
Now on the second film, you need
someone to tell everything to. You
tell everything to one person. Who
did you pick? My roommate, Stephan.
Now everyone knows that he knows. I
am not giving you his second name!
He lives in your house! Daisy, I
imagine you are like a sphinx and
you do not crack. I cannot keep my
own secrets but those of other
people, fantastic. People often tell
me things about themselves, without
me asking and people say because I
have a big face, I look honest. I
can keep other people secrets. It is
one of the reasons for that is
because you do not really know the
plot? I was surprised by this film.
I had read it and then I put it away
and I did my bit and I went to the
set a couple of times, but
otherwise, I went home!
Gwendoline, you got
the double whammy.
You've got Game Of Thrones and this.
I was having root canal surgery and
there was a clamp holding my mouth
open and I had the bed and all the
lovely plastic things around and I
was reclined back in the chair, it
was not an ideal situation and the
dentist left the room. I am lying
there with my mouth open and the
dental nurse says to me, tell me
what happens in Game of Thrones! She
literally had me where she wanted
me. She was not going to let me go.
She said, what is it like being
naked with Jamie Lamb buster, tell
me it is sexy!
Mark Hammill, you had the grandaddy.
You had, I mean, one of the biggest
secrets in cinema history,
that Darth Vader was your father.
Yeah.
Spoiler alert!
Kids are just on episode two.
What?!
So how long did you have
to keep that secret?
Well, the contrast was when we did
Star Wars, nobody cared.
You know, I read it and I gave it
to my friend to read.
I said, "This is the goofiest
thing I've ever read."
He called and he said,
"You're right, it is goofy.
Can I give it to Meredith?"
I said, "Sure!"
I passed it all around.
Nobody cared.
By the second film,
that's when the scrutiny
became more intense.
Yeah.
There was a wonderful
substitute revelation.
In that scene, the way
we filmed it, Vader said,
"You don't know the truth,
Obi-Wan killed your father."
And the idea of Alec Guinness
being the real villain, I thought -
wow, what a spectacular twist.
And it's just as you
see in the film, "No!
Search your feelings,
you know it's true."
Wallop, the hands goes off.
So vivid, it's so vivid.
The director, Irvin
Kershner, took me aside.
He came to my dressing room
actually and he said,
"I'm going to tell you something.
I know it, George Lucas knows it
and when I tell you,
you'll know it, but if it leaks,
we'll know it was you."
So I said, "What, what?"
He handed me the piece of paper that
said, "I am your father."
I was shocked.
I said, "Is that true?"
He said, "Well, you search
your feelings, and we're
going to play it like."
So, oh, my gosh - Dad Vader.
And then I was paranoid
because I thought, you know...
It was way before social
media and all of that.
Yeah.
I had to keep the secret
for about a year-and-a-half.
I didn't tell Carrie,
I didn't tell...
Well, you know telephone,
telegraph, tell a Carrie!
She had no vault whatsoever.
In fact Harrison
and I would test her.
If you really wanted
to get something out fast,
you'd ask Carrie to keep
in confidence, and out it would go.
So at the screening,
when that happened, Harrison
turned to me and said,
"Hey, kid, you didn't
fucking tell me that."
I apologise for the F-bomb, I only
used it for historical accuracy.
But, yeah, I mean, I was so thrilled
because, I mean, I don't liking
having the burden of that.
I talk in my sleep, you know.
It could be really dangerous.
Does Harrison like your
impression of him?
No.
Actually, he once said to me, "Hey,
I don't sound anything like that."
It's very accurate!
I read somewhere where back then
some of the special effects
were simpler than maybe
they are now.
Yeah.
So the Jedi mind control,
when you can move objects.
Explain how they did that?
Well, first of all, George called
Star Wars the most expensive,
low budget movie ever made,
and what he meant was every penny
had to go up on the screen.
The ingenuity was fantastic.
So for instance, when I was hanging
upside down in the Wampa Cave,
they had fishing wire attached
to it, and pulled it out of my hand
and then just reversed the film.
Oh, OK.
So it's very simple.
But I mean, the ingenuity
is tremendous.
Now they CGI it and spend
way too much money.
Can we see if we can recreate it
in a very low-tech way?
I'm game.
OK.
So if I give you - if we move that -
if I give you an orange.
No, no you're good.
If I give you an orange.
Well maybe you better move them
farther in case my aim is off.
So if you could try to just get it
in that general vicinity.
OK.
So hang on.
Wait, wait, wait.
So we've go to look astonished.
This will all make sense.
We've got to look astonished
when Mark is holding the orange
and then slowly back to nothing
as the orange lands.
OK?
OK.
OK, so are we all set?
Right, I hope so.
OK.
APPLAUSE.
I think that was good,
I think that was good.
OK, was this a good one?
Was that good?
OK.
Let's watch it back,
let's watch it back.
All right.
Here we go, OK.
APPLAUSE.
That's good, isn't it?
Very good.
Excellent.
Money well spent.
It doubles as a salute to BB8, bad
entrance. I liked the way it was
just thrown. The force was weak and
then strong. When it ended, the
first three, the franchise ended,
where you relieved that it was over
or were you sad? It was sort of like
the end of school, you're clearing
out your locker, knowing that you
were not going to see everyone
again. You really bond and become a
family and you spend more time with
the cast and crew on with your real
family. There was a sense of
completion, a beginning, middle and
end and I thought, that is it. It
must have been weird, you must have
assumed you could stop being Luke
Skywalker at some point in the
future. And it never happened,
Carrie talked about it, she is
Princess Leia. She was really made
Dutchman, and she came to see me on
by and asked about my biography,
Mark Hamill, known for a series
space films and she said Mark, I'm
Princess Leia, your Luke Skywalker,
get used to it and get over
yourself. She was always miles ahead
of me in terms of realising what was
the obvious. That thing with
Harrison and Carrie and yourself,
because of what happened, you were
part of each other's lives and it
seems so fitting in a way that you
got to say goodbye in this way, in
this movie to carry. Yeah. Really,
it hit us all hard and I am not sure
that I have really gone through the
stages, denial, acceptance, the
bargaining, because she is so in the
present for me, not in the past
tense, she is wonderful in the
movie. So good. She did not rate
herself as an actress, she rated
herself as a writer but she was so
proud of this movie. She knew she
had done something really good. She
is wonderful in the movie. The tough
part is that you want to grieve in
private, but she belonged to the
world, so not only does it come up
in a daily basis with the public,
but you go on press junkets and you
are asked about 47 times a day and
you want to be sincere every time
and not slip into, I will never stop
missing her, I will always Love,
because it is true. I found this
movie really moving. They handled it
really well. Really nicely. The
movie is the same as it was always
going to be. They didn't change
anything. It has ended up being this
beautiful love letter to her as well
as everything else. It is a whole
other dimensions. It is that amazing
thing that Joan Didio said that her
husband passed away, she kept
expecting him to come back the
wonderful thing is that we do get to
see her again, doing what she loved
and what she is brilliant at.
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE. I suppose...
You didn't know what you were
getting into when you signed up
for Star Wars, but you guys did.
You knew that this
film was a big deal.
So, Daisy Ridley, where were you?
What were you doing when you were
told you were going to be a big part
of this Star Wars world?
Um...
I was at the theatre.
I was at the Tristan Bates Theatre
and I was with my friend and I'd
been at an audition earlier
on in the day.
And I got an email -
it literally makes my heart
pound thinking about it -
I got an email from JJ
and I was like - "Wait, what?!"
Saying, "Hey, can I call you?"
I was like, "Ah!"
I had to ask to borrow a charger
and then I had to do the audition
for this other thing,
and then I went to the theatre.
Then I was looking at my phone
thinking, he hasn't called yet,
and I checked my voicemail
and there was a voicemail.
I was like, "Oh, God.
Oh, God."
And then I didn't know how to call
America because I had never called
America from my English phone.
Anyway, I finally got through.
They were like bad robar.
I said, "What's going on here?!"
And I thought I basically had
to convince him over
the phone that I was...
It's so weird, I haven't
thought about this in ages.
I know it makes your
heart pump, ain't it?
It's literally making my heart pump.
Yeah, it's mad.
And I thought I had to convince him
and he was going, "You know,
this is going to be this.!
I was like, "I'm ready, I'm ready.
I can do it, I can do it.
He goes, "Yeah, yeah,
you're going to be in Star Wars."
I was like...
Oh!
And I was outside the theatre
and the play had started,
and it was a fucking long play.
And I had to go back
in and finish it.
APPLAUSE.
Yeah.
Of course, you can't celebrate?
No.
I literally went in, sat down next
to my friend and was like...
eugh.
It was nuts.
You go to extreme lengths now to
avoid situations. I think with this
fame stuff, it really affects you
differently, everyone has their own
individual experience, it depends
what kind of life you lived before
and I always went midnight shopping.
I would go midnight shopping, is it
just me, really late or is that just
me? I feel like I want to start. Not
like filler grocery shop. Milk and
eggs. Crisps and chocolate. You go
to a proper supermarket. Asda has
got something going on there, do you
know what I mean, go down there,
make it work. Do people recognise
you in the middle of the night? Some
people do and they think why we're
John Boyega be doing this. That is
the key. Sometimes, you had a very
sweet encounter, in an airport? It
was before, I was going through
customs and is a small girl with her
mother and she pinch my jacket and I
turned right, she was so small, and
she said Mr Finn, is your bag OK and
I was like, and I looked up at her
mum, and she was like, you'd better
lie to my child! Yeah, my bike is
OK! It was that sweet moment, the
kids do not see you as the actor,
they see you as the character, but
there is still something so magical
about that.
Gwendoline, you got
the double whammy.
You've got Game Of Thrones and this.
So do you get bothered all the time?
I mean, it can be quite
intense, but it...
I think the pinnacle of this
intensity manifested itself
at a restaurant, fairly recently.
I went to the bathroom.
So this is in a restaurant?
Yeah, this is in a restaurant.
And it's a, you know,
it's a fairly expensive
restaurant, actually.
Thank you very much!
Thank you very much.
And I went into the bathroom,
and I went into the stall,
and I went to lower myself
into the correct position.
What I believe to be
the correct position.
Yes.
And then under the door...
No!
..slipped a hand.
With a phone.
NO!
And a female voice said, "selfie."
YES!
Who?
Who would do that?
I just said, "No, thank you",
And the hand slipped away.
These guys were forewarned. For
you... It was my first film, I had
done a lot of television and
theatre, but you do one movie and...
I appreciate it now. In a way, I
could not in my 20s, with a little
perspective, at that age, you go
Wow, every movie I do will become a
pop culture phenomenon! Note to
self, wrong! One of the reasons it
was good to come back, is to show
the way I am now because there was a
long gap where the original fans
grew up and had children of their
own, you would be at the airport and
the parents were saying, look who it
is, it's Luke Skywalker and this
four-year-old, they have no concept
of time, they think you made Star
Wars last week and the Luke Garbutt
me in their 50s and they were
aghast! -- and they look at me. And
now it is good for them to see the
ageing Luke Skywalker. The last
thing I want in life is frightening
small children!
Right, it's time for music.
This man has an Oscar,
a Golden Globe and a handful
of Grammys to his name,
and now he's back
with his second album.
Performing Too Good At Goodbyes,
it is Sam Smith.
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
# You must think that I'm stupid
# You must think that I'm a fool
# You must think
that I'm new to this
# But I have seen this all before
# I'm never going to let you
close to me
# Even though you mean
the most to me
# Cos every time I open up, it hurts
# So I'm never going to get
too close to you
# Even when I mean the most to you
# In case you go and leave me
in the dirt
# But every time you hurt me
The less that I cry
# And every time you leave me
The quicker these tears dry
# And every time you walk out
The less I love you
# Baby, we don't stand a chance
It's sad but it's true
# I'm way too good at goodbyes
# I know you're thinking
I'm heartless
# I know you're thinking I'm cold
# I'm just protecting my innocence
# I'm just protecting my soul
# I'm never going to let you
close to me
# Even though you mean
the most to me
# Cos every time I open up, it hurts
# So I'm never going to get
too close to you
# Even when I mean the most to you
# In case you go and leave me
in the dirt
# But every time you hurt me
The less that I cry
# And every time you leave me
The quicker these tears dry
# And every time you walk out
The less I love you
# Baby, we don't stand a chance
It's sad but it's true
# I'm way too good at goodbyes
# No way that you'll see me cry
# Oh, oh, oh, oh
# I'm way too good at goodbyes
# No, no, no
# No
# Oh-oh-oh-oh
# No way that you'll see me cry
# I'm way too good at goodbyes
# Cos every time you hurt me
The less that I cry
# And every time you leave me
The quicker these tears dry
# And every time you walk out
The less I love you
# Baby, we don't stand a chance
It's sad but it's true
# I'm way too good at goodbyes. #
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
Sam Smith. Come on over. That's so
beautiful. Thank you so much. Come
in, sit down. Sam Smith meet
everybody, Gwendoline, John, Daisy
Mark. There you go. Lovely, lovely,
lovely.
There you go. Congratulations. That
of course is off the album the The
Thrill of it All. Well done you,
sir. Thank you. I'm going to have a
glass of wine. Do - neck it. You
must be so relieved. There is that
thing - where it match the fist
album. This so has? Thank you. It's
stressful it really was. I can
imagine it's wildly stressful. I
want to sing for the rest of my life
and I hope that people want to hear
me. No-one is going to stop you. I
could always sing in the shower. You
will be singing, you're fine. With
this album, it's not - how can I put
this - it's not the cheerest of
albums. Never, I am rape not that
guy. You can turn to the Spice Girls
for the Cherie stuff. When you write
them are you feeling it or do you
think, this is good? I'm unlucky
with love. I write love songs.
Hopefully the third album will be
happy, joyious. OK. Yeah. I don't
want to upset the actors on the
couch. Since your were last here you
won an Oscar! APPLAUSE
Take that!
Is the Oscar sat in your somehows? I
feel it doesn't count, does it? It
does. It's a proper Oscar. I can't
look at it, I will wait until I'm
60, 70 I will surround myself with
my albums and Oscar and cry and eat.
I hide it in this thing in my house.
I can't look at it. It freaks me
out. Do you not let friends take
pictures with it? When I'm drunk.
When I'm drunk I'm like, "look at
this." There is a particular
character in Star Wars you are a big
fan of I notice from the social
media. Yes. Did you see the film or
meet the creature? I saw the film as
a kid. I was obsessed with the
creature. When I was Japan on tour.
Ewoks. When I was in Japan on tour.
They were every. Where I went to a
toy shop there was a life-size Ewok.
Life-size. I had to get it. We have
nice pictures. I'm obsessed. There
you are. So cute. Does he feature on
the album? It looks like you... He's
leaving me! This Ewok is weird
looking. That is's a pillow. You
haven't just ripped its head off!
That will teach you. I like the
trivia. You said in an interview
they weren't suppose to be ewoks? I
have no memory of that! I know what
you are talking about. Originally
George wanted to go to the Woki home
planet it was down to costs. A lot
of fake fur. They make those
Chewbacca suits hair by hair. I
visit the creature shop, the artists
are incredible, incredibly talented.
George said, let us do a chunken
version so we don't need to make the
costume big. It's very clever. It is
and cheap. They are big in Japan?
I'm waitling for Sam's love song to
ewoks. It's coming. We're taking it
slow. Not a lot Rye ams with ewok
apart from the obvious!
We you had a similar Royal visitors
at the James Bond premier? Oh, yes.
It was exciting. They told me that
you have to bow and I thought when
you bow you fully go down like that.
I was at a full right angle. It was
the most embarrassing thing ever. It
looked dirty!
I like this, though. I like... You
are genuinely angling for an invite?
Oh, hell yeah, I'm obsessed have you
seen The Crown. I wouldn't mention
that when asking for an invite? I'm
obsessed with them I love what they
wear. The Queen is so cute. I want
to meet her. You could be the turn
at their reception. Yeah. A lot of
sad dumping songs - I will up it for
them. A happy wedding. Do covers.
Rock. No-one will know. The the
album, congratulations on 2017, what
an amazing year for you. Continued
success in 2018. Sam Smith
everybody.
APPLAUSE
Right, that's nearly it,
but before we go, just time
for a visit to the Big Red Chair.
Before we get to the Red Chair...
Have you seen this? Yes, yes. This
is the lever. If you want to use
your Jedi Master powers to flip the
lever... You see how well I did with
the orange. Feel free. We spent a
lot of money - please do it! Here we
go. Who is up first? Hello. Hi. What
is your name? Bona. Where do you
live? Oxford. What do you do? Work
for the HMS In finance. Don't boo
her she has a very good job. I don't
know. She may be useless. You might
be about to be fired.
We don't know. Let's assume she's
good at her job. Off you go. OK. Me
and my sister went shopping one day
and I was trying to reverse into a
parking space. It was very, very
tight. I said to my sister, can you
get out and help me. She gets out of
the car and she's directing me. I'm
looking in the wing mirror. He
starts hitting my car. I get out of
the car she went - the car is on my
foot! I was like, what is your foot
doing under my - ah! I had hoped for
more. I did it manually. We don't
want to wear it out. I did it
manually. Shall we do another one?
Sure. What is your name? Lynn. What
do you do? I work in a GP's surgery
in the treatment room. OK. You don't
know Bona in finance, do you? No. I
like you are wearing your lanard on
TV - that's good. That's a good way
to identify you and fire you. OK.
Off you go with your story. We are
going some years back. I was a
prison officer and during that time
- She's lived, hasn't she? Yes. Oh,
you don't know the half of it! At
the time it was the prison's
responsibility to take the prisoners
to the court hearings. I was never
very good traveller. Between going
from the prison to the court I swat
my back to the engine in a vehicle
with no windows I was feeling pretty
horrible by the time I got there.
However, I tried to be brave, carry
on you know with this feeling of
water in your mouth constantly. Yes,
yes. Anyway, we took the prisoner up
to the dock where the judge started
to run through some of the awful
things that had happened in this
case. I threw up on the back of the
prisoner. At which time he was taken
back to the cells, I was sent home
and I never done court duty again.
The vomit. You are a cruel man, but
fair. I think so. Let's have another
one. Oh, hello. Oh, wow! I wonder if
he's a Star Wars fan? What is your
name, sir? Jason. Where do you live?
Tatooine. Oh, well done. That was
good. Well done everyone.
If you'd like to join us on the show
and have a go in the Red Chair,
Please say thank you to my
guests - Sam Smith,
Gwendoline Christie, John Boyeg,
Daisy Ridley and Mark Hamill.
Join me next week with singer
Tom Chaplin, top TV chef
Jamie Oliver, Victoria star
Jenna Coleman and the one
and only Will Smith.
I'll see you then!
Goodnight.
Bye-bye.