This programme contains  some strong language.
And it's my absolute pleasure to say  welcome to the Graham Norton Show!
Oh, the anticipation -  I'm on tenterhooks.
I'm like Meghan Markle waiting  to find an engagement
But can I just say,  what a lovely week it's been
for our Prime Minister,  Theresa May!
than with a huge  party...conference.
First of all, to be fair,  she did have a very sore throat.
That can happen when you are going  "No! " at poor people.
Did you see that bit  where her speech was interrupted
You know, that guy that turns up  at events and behaves like a twat?
Boris is now favourite to be  the next Prime Minister.
I say favourite, it's like deciding  which STI you'd prefer.
And to cap everything off,  did you see the letter F come loose
from her party slogan  while she was talking?
You really know things have gone  tits-up when even your own
Later we'll have music  and chat from rock and roll
But first - he's a Grammy and Emmy  award-winning stand-up
He's back on our shores  with his new show, Total Blackout.
It's a warm welcome back  to the brilliant Chris Rock!
This Hackney heartthrob rose to fame  as Stringer Bell in The Wire and has
gone on to play roles as diverse  as Nelson Mandela and
And starring with Idris  in The Mountain Between Us is one
She's won four Golden Globes,  a Grammy, an Emmy and an Oscar.
Long time no see. You were backstage  hanging out, shooting the breeze.
Chris and Kate, do you know each  other? Not at all. Always admired
Kate and her work. Likewise. She's  the only white woman celebrity with
white children in the world.  LAUGHTER
Quite an accomplishment. Just you.  Only one. No, my word. People point
in the street. Wow! Beautiful  children. Somebody giving white kids
a chance! LAUGHTER  Idris and Kate, you worked together
but was your first time meeting at  the Baftas? It was, yeah. We met at
the Baftas and we presented  together, it was at the beginning of
last year I think. This picture, do  you know this, it became a kind of
meme on the Internet. Idris knows!  What did I do wrong? My favourite
was, if Kate Winslet had held onto  Leo as hard as she's holding onto
Idris, he might not have died!  LAUGHTER
Chris Rock, great to have you back  doing comedy. Are you doing this
because it is such a rich pickings  for comedy in the world? I'm doing
it because I got divorced, so I'm  broke! I need money. LAUGHTER
It's a global tour. Yes! You need a  lot of money. My gosh, you see this
sip. My ex-wife got 30% of that.  LAUGHTER
So, the Trump Joad is presumably  just write themselves for you? Yes,
unfortunately -- Trump jokes. It  might work out. Give him a chance!
You know what, I don't know him know  him, but are used to see Trump at
clubs and stuff. I was at this  place, the China club in New York
and Trump would come in with a suit  on and girls would be all over him,
like I'm going to... Donald Trump!  It was like 20 years ago, they would
be all over him. Wow! A bunch of  girls would be going, wow, Trump. He
was the man. He's the devil!  You were proper friends with
the Obamas, you were at the famous  last White House party.
I was there.  It was scary.
I remember I...  I just remember like, hanging out.
First of all, every  black person was there.
Jay Z, Beyonce, Oprah,  so it's like I'd died
and went to black heaven.  I remember, at one point
in the night, I was like,  with Michelle Obama and she was kind
of sad, "I don't know  what we're going to do."
"I don't know what's  going to happen."
I was like, "You'll be all right!"  LAUGHTER
You know,  Housewives Of Atlanta, something.
LAUGHTER  "You'll get on something."
"You'll be fine."  And she looks at me and she goes,
"I was talking about the country."  I've never felt
so stupid in my life.  And actually, Idris,
we've got a picture of you,  here you are, in the White House.
Yes.  I met the man.
Oh, look.  It was great.
Sharing laughs.  Do you remember what you
were laughing about?  Yeah, exactly.
Was it about David Cameron?  LAUGHTER
No-one's talking  to him, he's just like...
LAUGHTER  President Obama at the time
was telling me I was his second  favourite character in The Wire.
Oh.  Omar, number one.
Yeah, Omar was his favourite  so I laughed out loud,
as you can see, like  "Come on, man!".
Have you hung out in the White  House? No, I haven't. But I did meet
the Queen, does that count? Yes, it  does! Have you got a CBE? Yes. Why
weren't you fast tracked to Dame  Kate Winslet, it sounds right. No,
it doesn't! Were you slightly  annoyed when you open the envelope
and it said CBE? It's definitely one  of those ones for the parents, my
parents were very excited. Is she a  fan, did she say that she loved you
in something? She has the most  incredible skin, and beautiful
bouncing hair. And there is a  system, she's very well rehearsed
and practised at this. You're told  what to do, you step forward and
curtsy or bow and she gives you a  suggestive nudge backwards, saying,
you're done, that's it! And then she  said, well, congratulations on your
achievements. She said, you're a  mother, and she said, that is the
only job. And I thought, good lady,  I was really touched that she said
that. And then she went... LAUGHTER  So, better get back to it! Fair
enough, I have to say. Kate and  Idris, you bring us a new movie, The
Mountain Between Us, opening  tonight. A rare thing, the romantic
survival movie! Wynne that's all  romance is!
That's all it is. There's the 60%!  So, it's an extraordinary story
because you didn't really crash a  plane but you were really on the
mountain, for how long? How long  were we mounting for? On the
mountain! Press the red button.  Titles. The shoot was for about
seven weeks but the -38 stuff, we  were there for about four weeks,
give or take. Give or take, very  cold. You are sharing a small plane.
We are total strangers, they don't  know each other and they are trying
to get from Idaho to New York. I'm a  photojournalist and Idris is
performing a neurosurgery. They  charter a light aircraft together
and the plane goes down in bad  weather, the pilot is killed and
they crashed into the side of a  mountain and it's the story of how
the two of them try and get  themselves home. The two of you and
a dog. Wonderful. The dog does very  well, I felt, no chapped lips,
doesn't lose any weight. A glossy  coat and chasing balls at the end.
Incredible performance. Was it just  one dog? Yeah. And I just say, I
thought, please may this film not go  to the place where you're sitting by
the fire looking at the dog,  thinking... Relax. Didn't happen.
But they did have sex with the dog!  We will whet your appetite now,
Chris. This is a clip from The  Mountain Between Us. Your character
is a beery and sing something nice.  -- is experiencing some thin ice.
And that is really you? Yeah and it  was really Idris as well, funnily
enough. It was -30 eight. Yeah. You  kind of feel like, if you stick your
tongue outcome what is it like, do  your eyes stick together? Don't try
and take a piss. Crystals. Is it  little or is it one long bicycle? --
icicle. It is,,, then you put it  away. Is it the same with ladies? It
is but we have to get more of our  body out of clothes in order to be
able to pee which is challenging but  I was delighted by the portapotty.
The great thing about having a wee  and a poo is that it immediately
freezes. You had a poo? We've all  been in one of those portaloos. You
all had a shit at some point in the  film! You would go into this
portaloo and think, OK, fine, but  everything's fossilised. No wonder.
I can do this. How long were you in  the toilets for? Scientific. It's
easier for boys to wee and it is for  girls, so I tried to use the
fossilised Porter party. And despite  the temperatures, romance blossoms.
Yes.  ALL: ooh!
Idris Elba.  We think of Idris Elba as a leading
man, as a ladies' man...  But you haven't actually done
that many love scenes?  No.
Why is that, how is that?  Umm...
Aah...  LAUGHTER.
No, I just haven't  had the opportunity.
I've done a lot of films  where there's a lot of guys.
No, that's not true.  That's no excuse!
APPLAUSE.  How can I say it...
I just haven't been  in any romantic...
That would be a real good movie!  No, I'm not...!
Umm...  But, no.
LAUGHTER.  It rose in the mountains,
something like that!  But the director had never directed
a love scene, is this right?  Yeah, that's true.
So, "awkward"...  Kate Winslet...
I'm afraid I had to get quite bossy.  So, I've done a few of these
kinds of scenes before.  So we get there and poor Hany,
our director, he's such a lovely man  and he was really quite nervous.
And he had an extensive shot list  and I'm thinking, oh, my God,
they're absolutely never  going to get all of this done.
What kind of scene is this, anyway?  There was like 25 shots!
And Idris...  You were a little bit
nervous, weren't you?  Not really, no!
Well, OK.  That was my game,
to just get in there.  Deadly!
Everything was moving quite slowly  and I'm, like, look...
OK...  We need to really start filming
this, what's with all this chat?  And Hany said, actually,
I'm really kind of nervous,  I've never done this...
I really never have  shot like this before.
And Idris said, no, I've never done  much of it either, and I went...
OK!  Put the camera over there and we're
going to do this and we're  going to do that and then Idris
said, keep your socks on.  And I'm like, keep my socks on?
Everything else is off!  What's with the socks?
No, I've got a foot thing.  I've got a thing.
You know?  LAUGHTER.
I didn't want the socks took off  and they were like...
Hobbit feet?  And I would be like...
This was a moment.  Oh, my God!
It's talon time!  Yes!
I've got very big feet  and they're not particularly
beautiful feet, either.  They're all right!
I shall keep them inside  the shoes that they are in.
Anyway...  So, I'm thinking, Idris doesn't
want to see my feet because maybe  he just does not like feet
in general and that's  the whole thing.
It's the opposite,  ladies and gentlemen.
Idris LOVES feet!  Listen...
Everybody take your shoes off!  I can't wait to see this movie!
Chris, who directed yourself? In a  sex scene was Mike yes. That is
funny! I had a ball! I had a lot of  balls! I had a great time, great
girls, they were down, whatever. I  did direct myself. In between takes
would you run to the monitoring  naked and have a look and come back?
Yes!  APPLAUSE.
The interesting thing is Kate  Winslet, the all-American in the
film and Idris Elba plays British  and we have heard your American
accent, Chris, did you watch The  Wire? Did you know he was British?
Not at all! He's scared the shit out  of me! Nobody knew you were British?
The truth is, I auditioned for this  for so long and they told me, don't
come in with your English accent.  You auditioned? Four times! Get out
of your! Who else was in the room?  Idris Elba or Martin Lawrence? !
Some of the great young New York  actors, there was a lot... For real.
If I was going to audition Anne Soy  be in the lobby I would just turn
around! Idris is here! -- and I saw  you. But your American accent has
not always been that good! What is  about to happen? Space precinct from
1994? Oh yeah... 1994? You have  never seen this? I have heard is a
clip and I had a quick look on  YouTube and they doubled over my
voice, it is not me! I am not  joking! It is actually me! Whoever
it was did not even do a very good  American accent either. Have you got
it? We do! This is Idris Elba, but  beautifully done, the dubbing, you
may not even notice that it is not  in speaking! Are you involved with
the police? We just concentrate on  doing what you do best. Being
beautiful. It's a? I will meet you  in the day. I'll be back. Hot
delivery, anywhere guaranteed!  APPLAUSE.
That is good! Chris Rock is back, is  called Total Blackout and a lot of
the British dates and a lot of the  British dates have sold out new
ones? I don't know. I will have to  read this... Very small! New
dates... Cardiff and Bournemouth? I  have no idea! You are going!
Bournemouth international centre is  getting Chris Rock! The whole of the
UK should be happy about my divorce!  You are doing North America,
Ireland? Yes. Israel. I am all over  the world. Whenever they will have
jokes... We are there. Japan! You  discuss your divorce a little bit
was Mike yes, I'm going to Japan!  You should try Margate when you are
here! I will do your backyard!  Anywhere! I am broke, Idris, broke!
As you travel, when you go to  Bournemouth, will you make a
reference to a weird fish and chip  shop outside? I do a little
homework. Did the Mayor sleep with  anybody? What is the popular street
or hotel. You have to insert all of  that stuff into the act. With
standard, I have so much admiration  for standard because it must be so
utterly terrifying... Is there shall  be reconstructed or did you find
yourself improvising more than you  thought you might? It depends on the
night, in some places the audiences  give back so much and you run with
it but others... Were almost doing a  play! Do you think sometimes, shit,
I have a really... I had a very  weird one in Perth in Australia. OK!
I have to use all of my Spidey  senses tonight! But the humour is
different? Pop culture changes from  city to city but when you talk about
relationships between men and women,  it is exactly the same. Nothing
changes. All over the world. When it  comes to your work ethic, you have a
great attitude, did you say, people  say you are so rich but you have
always had more money than your  friends? Yes because I always worked
harder than my friends, I was always  cleaning more yards or painting more
offences, I have been rich my whole  life! You also did not mind doing
the terrible jobs? No, I was not  good-looking so it helped to have
money! Eventually they will come  around! Tell us about Eddie Murphy.
The story of Eddie Murphy changing  your life. My favourite Eddie Murphy
story, Eddie Murphy discovered me.  When I met Eddie Murphy it was like,
the early 90s, the late 80s. Not  Doctor Doolittle, the man with the
leather suit. I was at a club and  Donald Trump was at this club! I am
telling the truth, Donald Trump was  at the club, it was me, Eddie
Murphy, Donald Trump, and I was not  famous, I was like the kid hanging
around the gangsters. And this girl  says to Eddie Murphy, I love you so
much, it was a white girl, I have  never guessed a black man in my
life, can I please guess you?  Please! I just want to be able to
say I kissed a black man. And Eddie  Murphy has a huge entourage of 30
people and he goes, OK, let us get  this straight, he cannot start at
the top, you have to guess some of  these broke niggers first! Bart's
Eddie Murphy, funny guy! -- that is  Eddie Murphy. When did you do the DJ
work? Before I was a stand-up, I am  from New York and that is what we
did back then, we were disciples of  Grandmaster Flash and all of these
guys, we would watch the DJs and we  would pool money and get equipment
and we would play block parties. And  we would broke niggers -- rap.
Somebody shows pictures of you DJ  in, you are looking like the ball
boy at Wimbledon! It does not  suggest cool! You are great looking
kid! DJ...? DJ Dris? I did that to  science... I do Dris when I am in
bars, wrapping, but mainly Idris  Elba! Everybody was Gary Dempsey at
one point! Everybody loved a bit of  that! Kate, what was your DJ name?
Frilly knickers! It definitely was  not. I have never had a DJ name and
I have never heard you. You have to  invite me! I will! Really good.
Amazingly, we must also mention...  It is a 20th anniversary of Titanic!
20 years!  APPLAUSE.
In my head, that is a new release!  Yes, 20 years, I am old, 42! I had
my 21st birthday on that shoot. I  remember the amount of cake that I
bet. 20 years later, the love for  those characters is still so
intense. Tell us about the auction,  the dinner with yourself and
Leonardo? Recently, back in July, I  was doing some fundraising for a
cancer sufferer who desperately  needed life-saving treatment and I
was so desperately trying anything  and I called Leo and I said, can we
do dinner with Jack and Rose, how  can I pull this off? He said, we
will do better, and his foundation,  which is completely unbelievable, he
has an annual fundraiser in St  Tropez and I said we will auction
Jack and Rose for dinner. And we  will make those funds. And I thought
that would be incredible. And we  raised $1.35 million.
APPLAUSE.  That is amazing! The Evening
Standard so quickly, it suddenly  happened and I could night -- could
not quite work things out, we ended  up selling three separate dinners.
What can I say? Did that include the  tip? It does include a life jacket.
James Cameron very kindly... I  called him and I said can you send
us a life jacket and he did, he sent  us a life jacket and we need another
two! Jack and Rose and a life  jacket! You make it sound like a
bargain! It sounds so lovely,  because the friendship between you
and Leonardo DiCaprio, it is real?  It is not just show business, you
went through so much? It really is  like family, jolly lucky to have
such an amazing friend. Such a  namedropper! He is probably so
completely sick of it! I love Leo!  Did you do Titanic material? No! I
don't do it now, I loved Titanic. It  was amazing! I was actually in the
land! I played the violin! -- in the  band. We must mention another film
viewers, this is Woody Allen's  latest film. I am in that, also! It
is a period piece. It is set in 1950  in Coney Island and I play Jenny,
she is an oyster bar waitress with a  lot of regrets in her life and is on
her second marriage, living a life  she never imagined she would, her
young son is apparent maniac and she  meets and falls in love with Mickey,
the lifeguard, played by Justin  Timberlake, and he also meets my
stepdaughter, aged 22, younger and  wittier, and it starts to make for a
rather strange and terrible things.  Woody Allen, he makes these movies,
he makes them and it's for quite a  low budget. Yes, they are very low
budget which is quite hilarious.  What happens, you end up sharing
trailers. I shared a trailer with  Justin Timberlake. It's a very hard
life! And I was sent up a mountain  with Idris Elba! Anyone else? There
was a tiny thin bit of plasterboard  partitioning between the different
ends of this small trailer. I would  take my own cattle in each day. I
would hear him weeing each morning.  "Morning, Justin Timberlake." And he
starts singing and then I think, I  quite like my life. Very cool. I
don't think you're supposed to talk  through the partition, you're
supposed to pretend it's solid. I  know! I heard everything! We've got
a clip, Woody Allen chose it and  send it to us because the film comes
out later this year. I knew I'd find  you here, why aren't you in school?
I wanted to see this picture. You  can't not go to school. Jesus,
Ritchie, this is why you're in  summer school. I don't like school.
Doesn't matter if you don't like it.  I don't like waiting on tables. Some
things you have to do whether you  like it or not. I want to watch the
picture. Where did you get the  money? I'd took 20 cents out of his
pants when he was asleep. You stole  from your father? He's not my father
and I hate him! Don't say that! He's  a good person. Why does he hit you?
He doesn't hit me. When he gets  drunk he hits everybody but he
hardly drink is any more. -- hardly  drinks.
Right, it's time to meet our  musical guest tonight.
With his bands Oasis and Beady Eye,  this Britpop legend became one
of the most iconic frontmen  of all time.
Here performing For What It's Worth  from his debut solo
album, As You Were -  it's Liam Gallagher!
# In my defence all my  intentions were good.
# And heaven holds a place somewhere  for the misunderstood.
# You know I'd give  you blood if it'd be enough.
# Devils on my doorstep  since the day I was born.
# It's hard to find a sunset  in the eye of a storm.
# But I am a dreamer  by design and I know in time
# For what it's worth  I'm sorry for the hurt.
# I'll be the first to say I've  made my own mistakes.
# For what it's worth I know it's  just the word and words betray.
# Behind the lens is  a poison picture you paint.
# And let's not pretend  you were ever searching for saints.
# Cause I've been crucified  for just being alive.
# Somewhere in the crossfire  of this whispering war.
# Seems that I forgot just  what I was fighting for.
# But underneath my skin there's  a fire within still burning.
# For what it's worth  I'm sorry for the hurt.
# I'll be the first to say I've  made my own mistakes.
# For what it's worth I know it's  just the word and words betray.
# The first bird to fly  gets all the arrows.
# Let's leave the past behind  with all our sorrows.
# I'll build a bridge between us  and I'll swallow my pride.
# For what it's worth  I'm sorry for the hurt.
# I'll be the first to say I've  made my own mistakes.
# For what it's worth I know it's  just the word and words betray.
Thank you. The mighty Liam  Gallagher. Come on over, sir. Just
you. Liam Gallagher, hello. There  you go. You know everyone. Very
good. Sit down. Well done, sir.  Congratulations. On the what? Your
new record! It's not out yet but  it's all right. I'm doing what I do,
know what I mean? In television  world it's true, the album is out
today. Oh, yeah is out today, yeah.  LAUGHTER
You can colour it in. You get a  colouring that. You can just colour
it in. It's something you said you'd  never do, a solo album. Yeah because
I prefer to be in a band, know what  I mean? It's better when you're with
the lads, even though they are over  there. Now I've got to do all of
this chatting! He's a god, kind of  thing. It's nice to be making music,
that's for sure. On the tour you are  going to be back in the band. Yeah.
How quickly do the tourists sell  out? I think it was about maybe an
hour -- the tours. As real good. Not  as fast as yours. The American one
is still going. You keep all of the  money, huh? Yeah, got a lot of
outtakes, know what I mean. Got to  play a lot of bills.
Making the record, here tonight you  got the strings. What have you got
against saxophones? They're is a bit  creepy, a bit dim Faye, I think. You
know something's going down. -- a  bit pervy. Somebody got it out and I
said, put it away, mate. He said, it  will sound like a guitar and I said,
there a guitar over there, and it  sounds like a guitar. I find it a
bit odd. So, there are no saxophones  on the record. No saxophones.
Liam, you and Twitter...  Why do you stay on Twitter?
I like winding people up, man.  Without a doubt, man.
You really do.  Without a doubt.
That's what it's about.  Know what I mean?
Everyone's a bit square  at the moment, aren't they?
Everyone is a little bit  serious and miserable.
Know what I mean?  I do like winding people up.
And I can take it, I do  like a wind-up back.
But it's a bit...  A lot of these rock and roll stars
these days are coming  and just getting the cheque.
Imagine Keith Moon drumming his arse  off and then going home.
You boot a few things  and that, don't you?
Know what I mean?  And the tweets...
Some of them are a little bit out  of order and I do apologise.
But...  You know?
A bit?  There was a time recently
when you were hacked.  It's still going on, that.
There's a police investigation.  But previously...
LAUGHTER.  You had tweeted Noel.
And I remember, how real is that?  Is that a game?
And then you slap each other  on Twitter and then you phone each
other up and have a laugh?  No.
That's well for real, man.  Is it really?
We don't like each other, man.  A lot of people think we're waiting
around for a few more noughts  on the end but they've already
offered us loads of money.  Like millions and millions.
It's not about the money, is it?  Know what I mean?
Yeah.  The age gap is five years. When your
kids, five years is a big age gap.  It started off come he bought a
stereo once, he was working and I  had my first drink and I got up in
the middle of the night and he had  his sound system. I was looking for
the lights, my head was spinning and  I thought, I can't find the lights,
and I thought fuck it, and I'll piss  here and I tempt WWE all over his
set. That's where it started -- and  I pissed all over his set. I said,
it could have been worse, it could  have been in your mouth. Got away
lightly, I think.  Me and Liam have squared away.
Only for ten minutes.  Because you threw my
hat across a bar.  No, you started it.
He got excited.  Did Liam piss in your hat, Idris?
He gave a feel of my hair.  No, I didn't.
I gave him a hug.  He didn't like that
because he loves his hair.  And then he took my hat off.
So we had a little bit of...  But we're all good, now.
Great!  We'll leave it there!
Thank you so much, Liam Gallagher.  Good luck with the record and the
tour. The, stay. -- Liam. We're  still on the telly! We've got to go
to the weather and the local news  now.
Right, that's nearly it,  but before we go, just time
for a visit to the big red chair.  Who is there? What's your name?
Rosamond. Where are you from? New  Zealand. Oh, New Zealand. Do you
live here? Yes, just moved here.  What are you going to do? I work in
recruitment and HR. Goodness, that's  quite dull! A couple of years ago
when I was at university with my  boyfriend he was doing a paper where
he had to wear a heart monitor for  the weekend. He stayed in and I went
out, I came home at 4am, as you do,  I woke him up... We knew where that
was going, didn't we? He'd been  shagging someone else because the
heart monitor would have gone up.  No, Liam, no. Its choices and
consequences. You chose to flip her,  and now look. We're dying to hear
the rest of her story. Can I go now?  No, said! -- sit. Who is next?
Hello. No, it's too late, that was  Chris Rock! Concentrate, everybody.
Hello. What's your name? Surely.  What do you do? I'm a beauty
therapist. In London? Yes. Lovely.  I'm from Malaysian. How long have
you been here? 20 years. You must be  good at beauty therapy? I'm all
right. A ringing endorsement! On you  go. OK, I went to a yoga class one
day with my new sports bra top,  which is a light blue colour. I'm
feeling good about myself, 20  minutes later I go into the class
and I look at the reflection and the  top has turned into deep blue
instead of light blue in a  particular area, on the nipples,
which is when I realised that they  don't have any glands and there is
no sweat. I've panicked, I started  rubbing it hopefully to blend in the
sweat but it actually got worse, so  the nipple turned hard. LAUGHTER
I had two direct nipples. That was  the longest yoga class ever! We love
her even more!  Well done, everyone.
If you'd like to join us on the show  and have a go in the red chair,
you can contact us via our website  at this address.
That's it for tonight.  Please say thank you to my guests.
Liam Gallagher.  Chris Rock.
Idris Elba.  And Kate Winslet.
Join me next week with pop star  Niall Horan, comedian Matt Lucas,
Breaking Bad's Bryan Cranston,  Hollywood stars Colin Farrell
and Nicole Kidman and,  for the first time, the legendary
Jane Fonda!  I'll see you then!
Goodnight.