This programme contains
some strong language.
Good evening, everyone -
my name is Tom Cruise, and you're
watching The Graham Norton Show!
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
Oh, oh, oh!
For me? Too much!
Hello everybody, hello and welcome.
We're very excited, yes  -
Tom Cruise is here.
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
Tom is taking a break from filming
Mission: Impossible 6 to come along
with some of his co-stars
for a chat.
Of course, in the films,
Tom's elite band of secret
agents take on jobs that
seem utterly impossible.
Utterly impossible,
like, I don't know...
Persuading a Ukip leader to resign.
That kind of thing.
LAUGHTER
Beating Ant and Dec
at the National Television Awards.
That sort of thing.
Mind you, sometimes
the impossible can happen.
Can you believe, Donald Trump has
been American President
for a whole year?!
AUDIENCE OOOHS
It seems longer, doesn't it?
Were there more months
in this last year?
LAUGHTER
Were there extra months?
It's also Donald Trump's 13th
wedding anniversary.
Thirteen years!
Unlucky for some!
It certainly is for Melania.
Here are the happy couple.
LAUGHTER
That's just lovely...
The traditional gift for a 13th
wedding anniversary is lace.
I think you can tell
what Melania's thinking.
"Please God, a tablecloth,
not lingerie".
On the subject of happy couples,
congratulations to Princess Eugenie
who got engaged this week.
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
It's a good thing, it's happy news!
Yay!
Her boyfriend Jack proposed
to her while they were on holiday.
Doesn't really narrow it down.
LAUGHTER
"Is this a holiday?"
"Yes, this is a holiday."
Though, to be fair, it is the third
most exciting piece of Royal news
since Harry's engagement,
and Prince William shaving his head.
LAUGHTER
I think it looks great.
No, it looks good.
And his kids can have fun painting
it in time for Easter.
LAUGHTER
I believe that's called
a 'number one all-over',
that's what that's called.
Which, co-incidentally,
was what Donald Trump wanted
for an anniversary present.
LAUGHTER
It's clever, it's clever!
APPLAUSE
Let's get some guests on!
Later we'll have music and chat
from chart-topping Paloma Faith...
CHEERING
But first -
he's one of our most successful
comic exports with cult hits Spaced,
Shaun of the Dead and Hot Fuzz,
now he's Hollywood's hottest geek -
please welcome Simon Pegg everybody!
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
There he is.
Hello!
Suited and booted.
Lovely.
From the Man of Steel
to the Man from UNCLE,
he's the hottest thing to come out
of Jersey - is it a bird,
is it a plane..?
No, it's Henry Cavill!
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
Here he is!
Hello, Henry.
Have a seat.
You know him.
This Swedish actress is fast making
a name for herself in films
such as Girl on a Train,
Florence Foster Jenkins
and The Greatest Showman -
it's a first-time welcome to Rebecca
Ferguson!
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
Lovely to see you!
Welcome, welcome, have a seat.
And he's a true Hollywood great,
and a man on a mission...
Please welcome our
favourite Top Gun...
It is Mr Tom Cruise!
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
MISSION IMPOSSIBLE THEME TUNE PLAYS
Good to see you.
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
Hi, man.
Very nice, very nice,
professional, professional,
pretending not to know them at all!
So this is weird.
We've never had this before,
people who are actually making
the movie that they've come
on to talk about.
We shout all day.
Were you all on set today?
We've been at work today.
All of us were on set filming.
What were you doing,
running or talking?
LAUGHTER
Personally, I injected a man
in the neck with a traquiliser,
put him in prison and got kicked
in the head by Henry,
and that was my day.
That sounds like more than a day.
So Henry, we know what you did.
I kicked him in the head.
Very good.
That wasn't on camera!
No, no that wasn't work,
that was in the trailers.
Rebecca, were you on today?
Oh, yes.
I actually, I'm going to stand up.
I had this pose today
with a semiautomatic rifle,
with my belly like this.
Shooting bad guys.
Six months pregnant.
I'm glad you said that because I
wasn't going to say anything!
Six months pregnant!
That's what gets men in trouble.
You're six months pregnant?
I am, I don't know what happened.
I could guess!
Six months ago, yes.
What were you doing today?
I was just shooting
guns and having fun.
Stuff.
Stuff, shooting guns.
Where are you, are
you nearly finished?
I don't know.
Are we?
We hope so.
You've been filming
since when, last year?
Last March or April?
Yeah, last year.
So nearly a year, you must
be nearly finished.
Because I broke my ankle,
we had to shut down completely.
Now...
We are about six weeks away.
The ankle...
Are you fully recovered,
are you well?
It still broken but I'm doing well.
You're kidding, is it still broken?
Yeah, it's not fully
healed but we're shooting.
But that's nuts.
We've seen a picture,
you're running and doing
all the stuff again.
Now...
We have a release date,
so we've got to keep going.
Yeah, otherwise you'll
end up going live.
Yes.
On the night.
LAUGHTER
Much better,
it's much better.
So, you probably, I'm sure
you all saw the footage.
It was in the papers
and online, of the accident.
Yes.
I think we all kind of thought, how
did you break an ankle doing that?
It looked like you should
have broken your jaw
or something like that.
I know, everyone said
that was the stunt.
I mean, I'm going to run
across and hit the side of the wall
and then pull myself over.
That wasn't the mistake.
So you were always meant
to not land on the roof.
Yes, always.
OK, so what you've done,
you've brought us some footage.
I think this is so cool to see this
from a different angle.
I can't watch this!
I haven't watched it yet.
Most of it's fine,
there's one clip...
I will warn you, it's
not for the squeamish.
Gross!
You see I'm wearing two wires,
they're basically just safety wires
because I go at full tilt and I'm
sprinting as hard as I can and I hit
the side of the wall
and that's the stunt.
I hit the side of the wall and then
I'm chasing after Henry, actually.
LAUGHTER
All his fault.
All his fault, I blame him.
I hit the side of the wall
and then I climb up
on the wall and I'm supposed
to run past camera.
OK.
This is the shot from behind you.
Yes.
You see the speed and the momentum
of the run, and it's in London.
There we go.
So it keeping me up.
Here he goes, look at that.
AUDIENCE GASPS.
Now...
It's good noise of the body.
But you get my point,
you think how did you break a leg?
Let's look at it from the side.
This is from the side.
Oh, no!
This isn't a bad one,
this isn't a bad one, Rebecca.
This is from the side.
Here we go.
We shot it with three cameras.
OK.
Here he goes, and boom!
AUDIENCE GASPS.
Now we've got the camera
which focuses on the foot.
Now, if you are squeamish...
Don't watch!
Don't watch this.
Si still hasn't seen!
LAUGHTER
They keep trying to show it
to me and I'm like...
No!
I mean, a bone doesn't pop out
or anything but it is an odd angle
for anyone's foot to be in.
Nobody's foot should
ever have to do this.
Yeah, ever.
Oh my gosh.
Jumps at speed, that momentum...
Here we go.
Watch that.
Watch this.
Do it again!
LAUGHTER
But here, here is why,
here is why Tom Cruise gets
paid the big bucks, OK?
Because this is it from
the front angle, OK?
So you've just seen what happened
to his foot, now watch this.
I knew I broke it instantly.
So you're down.
Anyone else would go,
"Well, that's over".
No.
Up he gets, up he gets,
and he's running.
APPLAUSE
I didn't want to do it again.
No.
I didn't want to do it again
and I knew instantly it was broken.
Run past camera, got
the shot, it's in the movie.
That profile shot, both our
shots were in the movie.
And Henry...
Everyone said when you got up
and ran out of shot,
"Oh, that's so him!"
To complete the shot like with your
foot hanging off, that's so him!
LAUGHTER
I just went and said,
sorry guys, it's broken.
Take me to the hospital,
it's broken.
That's a wrap.
Everyone, the crew got
on the phone and made
their vacation arrangements.
I made a baby.
LAUGHTER
We had six months
at least, I thought.
I told you it would be six
months, I told you that!
And when this film finally
ends, Henry Cavill...
LAUGHTER
We are going to miss each other.
But Henry, you're probably not
going to miss your face furniture.
You're not fond of the face
furniture, are you?
It's not that I'm not fond
of it, it's just that...
Look at that.
If I'm walking past schools,
people give me funny looks.
LAUGHTER
And it's tough to buy vans.
Can't give children sweeties.
Because you normally do that a lot!
LAUGHTER
If you hang out the park
long enough, why not?
Hey guys, I'm Superman,
come and get some sweets!
I'm not a stranger, I'm Superman!
LAUGHTER
I think he rocks it,
very few men can carry that off.
It's very good, but you know what's
annoying about that?
That's like if Henry Cavill wore
a stupid hat, you would think oh,
that stupid hat looks really
good on him!
And it is not that.
He looks really good and if you put
it on, it's a stupid hat.
But now Simon, this is your fourth
Mission Impossible?
It is, yeah.
You've been working with Tom
for what, over ten years now?
12 years.
We worked it out
yesterday, didn't we?
Oh, wow.
It's 12 years this year.
So you know each other very well?
Pretty well.
We've been in the
trenches a long time.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
So do you forget that
it's Tom Cruise?
Yes and no.
You kind of like...
On a day-to-day basis,
we're working and we're friends
and it's fun and it's a job,
but when we're out doing press
or whatever, I see Tom become Tom,
the Tom people know.
Like I've seen Tom
become Tom Cruise.
LAUGHTER
Which is amazing.
What does that mean?
Is he Tom Cruise now,
is this Tom Cruise?
He smiles.
Like when we were shooting in Paris,
we'll be doing a scene
and then he'll just go,
hey, how you going?
That's Tom becoming Tom,
because he's very, very
good with his fans.
I remember that night in Vienna
when we were doing a recce,
looking round and it took about ten
minutes for 100 people
to be around us.
He was so good with them,
just waving and smiling.
I'd be punching...
Spitting.
No you wouldn't, Simon.
That's very nice, thank you.
You did it for my sister
as well, I think.
You do that thing where you just
become maverick, you just smile.
LAUGHTER That's Tom
Cruise right there.
It is, that's him.
There he is.
I told you he was here!
Here is an odd thing,
because Rebecca, your mother,
is she famous in Sweden?
She is famous in Sweden?
Well, no, she is not
famous but she hung a lot
with the avant-garde cool people
like Abba back in the day.
Those avant-garde Abba people.
LAUGHTER
They finally went
mainstream, they really sold out...
But she worked with
Abba, didn't she?
So what she did was...
Do you know this?
This is good, I didn't know this.
No she did.
I think she was dating a man called
Ron Spaulding and he took
all of their cover images
of their LPs.
Actually she is on one
of the covers, which
you apparently have.
I do.
So we all know this album,
don't we ladies and gentlemen?
Abba, there they are in the back
of the car drinking.
We turn it around.
We turn it around, now, which one
of these people is your mother?
If I do this, can you
see the similarities?
Oh, yes.
Here we go.
Rebecca Ferguson's mother's
legs on an Abba album,
ladies and gentlemen!
APPLAUSE
Beautiful!
And she helped to actually,
not translate, but she went
through all of the lyrics in Swedish
and helped rewrite them
to English, Waterloo.
Really?
So if there's any
mistakes it's her fault.
In fairness, it does make no sense
but bless other trying!
So listen, the new Mission
Impossible, it won't be coming out
until the 26th of July.
Before then, the trailer's
being released...
Super Bowl.
February, is that the fourth?
The fourth, Super Bowl,
we going to have a little 30 second
spot and then it's going to send
everyone to the Internet
and out in the theatres.
And you've just announced
the actual title.
Mission: Impossible - Fallout.
Fallout?
Fallout!
Fallout, yes!
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
So we now know the title.
Yes.
Do we know anything else about it?
No.
You know it's a kind of,
it really is a story of...
It takes into account
all the Mission Impossibles,
really, and it is a fallout
of all the things that we did
in the early Mission Impossibles.
Ethan in particular, yeah.
Well, it's kind of the good
things that we've done
and they're using it
now against us.
OK.
And obviously there's
familiar faces?
Henry's an antagonist,
the primary antagonist in the film.
Is that posh for a baddie?
Well...
I would say you have Lane who's
the baddie, Sean Harris.
He's coming back from Rogue Nation.
Oh, OK.
And we have Michelle Monaghan
and Angela Bassett, Vanessa Kirby.
Ving Rhames, of course, is back.
Yeah, yeah.
And you're back as Faust.
Forget those other
people, I'm back again.
And Benji Dunn is back.
Yes, of course.
Do you have a name, Henry?
Do I have a name?
Yes.
August Walker.
Oooh.
You had to be a villain.
Say it again.
I didn't know it was August
until about halfway
through the movie, though.
I was just referred to as Walker,
and I was like, I saw the chair,
and I was like, hold on a second.
My first name's August?
LAUGHTER.
And McQ was like, yes.
Chris McQuarrie, who's
writer-director and kind
of creative partner of mine,
and it's his second
Mission he is directing.
Mission: Impossible, obviously,
you pays your money.
You want the big, big stunts.
Now, last time you watch
on the show, you were kind
of hinting at this big set piece
in this movie that you
spent years preparing.
Yes.
So I think you can tell us a bit
more about it now, right?
Now I can tell you a bit more.
I spent really two years,
McQ and I were talking
about a sequence, and it's an aerial
sequence with helicopter.
And I've wanted, I've studied many
different films, and...
So I went and I got my helicopter
licence, and we are flying...
One second there.
I was surprised you didn't
have a helicopter licence already.
I'm sorry.
When they were telling me,
and they said, and he got
his helicopter licence.
Really?
I'm sure I've seen him
flying helicopters before!
Were you flying without
a licence previously?
Yes!
Not to get you in
trouble or anything.
Oh, were you?
Yes.
So no wonder you got it quickly.
I know, very fast.
OK, so you get the licence.
Yes, and then we just started really
working the sequence to see,
what can we do practically.
I mean, I think in terms of action,
this is probably the largest
practical action film ever shot.
Like when you look at
the film, there is no CGI.
So we are going through Paris,
the motorcycle, it is just
full on, cars, you know,
we are all doing our own stunts.
And the helicopter sequence is just
incredibly exhilarating
and very dangerous.
So there's really only one country
that would allow us to do it,
where we had to build special camera
rigs for the helicopter.
So I got my licence, and we just,
I trained up on aerobatics.
And it's different.
I fly aerobatics in aeroplanes,
but helicopters are very different.
So we are flying very low,
very close to rock faces,
and a chase, and I'm chasing
Henry into sequence.
And we've got some
pictures of it here.
So that's you.
Is this the end of the sequence
or the beginning?
I think we've got these pictures
the wrong way round.
No, it's...
I can't tell you that right now.
OK.
Well I just think this
might be out of...
Henry is hanging out
of the helicopter.
There is Henry back there.
He is hanging out.
He's not even flying a helicopter!
Really!
That's totally ruined my bit.
Because we are doing aerobatics.
At least I know my
own fate, you know?
He was there at times...
I was on his tail, like a foot
of his tail rotor at times.
He had no idea.
There were times when I genuinely
thought, I was like, OK,
this is how it goes.
But at least I get
killed by Tom Cruise.
It'll make the papers.
Henry's lucky, because he can
actually fly anyway.
Yes, of course.
LAUGHTER.
APPLAUSE.
So here you are flying.
I'm guessing that must be
after this next bit,
because this next picture,
you're on the outside.
So someone must be
flying that helicopter.
It can't be...
Please tell me you didn't get out
of a helicopter while it was going?
So that's you.
And that is you, hanging
off a helicopter.
Yeah.
But this next picture, one,
it is just a beautiful picture.
But it's crazy.
So that's you.
Yes.
I mean, that's...
I know, right?
I can tell by this
you're quite high.
We were on the ground that day.
We're the ball, hanging underneath.
The rest of the cast!
And because, you know,
Tom does all this stuff.
Does that mean that you guys have
to say yes to everything?
Fucking hell, yeah!
LAUGHTER.
They want to.
They can't wait.
You can't get these guys
out of the stunt room.
Do you know what?
You can't.
Henry's like in the helicopter.
He is loving it.
You were freezing
in that helicopter.
Oh, helicopter's cold, yeah.
It's New Zealand winter,
and the doors were open.
You posted a picture
on your Instagram of you doing
a stunt which looks very painful.
I think it's you being lowered down
a cliff by your nipples.
LAUGHTER.
That's his holiday.
I don't know how they wrote
that into the script.
That's not in the script.
I love the stiff neck and the thumb.
I'm fine!
It's one of those moments
where you're being lowered off
this 1800-foot cliff.
A very famous one.
Yeah, one of those moments.
As you do.
I know I'm perfectly safe,
because the stunt crew
is absolutely fantastic.
The Eastwood team is really good,
and you trust the harness
and they've all triple checked
everything.
But it's still 1800 foot and you're
walking off backwards.
And they're not doing it.
It's so high, and the boats
at the bottom in the fjord
are about this big.
That it looks like a painting.
And so you lose all sense
of like fear and adrenaline
for the height, and you start
thinking, if I were to fall,
could I like squirrel suit with my,
and make it all the way
to the water, maybe just like skim.
You've been in Superman too much!
It's got to you.
And Rebecca Ferguson, obviously,
you know, with child now,
so that makes stunts harder.
But even when you did the last
movie, you seemed quite unsuited.
You did suffer from
vertigo going into these?
Oh, yeah.
I mean, that is a bizarre thing,
to say yes to being
in one of these films.
Well, I didn't really know
what I was saying yes to.
OK.
Because I didn't really know how
these films were made.
You know, when I was
on a camel in the desert...
We explained it to you!
Very quickly!
And then the first day of shooting,
Tom, what did we do?
We jumped off a building.
Yeah.
The first day of shooting.
I think we've got a picture of you.
So that's...
That's me swearing and shouting
the naughtiest words ever.
In my ear.
In your ear.
"I'm so sorry!"
"Swear, swear, swear."
"Did I say that?"
"I'm so sorry, I apologise,
I'm just so f..."
The worst words ever.
And then we jumped off,
and he just looks at me
in the Tom Cruise kind of way,
and he goes, "Welcome to Mission."
LAUGHTER.
I don't remember saying that.
I do not remember saying that.
No way!
That is way too cheesy.
I would never say that.
You said it to all of us!
I remember my special day, too.
Now, normally, ladies and gentlemen,
on a show like this,
we would show a clip of Mission:
Impossible.
But you haven't
finished the film yet.
I'm sorry.
So it's not going to happen.
So we thought we'd make
a snatch of one of our own.
One of the most iconic stunts that
you do, Tom, is the running away
from something exploding.
You're very good at it.
Thank you.
We've got some stills.
Running away from a van.
That's in the Channel Tunnel there.
This is the exploding
fish tank, there you go.
Do you know, I've just noticed.
That's a very good move.
I like that.
Touchdown.
Score!
That is very good.
And presumably timing is key,
because these are real explosions.
They are real explosions.
That one was particularly
very crazy.
Was this the one where no one
properly told you the timing?
Yeah, the guy was over there,
and he said, OK, we're
going to go on three.
And he started going, three, two...
And I said, wait, stop!
We have an explosion
that is going to go over my head.
And I said, you just said on three.
He said, I meant three.
What does that mean?
I said, everyone, just please.
It was like two in the morning
and he's setting it up
and there is glass and just
tonnes of water.
He said, well, I'm going
to go, three, two, one.
And I said, do I go
then, do I go on one?
Like, when do I go?
Are you going to push
the button on one?
It was, you know.
He kind of looked at me like...
I don't know.
I'm not sure.
Around then!
Just go.
Just run!
When you hear the
explosion, just go!
You really ought to run,
because it's very dangerous!
It's very dangerous,
I'd run really fast if I were you.
If I was you,
I wouldn't hang around.
Well, what we've done is,
we've got a green screen here,
so we can raise up the green screen
at great speed.
LAUGHTER.
APPLAUSE.
While we're waiting for that,
we're going to get some members
of the audience to do this.
But in terms of this, Tom,
what they're going to do...
They're going to start back there.
They're going to run to here,
and then what have they got to get,
height and presumably facial
expression?
So in terms of jumping,
what's the best way to get height?
Are they going to land on the mats?
That's the idea.
First of all, watch
your ankle on the mat.
He knows this.
He knows this!
Let's get people to do this.
We'll get to you.
Now, who wants to do it?
You want to do it?
What's your name?
Jamie.
This is Jamie.
He's not going well.
Watch your ankle!
Come this way.
You shouldn't let him do it,
he fell off the step!
Up you go.
So, Tom, tips for Jamie.
What sort of facial
expression should he go for?
Just whatever feels natural.
The most important thing is,
don't get blown up.
So I'm trying not to get blown up?
Yes!
I'm escaping.
You're escaping, but you're brave.
He's brave.
You can't look terrified.
You're frightened,
but you're still brave.
I'm not going to go too high?
I'll do it for you!
I like that.
I'm not going to go too high!
Do what you feel comfortable.
So, what's the countdown?
Is it three, two, one?
Three, two, one, go!
OK.
So you're going on one.
On three.
What?
Three.
No, one!
You do it, Simon.
OK, here we go, Jamie.
Three, two, one, go!
That was good, Jamie!
Excellent.
That was very good.
OK, well done, Jamie.
Shall we see it?
Have a seat.
Let's see it.
He's running, he's running...
He looked like he was loving it!
Loving life!
Do we have a woman
who'd like to do it?
You'd like to do it?
Here you go.
Are you all right in that dress?
Yeah, it's fine.
What's your name?
Maddie.
OK, here comes Maddie.
Now, so, you saw Jamie.
So it's very important that
you just piss all over that.
LAUGHTER.
So women just do it
the same, right, Rebecca?
Yes, we do.
And think up, OK?
I want you to think up.
We're looking for elevation.
And relax your face.
Jamie was like a stone.
One thing Jamie did,
which you saw in the playback,
was it looked like Jamie did
a really big fart.
That exploded.
Don't do that.
OK, here goes Maddie.
Three, two, one, go!
APPLAUSE.
Oh, that's going to be good.
Well done.
Have a seat.
They're not nice like you.
Here's Maddie.
Super cool Maddie!
Shall we do one more?
One more.
Let's get someone.
You'd like to do it?
Oh, you'd be so good at it.
Come on, have a go.
What's your name?
Evelyn.
OK.
They're rooting for you, Evelyn.
Can I just say, you're OK?
You're fit?
Yes!
OK.
Right now, you're fit?
At the moment, you're OK.
You've seen the others.
I think the important thing is,
particularly because you look
so beautiful, big face
at the end, OK?
So we're looking for
height here, Evelyn.
Height and then forward.
OK?
You're good.
OK.
This is Evelyn going for it.
Three, two, one, go!
Well done, Evelyn!
Well done, that woman.
Are you all right?
There we go.
Let's have a look.
Let's watch Evelyn.
Here she goes, here she goes!
I fear she may not be
in Mission: Impossible 7.
Which is a lovely day out
at the dynamite factory.
Oh, dear.
Now, Henry, this is your first
film with Tom Cruise.
But it wasn't meant to be.
You were supposed to be in another
film with Tom Cruise?
Well, we had the opportunity, yes.
The Man From Uncle.
Originally, Tom was
playing Napoleon Solo.
And I auditioned for Armie Hammer's
role, Illya Kuryakin.
And I went to Tom's house in LA,
which is very surreal, by the way,
when you're trying to make things
work in your career,
and you get in a taxi in LA,
and you feel like saying,
"Take me to Tom Cruise's house."
But you give them an address,
and you turn up, and there's
big gates everywhere.
And it's obviously a nice area.
I imagine it's nice.
Garden's nice, he
keeps it nice, yeah.
That lawn is cut, yeah.
The hanging baskets, gorgeous.
Yeah, I got to meet Tom then
and we went through some lines
with Guy Richie at his house,
and it was still just very
surreal for me, thinking...
"I'm sitting here with
Guy Richie and Tom Cruise,
in Tom Cruise's house".
Yeah.
Like, when will I stop sweating?!
LAUGHTER
I'm leaving stains!
But then you got
the Tom Cruise role.
Man from UNCLE, Mission Impossible,
two big franchises.
You've talked to us before about how
close the James Bond thing came,
that you are down to the final two,
but I like the thing you did then
when you got your first
kind of big paycheque,
with your dad.
Oh, yeah.
When I got my first big paycheque,
it had been a few years,
I'd been working as an actor
for a few years.
How much was it?
LAUGHTER
Don't ask and that!
I'm joking.
That's so Swedish!
Sort of 300.
Pounds.
So I went back to Jersey
with my dad and I thought,
I want to treat myself,
you know, I haven't actually
got myself anything.
We were discussing what to do
with it and he said how about a car?
I was still driving my Peugeot 206,
the first car I ever
had and I was like...
It's time to upgrade this thing,
it struggles uphill at this stage.
Yeah.
Went to the local fancy garage
and there was a number of nice cars
there and the Audi R8,
which was one that
really stood out to me.
I thought this is a great car.
I was looking at it.
My dad was sort of pausing
around this other car,
in the really nice section.
I was like, what are
you doing over there?
He said, I was looking at this car.
I was like, wow,
this is really nice.
Yeah, one day.
And he went, "hmmm".
LAUGHTER
And I said
what do you mean.
He went, well, I'm sure
we can make this work.
I was like, it's an Aston Martin
DBS, you can't just make this work.
You can't toy with my emotions
like that, you either cannot come.
He was like, well, you know, yeah,
yeah I think it could be a thing.
Think about it, think
about what car you want.
They're two different cars.
I was like, I'm not thinking
about anything, that's
an Aston Martin DBS.
And so that was my second car.
Wow.
That's quite a trajectory.
Now I'm thinking, though,
does it stay on Jersey,
so your dad gets to drive it
all the time?
I've now forbade him
from driving at.
Oh, OK.
A couple of near scrapes.
Oh.
But it does actually
stay on Jersey, yes.
But I do like this idea,
because everyone struggles
and then suddenly, oh,
I've got a bit of money,
what am I going to do
with my first big paycheque?
Rebecca, do you remember
what you did with yours?
I bought...
Oh God, I wish it were
something more cool.
I bought a pair of Dior
sunglasses and then they got
stolen the day after,
but they left the case.
LAUGHTER
I like...
I bought an Aston Martin.
I bought some sunglasses.
But they were really nice.
Tom Cruise, do you remember
what you did with your first cheque,
where you noticed you had to money
in the bank?
Yeah, yeah.
LAUGHTER
No, you answered
that question.
Is it a terrible thing?
No, no.
I actually paid for my college,
my sister's college education.
Oh, that's so him!
APPLAUSE
I did.
The next one, I bought
my other sister a car.
Your sister a car, not yourself.
No.
My Aston Martin...
His dad's Aston Martin.
Yeah, actually, you should
change that to I bought my
my dad a Aston Martin.
Because that's actually
what happened!
I do feel like I've been
set up a little bit.
Simon Pegg, what did you...?
Make it up.
No, this is true.
I bought a second hand...
Orphanage.
A second-hand orphanage.
LAUGHTER.
I kicked all those little shits out.
And parked my Aston Martin there.
No, I bought a second-hand Mazda MX5
with my Switch card.
LAUGHTER.
My first pay cheque for Big Train,
which was a sketch show on BBC Two,
and I bought a car
with my Switch card.
Which was like a little
debit card, you remember.
I thought you'd have bought
something more nerdy,
like a Death Star made
of Lego or something.
That would seem to be
what you'd go shopping...
I did once by Darth Vader
helmet which cost more,
but that was slightly later.
Was it an original?
It was one that had been decorated
by a graffiti artist.
They did this whole project
called the Vader Project,
and they decorated all these
Darth Vader helmets
and I bought one.
Because that is you.
I mean, you are a proper fan of all
these things, and now you are...
Nerds are so jealous
of you because you've done
the trifecta, haven't you?
Yes, yeah, Doctor Who,
Star Trek and Star Wars, yeah.
You've been in them all.
Yes.
I wrote Star Trek as well,
which was an added...
Yes.
If I was a bit of chocolate,
I'd eat myself, wouldn't I?
And if you're listening
to this, kind of thinking,
I don't remember Simon Pegg
in Star Wars, you were in it.
You were properly in it.
Here you are.
That is...
You had a character
name and everything?
Unkar Plutt, yeah.
He was a junk dealer
on the planet Jakku,
and I was wearing that
in 50-degree heat.
And I had these big rubber,
like silicon gauntlets on,
which were my fingers.
And when I took them off,
I could pour the sweat out.
And if you're interested,
your sweat's a sort of milky colour.
Because Henry, you are
quite a nerd as well?
I mean, you must have been so geeked
to be Superman, to kind of...
Yeah.
I'm a geek.
We talk a bit on set about stuff.
We do.
Quietly in dark corners.
We actually...
Can I tell this story?
We were in Paris...
Does he have a choice to answer?
It's like, Henry, get in this
helicopter, are you OK?
No!
We were shooting a car
chase in Paris, and it
was me, Tom, Sean Harris,
Ving Rhames and Henry...
You just asked him
if you could tell it.
You didn't ask me.
Can I tell this story?
You come out all right!
This is the one that...?
Oh, yeah!
So it's a very cramped car,
particularly with Ving and Henry,
who are both big guys,
and me in the middle,
bombing around Paris.
And every time we finished the shot,
we have to reset the shot,
drive back to the start point
and do it again.
Henry has had enough
of sitting in the cramped car,
so he says, can I run back?
I'll run back.
He did a bit of running.
So Henry took off, and ran
back to position one,
and we just drove next
to him, going...
(HUMS SUPERMAN THEME).
He was doing the score,
we were just driving.
He did the whole thing.
The whole way, next to him.
It was one of the coolest moments
of my life, having Tom Cruise do
that driving next to you.
You know you've made it.
APPLAUSE
Right, it's time for music.
This Brit Award-winning songstress
is back with a number one
album The Architect.
Performing Til I'm Done,
it's Paloma Faith.
CHEERING
# Yeah, I'm a fighter
and I made it through
# Solid gold survivor,
that's my attitude
# But I didn't know (I didn't know)
# I didn't know (I didn't know)
# That I had to be your hero
# Baby, don't ask me to be
strong for you as well
# Pushed off the edge
and now I'm back from hell
# But I didn't know (I didn't know)
# I didn't know (I didn't know)
# That I had to be your
hero (So give me light)
# I'm not built to carry us
both (So give me light)
# Time to rest my weary
bones (So give me light)
# You've got to find your own road
# Help me see
# Just when I thought I'd had enough
# And no more light and no more love
# It's not over
# I won't save you when I'm weak
# Only got so much left to give
# It's not over til I'm done
# Oh-oh, oh-oh, ooh
# Til I'm done
# You look at me and
see how much I take
# But with this heart
of glass, I'm about to break
# But I didn't know (I didn't know)
# I didn't know (I didn't know)
# That I had to be your hero
(So give me light)
# I'm not built to carry us
both (So give me light)
# Time to rest my weary bones
(So give me light)
# You've got to find your own road
# Help me see
# Just when I thought I'd had enough
# And no more light and no more love
# It's not over
# I won't save you when I'm weak
# Only got so much left to give
# It's not over
# Whatcha think you ever
did for me before?
# (So give me light)
# Block out the sun and let
the moon fall on the floor
# (So give me light)
# I am empty, ain't got
nothing left to give
# (So give me light)
# And no you ain't
the one I wanna be with
# Just when I thought I'd had enough
# And no more light and no more love
# It's not over
# I won't save you when I'm weak
# Only got so much left to give
# It's not over
# Just when I thought I'd had enough
# And no more light and no more love
# It's not over
# I won't save you when I'm weak
# Only got so much left to give
# It's not over
# Til I'm done
# Oh-oh, oh-oh, ooh
# Til I'm done #.
CHEERING.
Paloma Faith, everybody!
Great job.
And the backing
singers and the band.
Hello, darling.
Lovely to see you.
Simon, Henry, Rebecca, Tom...
Beautiful job, lady.
Very good, very good.
Oh, oh she is shiny.
Have a seat, do.
So that is off the new
album, The Architect.
Here you go, that's it.
Number one, ladies and gentlemen!
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE.
I listened to you on the radio,
I love how happy you are
that it's number one.
You're not going to be cool,
you're just over the moon.
I've never been cool, Graham.
I feel like I've just
come to the office party
as the entertainment!
LAUGHTER
Hi, guys.
It's a morale-building exercise,
I'm here to just brighten
up your lives so you can slave away
for another 12 months
for my business.
Here's the weird thing.
You recorded this album
and you were pregnant
when you've recorded the album?
Yeah.
As you are.
Tell me all about it!
I didn't know this, so your voice
changes when you're pregnant?
Well, no, it wasn't
when I was pregnant,
it was afterwards that I felt
like it was better.
Oh, OK.
Because...
Have you done it before?
Had a baby?
My voice is spectacular.
Have you had a baby?
Yes, I have had.
So like, your body, everything
moves, all the organs move and it
opens up and goes a bit wild.
A bit graphic!
LAUGHTER
I didn't need that!
I'm quite lucky because some
of the things that were really
bugging me, like continual ailments,
never came back, because it must
have just moved a bit.
I think my lungs went
into a better place or something.
I just want to re-sing everything,
because I'd sung it all pregnant
and pre-pregnancy and then
I was like, no, this is better.
I feel like I can go
from low to high.
But maybe it's psychological.
Maybe you should have more babies.
I think I might.
Yeah.
Can we do on now?
It's, it's late.
All right, Paloma...!
There's quite a few nice
people to choose from.
It's quite the gene pool,
it really is quite the gene pool.
You're right.
Maybe we could all amalgamate.
Tom needs to work
tomorrow, he's busy.
Very quickly, you're off
on tour, aren't you?
Yeah, in March.
Fantastic.
I'm really looking forward to it.
Brilliant.
Thank you very much
for that great performance.
Paloma Faith, everybody!
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
That is nearly
it but just time for a visit
to the big red chair.
This is your least
favourite bit of the show.
Tom hates this!
Hello?
Hello.
Who are you?
My name's John.
John, hello John.
Where are you from?
I'm from Scotland.
Lovely, happy Burns
Day for yesterday.
Thank you.
LAUGHTER
And do you live down here now?
I do, Central London.
All right.
Oh, central London.
None of your suburbs for John.
No, he came from Scotland
and he made it.
LAUGHTER
Zone 1.
What do you do, John?
I'm a lawyer.
Oh, he did make it, oh, yeah.
Zone 1 John.
OK, off you go with your story.
So my grandad died...
LAUGHTER
It happens.
They get old.
We were having an open coffin
for him at my grandmother's house,
and they were keeping the coffin out
in the conservatory,
and we were having lots
of visitors coming and going
to pay their respects.
So that damaged the front door
a little at my grandmother's house.
So my grandad being a tradesman,
we looked up his book of contacts
to find someone we thought might be
able to fix it.
So we find a man called Jim,
give him a call and he turns up very
early the next morning.
So he's working away
on the door and I think,
I should probably make small talk.
So I ask him, "Do you want to pop
through and see grandad?"
He kind of casually looked up
and said, "Yeah, I'll pop
through when I'm finished, son".
So he finished the job,
got up, casually walked
through into the conservatory...
At which point I realised he didn't
know grandad had died.
LAUGHTER
So he walked in expecting
to see my grandad
in his slippers reading
the papers and saw my grandad
very dead in a coffin.
Oh my God.
LAUGHTER
The colour completely
drained from his face.
Even then made this
inaudible sort of" urgggh".
He turned around and just when out
the house so quickly and we've
never seen him again.
LAUGHTER
That was 15 years ago.
That's a good story.
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
You can walk.
If you would like to join us
on the show, let us know
at this very address.
That's it for tonight.
Please say a huge thank
you to my guests - Paloma Faith...
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
Simon Pegg...
Henry Cavill...
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
Rebecca Ferguson...
And Mr Tom Cruise!
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
Thank you, thank you, Graham.
Join me next week with musical guest
George Ezra, Voice judge Will.i.am,
Oscar winner Cuba Gooding Jr and,
for the first time, one
of our favourite British
stars, Imelda Staunton.
I'll see you then!
Goodnight everyone, bye-bye!
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
OK, so come to Tom in three, two...
What does that mean?
LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE
You see what I'm saying?!
I don't know, three,
two and he pointed.
I was like, does that
mean I start talking?
OK, good.
I go on the point.
OK.