Everyone get close to everyone
so you can touch someone.
This is very serious. It's more
serious than you can imagine.
Let's pray.
Father, we thank you for...
just being our God, and
for all that you do.
We thank you for this day, and...
we thank you for the chill
in this air, Father.
Because we thank you
for the sunshine,
because you create the chill
and you create the sunshine.
And you know these are
tough times, Father.
We're asking this morning
for your guidance.
- Amen.
We stand here today, with
a plant that's closing,
with a... a deep,
rich history, and,
it's sad for me and, I'm sure,
everybody else in
there to see it go,
but I will say this:
I'm extremely proud of the people
that work in this plant here.
There's none better.
They know how to get the job done.
- How old are these houses?
- Two hundred years?
No way. America was founded
only 200 years ago.
Oh.
- Then at least several decades.
- Yeah, maybe.
- Cold?
- Yeah.
But this is really beautiful.
Yeah, gorgeous.
See, America's airspace
is really busy.
There's one.
And there.
When you take a look
at an automobile,
you see glass all around it.
That's what we do.
We have about 70% of the market.
Okay? Which is pretty extensive.
We have facilities
around the world,
throughout China, United States
now, with our plant here.
What we're doing is we're
melding two cultures together:
the Chinese culture
and the US culture.
So we are truly a
global organisation.
So, we do have three
different shifts
right now that we
are working with.
A first, second, and a
third. Pretty traditional.
You'll also have a
30-minute unpaid lunch.
Plus, there's two
15-minute paid breaks.
Plenty of opportunities,
ladies and gentlemen.
Plenty of opportunities.
Is this a union shop?
We are not.
It is our desire to not be.
But we recognise
that, one, we need
to do things right by employees.
Okay? We recognise that.
I have, actually, 28
years experience.
Very good.
Payroll, human resources,
operations, things like that.
I have a master's in mechanical
engineering too, so...
Okay, good. Super.
Sounds like you got a
lot of good skills.
Well, I... Actually, I've worked
in all kinds of
different levels of...
Yeah? Okay, good.
What we'll do is we'll take a
look at your résumé. All right?
Where you sit today used to
be a General Motors plant.
This plant closed,
leaving 2,000 families unemployed.
And now, there are over 1,000
employees working here,
with still more to be hired.
It was a little over two years ago
that this facility was a very dark
and very stark reminder of the
greatest economic downturn
in American history since
the Great Depression.
And with that, you
understand the...
the personal impact that that has,
individually and for the
families of all those involved.
It's been a very fast process
from the very beginning.
When I hired in, there was
nothing in the plant.
And since that time, you can
see, in the last six months,
the amount of people and
equipment that have come in.
And it's, exciting.
The commitment everybody's
put in, hard work.
We're looking forward
to starting production.
Since you've arrived in America,
I believe you've found
many things different
from life in China.
We need to get to know Americans.
America is a place to let
your personality run free.
As long as you're not
doing anything illegal,
you're free to follow your heart.
You can even joke
about the president.
Nobody will do anything to you.
Americans' cars are big and
huge, very comfortable.
This represents the American
sense of casualness.
They don't place a heavy
importance on outfits and attire.
If you travel in Europe
in the summertime,
and you see someone
walking in front of you,
if he's wearing shorts,
vests, and sports shoes,
they must be an American.
Americans say what they
are thinking directly.
They don't hide anything.
They are very obvious.
Everything is practical
and realistic.
They dislike abstractions and
theory in their daily lives.
Time is limited today,
so I won't keep going.
The list here is really long.
Wow, thank you.
As required by Chairman,
we will have an opening
celebration on October 7th.
From now on,
I ask you to keep
October 7th in mind
and work hard towards
this grand celebration.
Welcome, Chairman.
Good to see you.
This one is the Chevrolet S-10.
It was made in 1982.
That's the first one they made.
The first car from the GM plant.
Wow, Dayton was very well
developed back then?
Exactly. A very well
developed area.
"I have a secret to share, and
from the bottom of my heart,
I love Ohio, and I love the place
where I invest significantly,
here in Dayton."
This is a historic project that is
gonna help grow this community,
give people jobs, and give a
future to your kids and my kids
that did for those trucks
back there when our parents
and grandparents worked on
refrigerators and cars.
And the future is bright,
folks. The future is bright.
Please join me in acknowledging
the newly-named Fuyao Avenue.
"Good morning, everyone.
And we meet again today."
Every time I visit this plant,
I see a lot of changes.
"Every time when I visit,
I see great progress."
You see there's still empty
space for more equipment.
It will all be installed
within a year.
"If we can follow through with our
plan and become successful here,
this will be a great example
of the US successfully
attracting foreign investment."
Thank you very much.
"Thank you very much."
He says that a lot of people
lost their jobs in this area,
and he thanks you for
the opportunity.
And tell him, one time,
he has to come down here
and eat some barbecue with us.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
So the clients are satisfied?
Yes, very satisfied.
Especially Chrysler.
I am pairing an American
with a Chinese.
The American is the
main operator, with
a Chinese supervisor
by their side.
They're pretty slow.
They have fat fingers.
We keep training
them over and over.
How you doing?
The chairman has said from the
beginning this is an
American company.
It's Fuyao Glass America. It
needs to be an American company,
we need to treat it like
an American company,
but we need to be
successful just like
all our plants
throughout the world.
So, basically, this
line, that's the stage.
So from there back to the stage,
- and then people out that way.
- Facing that way.
- Yeah.
- We're talking, like,
a concert stage without cover
and potentially a
overhang for weather.
We're gonna have to plan for that.
You know what I mean?
Like, a concert...
Chairman thinks we're okay
with October weather,
so you don't need any hang.
- No hang.
- What if it rains?
It won't.
In October, the weather
will be like it is today.
Chairman thinks, in October,
the weather will be similar
- to... today.
- Today?
Also, Chairman says that
door can't face this way.
What door?
Face... You know, the
opening right there.
Well, we just signed
a contract, so...
- What?
- That's a big...
You got to talk to Jimmy
about... I don't know.
I think it's...
Jimmy, do you understand
what he means?
We just did a purchase order and
ordered a garage door and stuff.
So, you got to face some
other direction, I think.
- So...
- They already put the door in.
So we're gonna have to
change it. Is that okay?
- Yeah, we need to change it.
- Okay.
Yeah, Z, just change it.
That's gonna cost us $35,000.
I have an idea, but I am
not sure it's a good one.
We hang two artworks here.
One is something iconic of China,
like the Great Wall.
- The other one is from the US.
- No. Only American ones.
Only American ones.
When in Rome, do as the Romans do.
Don't upset them.
American, just...
They haven't done good
decorative work here.
This can't be here. It
should be moved to the side.
There are... It's required by law
to have one in here, and
it has to be that height.
They're just saying
that it should be
moved to the side.
- We can move it, yeah.
- Huh?
David says that is
the required height.
We can't place it down there.
It has to be that high.
We can move it to that corner.
Then up there.
It's a legal requirement.
I'll ask him.
He has to ask and see. He knows
this is the right height.
But sometimes, you have
to think, before you do,
so then we don't have
to redo the work,
because it costs money.
Yeah, I've... That was done...
I wouldn't have
necessarily moved, but
that was done way
before I got here.
Catch another big fish.
Did you all set the bait this way?
- Looks fucking cool.
- How do you set it?
You got the Fuyao employees
down here doing it.
- Oh, yeah?
- They all work at Fuyao.
- Fuyao or Fiyao?
- Fuyao.
Fiyao? Is that how
it's pronounced?
Fuyao. F-U-Y-A-O.
- Fuyao, Inc.
- Fuyao?
- Yes, Fuyao Company.
- What type of company is that?
Automotive glass. They
make the glass...
Yes, make glass.
- Oh, nice. Okay.
- The car glass.
- Okay, wow, glass.
- Yes.
Ooh, that's a big one right there.
- Big, yes.
- Very big.
- How speak English?
- Carp.
C-A-R-P. Carp.
- C-A-R-P. Carp. Carp.
- Yep. Those are carp.
Now, the carp that you're catching
- likes corn and Wheaties.
- Huh.
Have you heard of Wheaties cereal?
- I don't know. Wheaty...
- Never heard of Wheaties?
- Wheaties? I don't know.
- Wheaties.
Yeah, buddy. You'd be surprised
how good Wheaties works.
Wheaties? W-E-D-S?
W-E-E-T-E-S.
- No. I don't know that.
- Okay. Yup, it does the best.
Looks like they're getting
ready to go, huh?
We're going home to gut the
fish, and we'll come back.
All right, Leon. I'mma go home
and get me something to eat.
- I'll be back down.
- Okay, okay.
- Nice to meet you.
All right, Leon.
- Patty?
- Yes?
- I'm getting ready to leave.
- Okay.
- All right.
- Have a good day.
For a year and a half, I
didn't have anything.
When I started at Fuyao,
I was thankful, I was
blessed, I was...
just on my knees, thanking
God that I had something.
- Hey, what's up, man?
- Hey, what's going on?
Going good.
- All right?
- Yeah.
This is the best game
in town right now.
Going back in there
for the first time,
I kind of welled up because...
I could see the post locations...
you know, on the
columns, you know?
Which actually tells you
where you are in the plant.
People still get lost. I
said, "I don't get lost."
At General Motors,
I was making $29
and some change an hour.
At Fuyao, I make 12.84.
Back then, if my kids wanted
a pair of new gym shoes,
I could just go get them.
I can't just do that now.
We lost our home,
we lost a vehicle.
- Have a good weekend.
- All right, you too.
When GM closed, I
foreclosed on my house.
Ever since then,
I have struggled to try to get
back to middle class again.
I've been living in
my sister's basement.
I am fortunate enough
to have a bedroom.
And the only thing in here
is my end tables and my TV.
The bed isn't mine.
The bed is theirs.
You know? So, yeah.
We've been down about... I
don't know, 45 minutes or so.
Water spots, I guess.
Thank you.
They've drained the washer.
They're slowing it down.
They get upset when we're all
trying to figure something out.
Everybody gets upset, and
then everybody's upset
in their own language,
and then everybody just
walks their own way, and...
meet back here in five minutes.
Set the water temperature to 60°.
Because it has high alkalinity.
Okay. Later on, we're going
to try to lower the...
Okay.
Be careful.
Beautiful. Beautiful.
Down a little.
Down a little bit.
This damn thing...
- Allen wrench.
- Allen. Allen.
Allen wrench.
- Allen wrench.
My first impression of
Ohio was how flat it is.
My family's in China.
Two lovely children
and a beautiful wife.
Fuyao offered me my
first job at 18.
I've worked in the furnace
for more than 20 years.
It's a hard job, but I love it.
Because of the language barrier
and cultural differences,
it's hard to quickly
integrate everyone's ideas.
I don't have much time
to eat every day.
So every week, I bring
a box of Twinkies.
This is my lunch.
I eat two at a time.
Look at the red sticks.
This one is broken.
We have to pull it
out by ourselves.
Look at the scars on my arm.
These are all scalds.
I got burned.
Air.
Wong and I have spent a
lot of time together
with him teaching me everything...
Mother's Day, we spent the
whole weekend working together
with our little translators,
talking back and forth.
That's when they told me that
they had to be here two years,
away from their
family, no extra pay.
That really made me start thinking
and appreciating what they're
doing for us more and more.
I've ate at their house,
they've ate at my home.
We've just bonded.
And we've tried to learn
each other's culture.
I got the big idea,
Thanksgiving, to...
invite my close friends,
which should have been about
four or five of them.
It ended up being, I think, 13.
Bought a 25-pound
turkey, the biggest
honey-baked ham I could get,
and all of the
traditional trimmings.
I know that in China they're
not allowed to have guns.
We had my 12-gauge shotgun
out there, pistols.
Couple of the very
brave ones wanted
to go up and down the road with me
on my Harley.
They talked about it forever.
That made me happy.
That's the front page of The
Washington Post, fellas.
That's big-time.
The only negative thing that
I can see from this article
is that, out of our 2,000 people,
they picked the number one UAW...
organiser and
sympathiser to talk to.
Number one.
- Anyway, it's a big deal.
- That's a big deal.
With all of this scrutiny
and with all of this
visibility comes
even more responsibility on us
to do things right.
Now the whole world is watching.
Now the whole world
is watching us.
It should say have
"to be the world."
Yeah, they said they had an S.
Good afternoon.
- Right?
- Good afternoon.
Good afternoon.
Thank you guys very much.
You don't know how
important this is to Fuyao
and to the chairman.
The plant looks great.
These people are coming here
to see something
that they never in
their lifetime thought
would happen.
You have given hope and you
have given life to a community
that was desolate.
This is one of the
greatest projects
in the history of
the United States.
So, be proud, and
most importantly,
have fun.
Two lands,
the bridge is what
brings us together.
Yeah.
And the... How do
you say in English?
- The bond.
- Bond. Yeah, bond. Bond.
Yes, bond.
Welcome.
Welcome to the US.
Today the chairman's
vision has been fulfilled.
Fuyao has invested
close to 500 million.
Ni hao.
Really good seeing
you guys. Thank you.
Thanks for having us out here.
We really appreciate it.
- It's a big deal.
- Absolutely.
This is big. A lot of people.
- Nice weather, man.
- Oh, my gosh.
Chairman ordered the weather.
Oh, I mean, it couldn't be better.
- Right.
- Hang in there.
- How you doing, Dave?
- Good to see you.
Yeah, all right.
"My dear guests and
friends, good morning."
Today, we hold the
opening ceremony
of Fuyao Glass America.
We've heard both
candidates for president
refer to Ohio as the Rust Belt.
And, you know, you look
at... look at this today,
and we reject that term.
With Chairman Cao, we know how to
make everything in this state.
And, this is a terrific example.
One last point: I
know many workers
here are trying to form a union
to strengthen their voice
in this great company.
Ohio has a rich... a
rich, rich history
of unions and management
working together.
I support those in this community,
in this plant, in this crowd
that want to vote on whether
or not to join a union.
I hope Fuyao looks at it the
same way. Thank you all so much.
Who the fuck does he think he is?
Out of place, totally
out of place.
Fuck him.
Three, two, one.
Our glass is totally made in USA.
Ladies, you're doing
a beautiful job.
Create good glass and
transfer good glass.
The senator mentioned the
workers union in his speech.
Does Fuyao have any
good strategies
for avoiding these risks?
Hey, Charles. How you doing, man?
Dave, there's one thing I
got to talk to you about.
Regarding Sherrod
Brown's comments...
Yes.
You know, that's obviously
not beneficial to us.
Absolutely right.
Don't wanna talk about
certain topics.
Correct.
So I think, at this point,
Chairman, you know,
will definitely ask about
- what we're gonna do about it.
- It's okay. Yeah. Yeah.
I'm gonna have to kill a senator.
I'm gonna take those
big scissors and
cut the... Senator Brown's head.
He...
It's big.
He didn't tell us he
was gonna do that.
He did that on purpose,
so they're cut off.
They'll never be allowed
in the plant again.
You all know our stand on this.
We don't want to see the
union developing here.
"First, you all know
our stand on this,
that we want to avoid unions."
If we have a union, it will
impact our efficiency,
thus hurting our company.
It will create loss for us.
If a union comes in,
I'm shutting down.
They keep interfering
with my production.
Slowly bleeding money is
even worse than a union.
"Right now,
if they're creating extreme
inefficiency in my production,
I'm just bleeding money."
John, if you want to
continue to be president,
you have to listen to my advice.
Every piece of glass counts.
Every piece that goes
down that line and
goes... gets on that
customer truck,
it matters.
Our customers are counting on us.
General Motors, Chrysler,
Toyota, Honda.
Whether it's coming from China or
whether it's coming from Dayton,
it's the same...
it's the same thing.
We have to be able to
provide them glass
at the same level of efficiency,
the same level of
cost and quality.
It's audit day.
We don't have glass to show them.
We should have some ready
for the customers to check.
The glass is gonna run
through the furnace,
basically the same as the
other furnace over here.
This one's just a
little bit faster.
So it comes down the
line, it comes in here.
Down in here is another
one of those free-liners
that puts the glass into position.
This is an automatic...
Keep it or throw it out?
- Throw out.
- Throw it...? Okay.
There must be some flaws
if the glass exploded.
The overall quality of the
glass is not good enough,
but there's no way
to improve it now.
We still want to
achieve our targets.
One is output. The
second is speed.
We need one more person.
Transfer someone from China here.
You have the Chinese, who
want numbers on this side.
You have Quality, who wants
customer satisfaction
on this side.
And we're in the middle.
Today was a shitshow,
totally a shitshow.
Any little microscopic
chip can cause a breakage.
As soon as it hits the
press, it begins to cool.
If there's a...
Got it?
Four hundred-and-something
degrees.
And they're six feet away from it?
We need to find some solutions,
whether it's them stepping
into a colder room
as soon as they leave there...
We've got to get them some relief.
How much time do you
spend in there?
About ten minutes or so.
Ten minutes an hour, a day, a...?
Sometimes every hour.
So every hour? So you go in
there, it's about 200 degrees,
and you clean up in there for
about two hours... All right.
The conditions...
are not favourable.
Doing the same thing
over and over again.
That wears on you.
Body, mind...
You're so... It's...
Sometimes you think...
"Why am I doing this?"
You think about whether
you have the stamina
and the will to do
this type of job.
Anything they're not happy about?
It gets really hot in here.
Our American colleagues
are very afraid of heat.
We try to give them the
environment they want,
as long as it's within
a reasonable budget.
The spaces between the production
lines are pretty narrow.
The Occupational Safety
& Health Administration
thinks it's too dense.
"A tall tree catches the wind."
Yes, it's a huge tree.
Let's welcome Chairman.
Dear staff,
good morning.
We haven't reached our goals.
This is a very tough
challenge for us.
We are all Chinese.
We were born
of Chinese mothers.
No matter where you die or are
buried, you will
always be Chinese.
The motherland is like a mother.
This is eternal.
Today, Chinese come to the
US to operate factories.
The most important thing is
not how much money we earn,
but how this will change
Americans' views of the Chinese
and towards China.
Every Chinese person
should do things
for our country and our people.
It's down to every
one of you here.
American workers are not
efficient, and output is low.
I can't manage them.
When we try to manage them, they
threaten to get help
from the union.
How can we make
Americans understand
that the Chinese can open
factories in America?
This is a big problem.
- Hey. Welcome. Thank you.
- Welcome. Nice to see you again.
- How are you? Good?
- Good.
- How are you?
- Hi. Welcome.
♪ Noble sentiments ♪
♪ Are transparent ♪
♪ For the sake of transparency ♪
♪ We've gone through
difficulties ♪
♪ For the sake of transparency ♪
♪ We've struggled every bit ♪
♪ Fuyao holds up ♪
♪ A transparent world ♪
♪ China is filled with spring ♪
♪ And happiness is everywhere ♪
♪ All the blessings from Fuyao ♪
♪ Are transparent ♪
Ni hao.
- Ni hao.
- Pleasure.
Ni hao. Good morning.
Pleasure to meet you.
- Good morning.
- Ni hao.
- Nice to meet you.
- Thank you.
- Good morning.
Nice to meet you.
- Ni hao.
Ni hao.
Good morning, my name
is John Withrow.
I'm supervisor in Lamination.
Good morning. I'm Austin Cole.
I'm a tempering backlight
production supervisor.
Jon Helton, the continuous
improvement supervisor.
Good morning, Darren Noble. Lead
supervisor, ARG
packaging assembly.
Welcome, everybody.
Welcome home.
The whole world is looking at FGA
and you guys are the top guns.
We are investing in the US.
We love the country, and we
want to be part of the country
and provide benefits
to the country.
And we hope that FGA
will be profitable soon
and to let our customers know
that we are a strong company.
This is a very valuable time
and also a special time.
Tonight we'll have you join
our year-end group party,
and, we also hope you can, get
some time to taste local cuisines.
Thank you for putting
us up in a nice hotel.
Yes.
I think that we are also anxious
to see how your process runs
and look forward to
taking back new ideas
and implementations to help
us run better as well.
I can't breathe in that.
Non-stop.
- Okay.
This is the line
they'll run 7,000 on?
We hope someday to get this good.
Attention.
Dress right.
Keep an eye on the distance
between yourself and others.
Eyes front.
Straddle.
Hello, everyone.
Good. We are good.
Number off.
- One.
- Two.
- Three.
- Four.
- Five.
- Six.
- Seven.
- Eight.
- Nine.
- Ten.
Eleven.
- Twelve.
- Thirteen.
- Fourteen.
- Fifteen.
- Sixteen.
- Seventeen.
Eighteen.
Nineteen. Report.
There should be 19 people in this
team, and all 19 people are here.
Over.
Good afternoon.
- Sorry.
- Sorry. Sorry.
- Please.
- Please. Please.
- Thank you.
- Thank you. Thank you.
Attention.
- Our team name is?
- Improvement.
Our slogan is?
To stand still is to move back.
Attention.
The preparation meeting is over.
Dismissed.
I heard things are not
going too well over there.
Right. That's true. That's why
we're doing training here.
You guys have eight
days off every month.
You have all the weekends.
Only eight hours a day.
That's an easy life.
Yes.
These workers only have one
or two days off per month.
They're not too happy about that.
That's why I told you American
workers are too lazy.
It's just your nature.
But you're not bad.
Every person can be changed.
We have some extremely
diligent workers.
Very motivated, very ambitious.
They're great.
But most workers are there
just to make money,
not to make glass.
How many hours a day do they work?
Eight hours per shift.
Eight hours. So about
100 dollars a day.
Here we say you have to
be worthy of your salary.
You need to prove you deserve
it. You understand, right?
Yes, I understand.
I heard that your workers like
to joke around and talk a lot.
The best tool we can
use is duct tape.
Put it over their mouths.
They will perform better.
- Tape?
- Tape on their mouths.
Can you do that there?
No, we can't. But if we could do
that, we'd have
improved production.
Because they're too chatty now.
Well, the most important thing
is that you all should be united
and concentrate your efforts.
It's not bad working here.
I'm married.
My child is in my home town.
We don't have many holidays, so I
don't have much time
to go back home.
Only during the Spring
Festival, once a year.
We work 12 hours a shift.
I'm tired, but I have no choice.
We work whenever we're
asked by our leader.
I have two kids now.
One is six months old, the
other is four years old.
They're pretty young.
If we're too busy, we may not
be able to take days off.
I only go home once
or twice a year.
My older kid is 11, and
the younger one is eight.
I work long hours and I spend
very little time with them.
Holy shit.
They don't have any safety glasses
on, nothing. Unbelievable.
Those aren't even
cut-resistant gloves.
Man, that is nuts.
You got to be kidding me.
The glass in our factory...
Different glass colours have
different values for recycling.
So they have to sort the colours.
These people sit there
all day long doing that.
That's fucking crazy. Picking
through fucking glass like that.
We are energetic at Fuyao.
All of us are energetic
and happy to work here.
All of our workers are members
of the workers union.
Mao Zedong,
and this is Deng Xiaoping,
Jiang Zemin,
Hu Jintao,
Xi Jinping.
These are the five leaders
since China was established.
Without backing from
the government,
the company wouldn't get too far.
Our workers union and the company
are closely related to each other.
They are like two gears
rotating together.
We need our workers to
fight for Fuyao's success.
We are all in the same boat.
Keeping the boat safe
means everyone is safe.
If the boat sinks,
everyone loses their jobs.
It's quite simple.
Chairman Cao, here
is a hada for you.
Next on the red carpet will
be workers from two teams.
They have won the
Excellent Team award.
Year 2017...
"Soaring ambitions."
"The spirit of craftsmanship
is all over China."
Let's welcome Chairman Cao
with our warmest applause.
Dear Chairman,
dear colleagues,
tonight is a gathering
time for our Fuyao family.
Everybody performing tonight
works here at Fuyao.
♪ We've cooked A joyful
New Year's Eve dinner ♪
♪ The family is cheerful
the family is joyful ♪
♪ We wish you radiant joy ♪
♪ Happy New Year we wish you
an auspicious New Year ♪
♪ We wish you a safe year we wish
your family a fortunate New Year ♪
♪ May you be happy
and prosperous ♪
♪ May the best come,
may the worst leave ♪
♪ Always be courteous and polite ♪
♪ May you be happy
and prosperous ♪
Come on. Two words have become
really popular recently.
What are the words?
Intelligence. Lean.
♪ Intelligent and
lean manufacturing ♪
♪ All industries
should adopt them ♪
♪ Finance, service,
manufacturing ♪
♪ Intelligent and
lean manufacturing ♪
♪ Technology is
developing rapidly ♪
♪ The information age
has already arrived ♪
♪ Employee relations
system is amazing ♪
♪ Great at resource integration
and market response ♪
♪ Waste eliminated and
revenues generated ♪
♪ Transition, upgrade
promotion, integration ♪
♪ A corporation with
lean manufacturing ♪
♪ Fuyao is creating a new future ♪
We're very impressed,
everybody from the United States,
with China's operations.
Very harmonious people.
You see it and you feel it.
♪ Young man there's
no need to feel down ♪
♪ I said, young man pick
yourself off the ground ♪
♪ I said, young man because
you're in a new town ♪
♪ There's no need to be unhappy ♪
♪ It's fun to stay at the YMCA ♪
♪ They have everything
for the men to enjoy ♪
♪ You can hang out
with all the boys ♪
♪ It's fun to stay at the YMCA ♪
Please hold the
hand of your bride.
From this moment on,
no matter poor or rich,
you will always care for her,
cherish her, and protect her,
until forever.
Will you?
- Yes, I will.
We're one...
big planet.
A world...
somewhat divided.
But we're one.
And tonight is an example.
- Happy. Happy.
- Aww.
Happy tears.
I'm very happy to share
in your culture.
- Thanks so much.
- No, thank you.
We are one.
- Yes, we are one.
- We are one.
Yes. One tongue, one company.
Yes.
Thank you.
- Aren't watermelons sweet?
- Sweet.
Choose the best picture
to put on the cover
of the next edition
of Fuyao People.
This is my community,
and to see this building
come back to life,
it meant a lot to me.
Fuyao is the leader, Fuyao
is changing the industry,
and I see us becoming number
one in the world next year
and number one in the
world every year.
Yes, sir. How are you doing?
I have a really good idea for you.
Why don't you film
those three microwave ovens that
have been out for two weeks
- that haven't been replaced?
- Okay.
- Why don't you film that?
- We will.
And tell me why this area is now
gonna be used for production
and no longer a lunchroom.
There's signs all
over that say that.
Where's the lunchroom gonna be?
I have no clue.
You're telling me...
That's typical.
telling me something new.
I just got back from vacation.
They're gonna take all the
tables and all the chairs out
and make this a production
space. Like everywhere else.
I hope they make your
office a production space.
They manage to have these things
on all the time. This is America.
We don't need Chinese
children singing and praying.
Coming back from the China trip,
some of the things I
started implementing...
Well, the first thing
I implemented was...
At our pre-shift meeting,
we used to just kind of sit
at the tables and talk and...
watching the Chinese
shift meeting,
where he had them all lined up...
I've found that that's worked out
really well for me back here.
Good morning, everybody.
Greg, I need you to stand
on two, starting off.
Chuck, I need you
standing on three.
I think that's everybody.
It's an experiment.
So, the lines are
running okay today?
Everybody got your
glasses and boots?
We're good?
Any questions?
Okay, let's have a good day.
They're gonna do
surgery for your hand?
They're gonna tell me tomorrow.
They'll tell you tomorrow what
your recovery's gonna be.
Yeah, they'll probably
start at four weeks,
determine what... you
know, how it's gonna be,
and then, from there,
go to the eight weeks.
I'm worried about my points.
- No, no...
- No, no, no, no.
Don't worry about any of that.
Don't have to worry about
your points for missing time.
I don't wanna lose my job.
No, you're not gonna
lose your job.
- What's that?
- My pay?
- Yes.
- It's covered?
Yes. I don't know how
all of that works,
but it is.
Yeah.
Everybody at every
level will say we
really, really, really
want to be safe.
But safe doesn't pay the bills.
The room that we work in,
there's only one way in,
no doors on the opposite side.
If a fire breaks out,
that's like being trapped.
They're wanting us to pull one of
those big sheets off
and inspect it.
Some of this float glass is so big
that I'm gonna have people
exposing their face,
and I don't... I don't
need to do that.
A couple days ago, I had
to tell the Chinese fellow
that I absolutely
refuse to pick up
two loads with a
stand-up forklift.
It's not strong enough.
I said, "If you want
to do it, that's
fine, you do it. I'm not doing it.
I'm not... I'm not risking
somebody's life."
Out of all my working life,
I have never ever had a
workplace injury, ever.
I mean, 15 years
at General Motors,
you know, never a
workplace injury.
And then my new job at Fuyao...
what happens?
I get a workplace injury.
Right now, I'm outside
the Moraine plant here,
off Kettering Boulevard.
There have been 11 safety
complaints filed against Fuyao.
Some workers claim unsafe
working conditions
and unfair treatment.
I say "people," you say "power."
- People.
- Power.
I say "people," you say "union."
- People.
- Union.
All right. Whoo.
Meeting after work, don't
forget, next week.
We'll see you there.
Bring your co-workers.
There's a lot of information that
you're seeing on TV about Fuyao.
"Safety concerns,"
other things that are...
are being reported,
much of which we do
not believe are true.
Because if you bring in a union...
this becomes illegal.
You cannot do it any more.
Instead, if I'm an employee,
I have to take my concerns
to the union rep.
When we had this
training in private,
I was horrified by this picture.
If this becomes a reality,
we wouldn't be able to
communicate directly
with our American co-workers.
Isn't that terrible?
If we are able to improve our
management capabilities,
it will help quell
the union rebellion.
"And if we are able to improve
our management capabilities,
it will help with our campaign
against union organisations..."
We hired Americans to work as
our managers and supervisors.
Our expectation was that
we could trust them,
pay them a high salary, and
they would serve the company.
Why didn't they?
I think they are
hostile to Chinese.
The loss from January to October
is about 40 million US dollars.
We have to reverse the
tide as soon as possible.
With the new restructuring,
I believe we will see this
plant in profit very soon.
We've invited Jeff Liu
to be our new president.
Good morning, everyone.
I was born in 1963, in
the Year of the Rabbit.
I've spent 27 years in the
US and 26 years in China.
People always guess I am in
my 40s, but I'm actually 53.
Why is that? Because
I have passion.
I have determination
to do things well.
"A major shake-up of the company's
senior management team,
with company President
John Gauthier
and Vice President
Dave Burrows leaving."
Actually...
terminated.
♪ We wish you a Merry Christmas ♪
♪ And a Happy New Year ♪
- Got one.
- Got one? All right, boss.
Need a hat, Jim?
- Right here. I'll take it.
- All right.
- That's good, brother.
- Merry Christmas to you.
Merry Christmas to you.
Thanks for your work.
Hello, everybody.
I would like to use
this opportunity
to thank each of you
for the hard work.
And also, we need
to work as a team
under one roof, one culture,
and make a great year for 2017.
We can turn the company around.
We make more money, and everybody
gonna share the piece of pie.
How's that?
Not bad.
You want a hat, Chairman?
He asked if you want a hat.
Of course.
Here you go, boss.
Let me wear a hat.
Hi.
- Ni hao.
- Ni hao, ni hao, ni hao.
- Hello.
- Ni hao.
Ni hao.
Someone from work was
kind enough to tell me
that there were these apartments.
Four hundred and eighty
dollars a month.
I fell in love with it.
I can afford to live here
and have my own place and
feel independent again.
Smells good.
This is the most enjoyable
moment in a day.
After I finish the cigarette,
my mind just calms down.
We workers lay down tracks
so the train can run smoothly.
The only thing we have in
mind is to do our best.
That's true for everyone here.
My wife.
My toothache has gone.
I've fully recovered.
The last time I cried,
I was a teenager.
But I cried once
after coming here.
I don't dare mention
that to other people.
But when all is quiet
in the dead of night,
I miss my family.
I've learnt most of what I
learnt from Leon and Wong.
None of us knew glass
when we came there.
When you get to be my age, not
too many people wanna hire you.
They don't wanna take a chance.
My brother, he's my
Chinese brother.
I would have his back, just like
I'd have one of my own brothers'.
I just... I think
the world of him.
Are you okay?
My supervisor started
yelling at me.
When... You work at the
table right there.
I was working right
here just fine.
Now he wanna change
it right over here.
We know, the table over there.
Now, instead of here, they
want you to do it here? Okay.
He said he expects us to
do eight boxes at a time.
I just want to make sure
you're not gonna get hurt.
He said he want us to
push them in here.
Well, now, you... It's probably
too heavy for you to push it.
So you need to let him know that.
I don't understand.
Sometimes, why she don't
know to tell that?
Make sure you're communicating
to them that you need help.
I have.
He knows.
Rather than trying
to find resolution,
they try to find out who's wrong.
And, in this case,
they're both wrong.
You need some skills
to handle Americans.
How can we take advantage
of American characteristics
to make them work for Fuyao?
There's a culture in the US
where children are showered
with encouragement.
So everyone who grows up in
the US is overconfident.
They are super confident.
Americans love being
flattered to death.
You will get into trouble
if you fight with them.
"Donkeys like being touched in
the direction their hair grows."
Right?
You should touch donkeys in the
direction their hair grows.
Otherwise, they'll kick you.
Do you understand what I'm
saying? You do? Okay.
We need to use our wisdom to
guide them and help them.
Because we are better than them.
They refer to us as
"the foreigners."
People just want...
They wanna feel
like they're in America working,
not like, when they
walk in the door,
that they've left America
and they're now in China.
They work non-stop. They're
in there all the time.
Around the clock, 24 hours a day.
They're in there on Sundays.
There's been some days, they don't
want us to take a break for lunch,
because they need X
amount of glass out.
The Chinese really don't
help us out at all.
They just walk around and tell
the Americans what to do.
"Just do this." And
you're like, "Why?"
They don't tell you why at
all, and they walk away.
I know it's a growing
company, I know it's new.
But with the workload
that comes with it,
you know, you wanna keep
your employees around,
especially your good workers.
A simple pay raise, even
if it's just a dollar.
Just show your appreciation
for them and their hard work.
Optimism, hope. That was what
we were all going in with.
The future looked bright.
Now, it's just... It's a 180.
To me, it's like they
don't respect you.
At least 3,000 people have come
and gone, either fired or quit.
Whenever you have a frustrating
day, you can go outside and...
throw your bin over.
Every one of our
bosses were demoted.
- Yeah.
- The Chinese are in control.
Have the Chinese
changed their mind?
Are they not gonna
turn this over to us?
Because that was one of the...
definitely that was
one of the things
that intrigued me
about coming here.
I love the fact that they came
in here. I love this business.
I worked at Appleton
for over 20 years
and I was one of the guys
that got laid off in 2012.
I've been looking for
something for four years.
I like working with the
people on the floor.
They are working their tails off.
And they're not getting
anything for it,
and I'm not talking
about compensation.
They're not getting
patted on the back.
I've seen the Chinese pouring
chemicals down the drain
out the back of our dock.
Chemicals.
There was a trail of yellow
paint going right to the sewer.
- Right out our back door.
- You couldn't miss it.
It's like they don't even
know what the rules are.
It's...
And I'm thinking, "This is
all going into the sewer
and going into drinking
water somewhere."
I don't wanna waste your time and
I don't wanna to waste my time.
With what we say at this table,
will it make a difference?
I've asked security to come escort
you out if you're
going to do that.
Okay.
Man, they treat these
people like shit in there.
Sometimes, you got
to be Sally Field.
If there are things
your boss can't
fix for you, come talk to me.
Especially how to manage
American workers.
Can we force them
to work overtime?
- Americans?
- Americans.
From HR's perspective,
we can't force them
to work overtime.
We can't say anything like that.
But in China, it's mandatory.
The Americans... I don't
give a shit what they think.
Go ahead and sue me,
but they should come the
hell in on Saturdays.
That's how I would do it.
I think the most important
thing is mutual understanding.
We're under enormous
pressure here.
A lot more pressure than in China.
There was a guy who couldn't fall
asleep for a couple of days.
I really admire Americans.
They can work two jobs.
They can have another job
besides working here.
I always thought Americans lived
a comfortable and superior life.
I thought they didn't have
to make any sacrifices.
Good afternoon, everyone.
Good afternoon.
All the stories that you've
heard about Fuyao is true.
Just to give you an
idea how things are,
my daughter does
nails for a living.
Last year, she made
$13,000 more than I did.
Now, think about that.
She cleared $40,000. I made 27.
Something's wrong with that.
A co-worker of mine was fired
for being hospitalised for a
week and not calling off.
That could've been me.
What if I got sick?
Would they fire me?
The man I was working with,
the cardboard he was
sitting on caught on fire.
And they just kept
right on working.
Dayton taxpayers and the
state of Ohio have committed
tens of millions of
dollars to Fuyao,
and yet Fuyao
management has failed
to provide the good
and the safe jobs
that this community deserves.
Labour.
Working people and the labour
movement built America.
It is what made America
great the first time.
The working people at Fuyao
right now who don't have a...
You have a birthright
that's paid for
by the sweat and blood
of people in this room
and people who have gone
before people in this room,
so that you had a
right to fair life,
to a workplace that was safe.
We fought these
battles 70 years ago.
We rejected 70 years ago
that management and
companies and rich people
get to pick and choose
what happens to you or what you
get or what you don't get.
Nothing in America has changed
in terms of working
people working hard.
That's not what
changed in America.
What changed in America
was people at the top
deciding they wanted
to rewrite the rules
to take advantage of people.
To make it in their
favour at your expense.
And you have a right and an
obligation to say no to that,
and that's what unionising
at Fuyao is all about.
And over the course of fighting
for this all these years,
we found a way for
companies to make
money and still be
fair to employees,
and still pay employees
a decent wage,
and still make sure
that they were safe.
These two things can
exist together.
As you fight this fight at Fuyao,
as UAW stands by you and
fights that fight with you,
as we show Fuyao
that we do things a
little bit different
in Dayton, Ohio,
I will be there every step of
the way fighting with you,
on the side of UAW, on
the side of workers,
and we will win this
fight. Thank you.
- Morning.
Next Monday...
everybody already
employed in this room,
whatever you're paid
today, two dollars more.
Thank you.
Everybody, whatever
you make today,
two dollars more next Monday.
Yeah.
Great?
And the people say, "Why are you
doing that? We're losing money."
The good efficiency generate
from the good employee.
How do we keep a good
employee? Better pay.
We want to be the best employer
in this town. But in return...
work hard, work longer.
Our team here, we can do
the same job as China.
Raise the bar, and I believe the
future will belong to everybody.
Thanks again.
Victory. Whoo.
- We are the union.
- UAW.
They don't want to have to abide
by the rules and regulations
of the United States.
They're in America, and
we want to make sure
that they abide by
the laws in America.
♪ We can bring to birth a new
world from the ashes of the old ♪
♪ For the union makes us strong ♪
♪ Solidarity forever ♪
♪ Because the union
makes us strong ♪
♪ Solidarity forever ♪
We have a better chance of
having things done fair
if we have it written
out in a contract.
That's why we need a union.
Management would listen to
us because they had to.
Every job I've ever worked
on, being a black woman,
that's the only way
that we have a chance.
I understand that,
at times, there's
gonna be a need for a union,
but right now, I got a man
that's given me a good job,
given me a good wage, and allowed
me to come to work every day.
I don't have any need
for somebody else
to come in and get in
the middle of this.
The only thing the union's gonna
do is keep the bad workers.
And the good workers, it's just
gonna go along like it is for us.
How's that work for me?
I know there are some
union activists here.
I know because I have people
who spy for me.
I have many different
ways to deal with them.
Here is one. He is pro-union.
This is him. This person here.
Look, we get along pretty well.
You won't see him here
in two weeks' time.
Good afternoon.
I want to thank you
so much for coming.
I know you didn't have a choice.
The union will go out of their way
to try to convince you that
it's a good thing for you
and that it is in
your best interest.
The contract that you get,
if you get one,
might include better
wages and benefits.
That contract might
include the same
wages and benefits you have today.
And that contract finally might
include less wages
and less benefits.
And the threat of a strike is
no longer scary to employers,
because today if you go on strike,
while you can't get fired,
the employer has the right
to permanently replace you.
I'll let that sink in.
You can't get fired
for going on strike,
but you can get
permanently replaced.
So are you telling us not
to vote for the union?
I'm here to tell you
to do what you want.
I got a question. Who
do you work for?
I work for a company called
Labour Relations Institute.
We're a labour consulting firm.
- Is the company paying you?
- Yes.
Didn't I say that? I usually
say that in every meeting.
- No.
- No, you didn't say that yet.
Well, the reality is, they pay
me to consult with you here...
They pay you to talk to us?
They pay me. They
don't pay me enough
to stand up here and lie to you.
Okay?
He says that he was being
impartial, but he wasn't.
The UAW is free to use
everywhere else in the world.
If they want to pay our...
pay our workforce
to sit through a presentation,
to listen to the pitch,
that's their right.
But while they're on our
clock, it's our message.
They spent a lot of money to
bring these people in here
to make sure that every employee
goes through this session,
not once, but twice,
maybe three times.
They have people walking around
there with patches and stickers on
that's saying: "Vote no.
You still have a voice."
Now, my question to
them people are:
What voice do you have?
When have you ever had a voice?
Ever since they started this
job, it's been a two-man job.
When they put me out here on it,
they decided they wanted
it to be a one-person job.
When I went to talk to HR, I told
them they were targeting me.
Put me on a job to set me up to
write me up for performance issues
and fire me.
I got the phone call from Fuyao
that they had fired me.
I really truly feel like...
that they targeted me.
I was on the news, I was at
the city council meetings.
It's been a pretty sad...
few days.
This sinking feeling of...
"I don't have a job."
I mean, I'm a good worker.
Workers union.
Should I have gotten so involved?
Put my whole life into it?
Here's old Fuyao.
Can't spell Fuyao without F-U.
When I was at Fuyao, I didn't
think we needed a union.
Move forward to today, you
have no voice, you have...
Truly, you...
From what I'm told, there really
isn't an American with authority
that they can talk to.
You know, I...
I think these employees
need something.
I think I need to make only
two more trips this year,
if you achieve what you planned.
Why do I need to come here? It's
not convenient for me. Right?
You think I like to come
to America every month?
It's tiring.
Is the union making any noise?
No, not too much.
Better than it was before.
Recently, we fired a lot
of union supporters.
We have tried different
ways. It's worked out.
A lot of active ones left...
Then you guys should hire
more excellent people.
Young people.
This is the culture I
want for our company.
Then we will have a
good atmosphere here.
A lot of things here in the
US are different from China.
Well, we've invested here already.
It's just not working that well.
Ah?
Morning, you all.
- Fired up, ready to vote.
- Ready to win.
- Ready to vote.
- There you go.
- You ready to win.
- All right, girl.
Fired up, ready to win.
These are actually people from
the United Auto Workers Union,
and they're out
here demonstrating,
trying to encourage
Fuyao employees
to vote "yes."
Fuyao released a statement earlier
saying that they believe the
United Workers Union is corrupted
and they hope that the
workers vote "no."
More than 1,500 workers
are expected...
We all have a
psychological shadow.
Fuyao doesn't want to be
controlled by the union.
As the Chinese saying goes,
"One mountain cannot
hold two tigers."
Voting just ended an hour ago.
Now the National
Labour Relations Board
is counting those votes
inside the plant
with both Fuyao and
UAW watching...
Yes.
We won by a landslide.
We won 60%?
Right.
We're awesome.
868 noes, 444 yes.
Yeah.
I wasn't shocked...
because I know the... the
young people got scared.
Them LRI people scared the
shit out of them, that's all.
Before we started
having those trainings,
I felt like there was
a big "yes" vote.
They spoke a lot about a strike,
and like, not being able to be
paid, unless we... You know.
So, I feel like people, you know,
are worried about their income.
Because I definitely
was, you know? So...
There you have it.
Overwhelming no.
Good morning, everyone.
Morning.
Last night I couldn't sleep
because I feel...
even more heavier
burden on my shoulder.
You guys gave me a chance
to make FGA better.
My goal is gonna work with
the team to make sure
every single issue I
cannot resolve overnight,
but give me some time.
Can we do this?
Yeah?
All right, one more
thing: life is short.
We're gonna select the best
ten employees go to China.
There's some pictures.
This is Shanghai.
Shanghai is the most
modern city in China.
Look like Manhattan, right?
It's like a Manhattan too.
Yeah, this is a Hyatt
Hotel. Hyatt Hotel.
They have a sky pool, 55 floor.
You swim in the sky.
And I'm gonna share the
good news for you.
One of you lucky guys,
you're gonna see that city.
We're one Fuyao, one family.
We create the miracle.
We need to create success forever.
Let's make American great again.
The smooth operation
of our US project
has laid a solid foundation
for our global strategy.
We've achieved double-digit
growth in operation management.
Both our earnings and profits
have reached new digits.
The China of my youth was poor
and undeveloped.
I feel I was happier then.
Now I live in a new era
of prosperity and modernity,
but I have a sense of loss.
I miss the croaking frogs and
chirping bugs of my childhood.
The wild flowers
blooming in the field.
In the past few decades, I
have built so many factories.
Have I taken the peace away and
destroyed the environment?
I don't know if I am a
contributor or a sinner.
But...
I only think that way
when I'm unhappy.
The point of living is to work.
Don't you think so?
Last Friday, I was
terminated from Fuyao
after two and a half years.
The excuse given
was I was too slow
pulling up something
on the computer.
Took me about two
or three minutes.
It wasn't quick enough.
I wouldn't take away the
last two and a half years.
I met a lot of good friends
and I learnt a lot
from the Chinese.
I don't have any food for you.
I have some watermelon
in my apartment.
I don't think he can eat fruit.
He can eat grass.
- Take care, guys.
- See you later.
- Bye, Wong.
- Bye-bye.
In the old days, all Chinese
people wanted in life
was to have enough food
and to raise their kids.
That's all they wanted.
When it comes to my
generation, we want it all.
We travel wherever we want
and buy whatever we like.
GM afforded me a great life...
that was cut off
when they closed the doors.
We will never ever make
that type of money again.
Those days are over.
There you go.
All right.
- Hey.
- Yay.
Well, I didn't even know.
You never give up on
the American dream.
To me, that would be un-American.
I can have that white fence.
I can have that nice home.
Send my children to college if
that's what they want to do.
Get treated with common decency.
You have to be able
to believe in it.
We used to have one person here.
Now we don't have anyone.
Next, I'm going to get rid
of four workers here.
Two for each line.
Automation means standardisation.
After we finish this,
we will have two fewer workers
uploading on the
encapsulation line.
The mechanical arms
do that instead.
You have already finished that?
Yes. These are all automatic.
And you're replacing the rest
with mechanical arms too?
Yes. I will replace the ones
on side-window tempering.
This one is being tested now.
We're hoping to cancel four
workers in July or August.
I'll change that
into machine work.
We can't get the work done
now. They are too slow.