I hate this.
Every year - every
year, it's like this.
Finally squeezed into
a train at union square.
Couldn't fall down if
you were shot. Come on.
It's impossible to catch a cab.
- Oh, Peter, Peter, Peter, Peter.
- Thank you.
- Yes.
Enjoy your day.
It's fashion week.
- Peter... embrace it. Come on. .
- Yeah.
There we go.
Excellent. Good.
All right.
Oh, no.
Yes, all right.
Let me help you here.
Squeeze.
We are supposed to be
interviewing our witness right now.
Peter, all right. Relax.
That's not gonna do it.
We're after an Israeli counterfeiter
- goes by the name of Ghovat.
We're going after "the ghost"?
We're going after the ghost.
What do you know about him?
I mean, this guy is nefarious.
I mean, counterfeit treasury bonds, dollars.
He's rumored to be the first guy to
crack the micro printing on the Euro.
Well, now we can add murder to that list.
Are you sure he called himself Ghovat?
Yes.
Okay. What happened?
I was at the party.
Why were you there?
Many models were invited.
It happened as I was leaving,
when I went for my coat.
I was in the back room when
the two men came in.
They were arguing.
They didn't see you?
I made sure to keep out of sight...
in the closet.
They... started shouting at each other.
Then, suddenly, everything
went... very... quiet.
The man who called himself Ghovat
- I heard him leaving.
When I walk out, that's
when I saw the other man.
He was on the floor, already... dead.
Okay.
Our men are gonna stay with you for now.
But if you need anything, day or
night, you feel free to call me.
If you heard this man again, do
you think you could identify him?
I will never forget his
voice as long as I live.
White Collar - Season 01 - Episode 02
Have you I.D.'d the dead guy?
Foreign national out of
Turkey, known associate of Ghovat.
Hmm, a falling-out over business.
Yeah, that's what I'm thinking.
My working theory
- this has something to do with fashion week.
Yeah, well, assuming our ghost has something
to sell, fashion week is a great cover.
He's got all his buyers in new York
this week, with no bells going off.
Unfortunately, we've got 30,000 buyers.
We've also got someone
who can identify his voice.
Are you gonna share?
You're gonna think I'm crazy.
It's never stopped you before.
- We throw a party.
- Is it your birthday?
- No.
- Then you're crazy.
Okay, look, okay?
Look at this.
Monte Carlo, Cannes, Ibiza, Rio -
this guy likes to have a good time.
- We put women, booze, fashion all together in
one spot - and what do we do, send him an E-vite?
He replies, "ghost plus one"?
No, we bring him to us.
We have Tara there
in the room, listening.
She can I.D. him.
- Got to party don't -
don't do this in the office.
A party?
The witness is confident she
can identify him by his voice.
How do you know he'll show up?
We fill it with beautiful women.
I was addressing my case agent.
Looking at his M. O. , He
has a thing for models.
Yeah? Well, me too.
Hey, Jones! You like models?
- Love 'em.
- Jones likes 'em, too.
Is there a plan in here somewhere?
Call me when one shows up.
Look. Caffrey, Ghovat - these
guys are cut from the same cloth.
Neal's convinced that
our ghost will show up.
I say we trust his
instincts on this one.
We've never been this close to Ghovat.
I'll authorize 5 grand for this party.
God, you know, 15 would be better.
- We'll make 5 work.
- Yes.
- And we'll get Elizabeth to help us.
- My wife?
She's an event planner
-best in the business.
She'll work with us on the price?
- My wife?
- Your wife.
His wife.
- Don't hit me.
- I'm sorry.
Royal Ossetra caviar.
This is gonna be perfect.
***
Neal, I just found spring bank.
Whiskey. Perfect.
I got a Garioch scotch over here.
'65?
No, '58.
Oh, grab the case.
All right, come on, we
got to itemize all this.
It's four bottles of scotch.
36 tins of Ossetra.
- Booze and fish eggs. You got that?
- ya
Drop the watch, convict.
We're not on a shopping spree.
No, it wasn't for me. It was for you.
Oh, thank you, but there's
nothing wrong with my old watch.
Honey, actually, that looks great on you.
Ah, a little out of my price range.
There's nothing wrong with enjoying
the good things in life, Peter.
Then why do they always seem
to end up in here?
Okay, so, we've got the
alcohol and the food covered.
Now we just need the venue.
Don't worry.
I got that covered.
It's a loft.
Seized in a D. E. A. Bust.
1, 500 square feet, service
elevator - it's perfect.
Is that chalk outline?
I'm sure they've cleaned that up by now.
It has everything you need.
Yeah, if five drunk frat buddies show up.
Aren't you supposed to
be lining up super models?
Ah, 64 and counting.
Oh, Neal Caffrey throws a
party, and 64 super models show up.
Oh, no, sorry, my mistake. My
mistake. 65, actually.
These two are twins.
Is that another one of your super models?
No, it's just a friend.
He's got a place we can use.
You think your friend's
place is better than mine?
Okay, it's better than mine.
Yeah.
Okay.
It's a lot better than mine.
Honey, I am really
impressed with this place.
I mean, I could have a
state dinner up here.
How did you pull that off?
He has a source.
But good luck trying to
pry it out of him.
Hmm, sounds like fun. I'll
work on him later.
She'll work on you later.
Okay, guys, I got 20 minutes to
get fiber optics in play.
I want a camera on every single entrance
and exit, starting with that one right there.
Okay. Let's go.
Hello. You're definitely in
the right place.
You're also a little early.
And you must be Neal Caffrey.
I am.
Would you mind waiting
inside for a little bit?
Actually, I think I'm
exactly where I'm supposed to be.
Then let me escort
you downstairs, at least.
You know, I got to say, I
expected a little more.
- I mean, you're charming enough, but...
- who invited you, again?
The agency.
I thought you were a model.
And I thought you were supposed to
be one of the smart ones.
Neal, this is agent Lauren Cruz.
I just had her transferred over.
She's gonna be keeping
an eye on you tonight.
So, where do you keep your gun?
All right.
Damn, Caffrey knows how to throw a party.
agent Burke.
- What?
- Hey, is that miss march?
Jones, pull it together.
Sports illustrated, not playboy.
Doing okay?
Come on.
I'm with the most beautiful girl
here. I want to see her smile.
Neal, straight ahead. Red
shirt, dark jacket.
Seems pretty jumpy for a guy to
be at a party filled with models.
So, let's mingle.
Excuse me.
Hi, I saw you looking around. Can
I help you find someone?
- I know almost everybody here except for you, Mr. , Uh...
- Dmitri.
Dmitri.
Write down that
name -"Dmitri.
" I'm just admiring the view.
Yeah, beautiful crowd, right?
Quite stunning
- Excuse me.
- Yes.
Hello.
No dice, Peter. Not our voice.
All right.
Wait. He's speaking Hebrew.
What's he saying?
He's saying, "I'm waiting. Where are you? "
Ghovat is here. He's watching him.
Ghovat's here.
Peter, he's here. He's
watching Dmitri right now.
I got it.
Back me up. I need you to flirt.
What?
- You're charming enough, right?
- yeah
That guy right there.
I'll be right back. Stay here.
I'm sorry.
- You just look really familiar.
- sorry.
- Oh, yeah.
- Do I know you from somewhere?
***
We need to leave.
Come.
- How are you? Have you met?
- No.
Hello.
You know, my friend here, Isabella, was
noticing how fantastic your suit is.
We have to leave, unfortunately, but
it was lovely to see you.
Have a good night.
Ah, well, I'm a model.
Where do you work?
Um, actually, you know what, I think
you're right. I think I don't know you.
I'm sorry.
There he is.
I got it, I got it! Bower, Whitman,
move in! Move in. Repeat
- move in. Now, now, now!
Get off me!
This is madness!
No, it's
-it's not him.
Peter, we got the wrong guy!
You're not getting this thing off me?
I'm working on it. You're lucky.
They have you on a 2-mile tether.
That's a lot in new York.
Remember jimmy Dimako?
The feds had his anklet set at 22 feet.
He had to take a shower with
one foot out of the tub.
- That's not true.
- Okay, maybe 30 feet.
But you have it better.
2 miles isn't enough, Moz.
I need to find Kate.
The man with the ring was
with Kate in California.
You tell me what he wants from her.
'Cause he didn't find what
he was looking for in San Diego.
How do you know what he was looking for?
Because I told Kate I
kept everything -
the money, the bonds, the
art, all of it - in San Diego.
Well, clearly, that's not the truth, because
you told me it was all hidden in Portland.
Isn't it? Isn't it?
Oh... there's nothing
hidden in either place, is there?
It's a test.
You told her San Diego.
You told me Portland.
Then whichever rock gets
overturned, you know who betrayed you.
Look, I just needed to
know what I already knew.
What, that you can trust me?
- Moz...
- that I'm the one who's been there through all of it?
But Kate - Kate's the
one who kicked over your rock.
Kate didn't betray me.
He forced her to.
Then why didn't Kate try to warn you when she
came to say goodbye to you that day in prison?
I think she might have, but
I was too stupid to see it.
Here.
"Weep for me, my love.
I'll miss you more
-" what is this?
It's just an old love letter. It
doesn't mean anything, okay?
But... the FBI was closing in on us.
***
We started taking precautions. We
started passing codes.
That could be cracked by anyone who's
ever seen the back of mad magazine.
Okay, you ask me why I don't tell you certain
things - it's that attitude right there.
I'm trying to be supportive.
Look, this was an early attempt.
Okay, we got more sophisticated as
the feds closed in.
So you think when Kate came to say goodbye
to you in prison, she left you a code?
Look, I need to see that security tape.
Your friend at the FBI has
access. He's seen it.
Oh, yeah, he's not just gonna hand it over.
You could... ask.
So, our ghost finally has a name.
It's Idil Hazeva.
Let's stick with "Ghovat"for now.
Do we know anything more about him?
Not much. No criminal record.
Name's not coming up on any of
our international watch lists.
We can't find him
registered anywhere in town.
Peter:Anything about the girl?
She's a model. We're looking at her.
What about Dmitri?
Andrei Dmitri, Uzbekistan national, linked
to a handful of enterprises -
uh, arms trading, money
laundering, prescription-drug fraud.
Exactly the kind of guy you'd
expect to show up at fashion week.
- Yeah.
- Does he still think he got away clean?
Uh, yeah. He slipped out the northwest
exit. Jones is sitting on him.
Tell Jones to keep his distance. I
don't want him getting tagged.
Let's see where this guy leads us.
Good work. We'll reconvene in an hour.
Nice report.
Thanks.
You know, you pull off the
whole FBI thing, too.
Yeah, no one looks good in FBI slacks.
Oh, don't sell yourself short.
Better.
- You sure I wasn't a little too direct and...
- yeah, but I like where you're going with it.
Where we headed for lunch?
Oh, uh, I'm gonna have to take a pass.
Elizabeth wants to meet me in the park.
Picnic. That's romantic.
Yeah, should I be worried?
Did you do something wrong?
- Probably.
- Show no fear.
Maybe she's just gotten
used to spending time with you.
You think?
- I'm not the best person to ask.
- Yeah.
Hey, Peter, before you
go... I need a favor.
Yeah?
The last time Kate visited me in prison, before
she disappeared -you saw that security tape?
Yeah.
I'd like to see it.
You think that's a good idea?
It's the last time I saw her.
I just want some closure.
Help me wrap up this case, and I'll
see what I can do about that tape.
This is nice.
Right?
This is really nice.
Yeah, it's great.
Honey, relax. You're not in trouble.
Oh, thank god.
Why do you think I asked you to lunch?
I don't know. That was what scared me.
Okay, hold on.
I got you something.
You did?
- What...
- here.
***
I noticed you were kind of looking at
that really nice watch at the warehouse.
It's not as nice, but it's close.
It's perfect.
- Yeah.
- Okay, try it on. Yes.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
- That's a different kind of...
- yeah, just...
- different kind of latch, there.
- Yeah, you go... There.
That's -
that's...
This is Burke. All
right, I'll be there at, uh...
I'll be therein five minutes. All right.
Look at that.
It works. It works.
- Looks good on you.
- Yeah.
What's going on?
They're moving me now.
What, protective custody?
No one's threatening you.
They're not taking any chances.
Came here to get an
agent, make contacts, not this.
Yeah. It's gonna be okay. All right?
If anybody can catch Ghovat, it's him.
Really?
He's the best.
Come here.
I just got word from Jones.
New watch.
Mm, yeah, gift from
Elizabeth. Thank you very much.
No sundial to clutter it up. Very nice.
What's Jones got?
- Dmitri is at a fashion show.
- Lucky him.
- And guess who's with him.
- Who?
Remember that model that
was with Ghovat last night?
However you got us
in, I don't want to know.
- That's our girl.
- That's our Dmitri.
Guy always looks like he's
waiting for something to happen.
Maybe he's waiting for Ghovat.
He lost his phone last night.
- If that was his only connection to him...
- figuring the only way back in is through the girl.
I'll buy that.
Want to go check it out?
No, I can't. I start flashing my
badge, they'll scatter like rats.
- You trust me?
- Nope.
Do you trust me to talk to Dmitri?
What are you thinking?
Stand there and look menacing.
- What?
- Stand there and look menacing.
No, Peter - "menacing" - you
look like your kid just struck out.
- What? This is menacing. What are you talking?
- No, it's not.
- It's menacing. It's menacing!
- That's not it.
Okay, that's it, right
there. Now cross your arms.
- What are you doing?
- I want to let him know you're packing.
Yeah.
Now say "I'll be back. "
No.
Yeah, Dmitri, right?
I never got your name.
No. You didn't.
What are you doing here?
Same thing you are.
Just waiting for a chance to
talk to our beautiful friend.
You enjoy the party?
A little too much
excitement for my taste.
Well, you know what they say.
It's not a party till
the police break it up.
Yeah, your little event may
have attracted the wrong element.
As a matter of fact, my phone was stolen.
That can make it tough to contact people.
But there are always ways to
get in touch with someone.
All right, let's cut the
act. We both know why we're here.
I don't know who you are, but
you're layout of your league.
This game takes way more than money.
You're not the only buyer
interested in what Ghovat is selling.
I'm the only one that matters.
You and your friend should take a walk.
He is definitely here to buy.
That girl could lead to
wherever Ghovat is staying.
I'll have Jones keep tailing them.
Hey, man, for the record, you're
much scarier than that other guy.
Much.
Looks like your boy Dmitri is
heading into a hotel on Madison.
Think he's staying there?
Well, he ain't bringing any
luggage with him.
Lock it down. Put somebody
on every exit. I'm on my way.
Gotcha.
- Anything?
- No.
He's been in there for... two hours.
- Nobody in or out?
- No, and I got two agents on every exit.
This is Burke.
Got a report of two
men arguing on the 50th floor.
Dmitri's on the 50th floor.
- Jones, get that room.
- Okay.
Damn it.
Sex games gone wrong?
No. Could just be a message.
- Maybe he was trying to shut him up.
- Yeah, but we don't even know if Ghovat was here.
No, our ghost was here.
The knife wound matches the blade width and angle of
penetration on our foreign national killed by Ghovat.
It's him.
Do we know how Ghovat
got out of the building?
Yeah. Found a service
elevator down the hall.
Wasn't on the reconstruction blueprints.
Which is exactly why
he picked this place.
Yeah, this guy is good.
Why a dress?
I don't know. It's
not off-the-rack.
There's no tag, which means it's couture.
We deal with a lot of knockoffs.
Ask me what I know about
a Prada bag sometime.
Oh, look at this.
There's a slit here.
It's about the size of an
electronic security strip.
A lot of the designers
are building them into the clothes.
So, basically, it's a
miniature flash drive?
Yeah, in theory, you could piggyback
up to 4 gigs on one.
Well, that's enough space to smuggle all
kinds of information worth killing for.
Lauren, uh... give me a photo book of all
the designers who had a show this year.
Let's find out who made this dress.
I don't know who this Ghovat is.
You don't know his name? Hmm?
Not even by rumor?
My world is fashion.
We both know we're not
talking about fashion.
I have a show this evening I
must be prepared for.
That's on hold.
- You have no reason for any of this.
- Actually, I do.
Can you explain why one of your
designs showed up at my murder scene?
You're the police. You tell me.
Whatever you did resulted in
the death of two people.
And if I didn't do it, my
son would be dead also.
All right, what happened?
A few hours before my team and
I are to leave tel Aviv,
my wife calls, tells me
that they have my son.
Ghovat kidnapped your child?
And then I was told to clear my
shop and wait for instructions.
And then he showed up, told me I had
to smuggle something into the states for him.
What was that something?
All I know is that it was in the dress.
That's it.
After we cleared U. S. Customs, I heard
from my wife that my son is returned to us.
All right, look, two people are dead because
of whatever you helped bring in the country.
Is there anything you
can tell me about it?
Well... ... I can show you the real dress.
That's it.
I always make two dresses.
I didn't tell him he took the wrong one.
That makes sense.
Dmitri shows up to get the dress from
Ghovat and finds out it's a fake.
They struggle, Ghovat
manages to make it out alive.
So why kill him and bring all that heat?
He's trying to salvage the deal but can't if Dmitri is
running around telling everybody the technology is no good.
What do you think is on this thing?
Could be launch codes, covert I. D. , The
formula for new coke -who knows?
But our technology guy swill have an
answer for us by tomorrow morning.
I don't know. Something that valuable - there's
no way Ghovat's gonna pack it up and go home.
I've got a thought.
Let's take our thread and go fishing.
How could you be so stupid?
Ghovat, please, you have to believe me.
I didn't know what you wanted me to do.
You - you didn't
want me to know.
Where's the dress now?
It's gone. I sold it.
You sold the dress?
My dress?
Someone made an offer ahead of the show.
He bought it for his fiancé.
How much did he pay?
$50, 000.
Who did you sell it to?
How long will we have to keep this up?
Just long enough to get
noticed. You're doing great, Tara.
I'll be doing better once this is over.
That dress really does
look fantastic on you.
If only I could wear it on a runway.
There's nothing to say you won't someday.
Can I get you a drink?
- New watch?
- Yeah.
Excuse me, sir?
This just arrived for you.
Hello?
I recognize you from the party.
- Who is this?
- I saw you steal Dmitri's phone.
Yeah, I was trying to
eliminate the competition.
Guess it worked.
So you know what you have?
I know exactly what I got.
You paid $50, 000for the
dress. I'll give you$5 million.
Aw, my fiancé loves it so
much, how about we make it 10?
Do you know who you're talking to?
- This is Steve, right?
- I tried to be nice.
I tried to give you a choice.
Nothing on the phone.
It's a burner.
You can pick up one of
these at any corner deli.
Prints?
It's clean.
- Agent Burke
- What's up?
We had two plain clothes taking Tara home.
Somebody got to
them about a half-hour ago.
Got to them how?
Blasted the car to hell.
Fortunately, our guys were wearing vests.
- What about Tara?
- They grabbed her, got away clean.
I have your girl.
What's the dress worth to you now?
So, now what?
You want the girl, I want the dress.
Trade?
Where and when?
I'm not interested in meeting with you.
Then who?
Agent Peter Burke.
Why him?
Because it's really the
FBI that holds the dress.
Is he there now?
It's for you.
This is Burke.
Yes, I'm sure you
heard everything earlier.
You want me to make the exchange.
That's right. I won't waste my
time telling you to come alone.
Just make sure to bring the real dress.
If it's not, are you
gonna make me eat it?
That's funny. Keep this phone on you.
You'll meet me at the central park
band shell tomorrow afternoon at 4:00 P. M.
Plenty of time for you to
get your men into position.
You have to let me go to the exchange.
It's my fault Tara is in trouble.
I'm the one who paraded
her around town in that dress.
The best thing you can do is help me
figure out what Ghovat's game plan is.
He knows we're gonna
have the place staked out.
He knows you're running a playbook.
Right, so I'm gonna toss the
old one, come up with a new one.
No. No, you don't. That's the point.
See, he's counting on
the FBI to have a plan.
So I do nothing?
Go with him.
Like you would?
If he expects you to
have a plan, don't have one.
Oh, that's the worst idea ever.
Prepare all you can. Just
know it's all gonna change.
What would you do?
Go home and have dinner with my wife.
You meet this guy in central park and you
give him the dress and he gives you the girl?
That's about the size of it.
I'm re ally glad you got into the white-collar crime
division, where nothing exciting happens.
It's -it's
pretty dull stuff.
Yeah.
Um, I got you another present.
Honey, not another one.
I-I'm enjoying my first one. Don't...
it's my old watch.
But I-I-I-I
love my new one.
Come on, honey, it's - it's big, it's
clunky, it moves around your wrist, and -
I mean, it's beautiful, but...
it's not you.
Take this.
I need you to be agent
Peter Burke tomorrow.
And this -
this is you.
Besides, um, when all this is over with, I
need you home at 6:00right on the dot.
Thank you.
And Ghovat wants the dress because
it's been tagged with a security device.
We cracked the thread this morning.
It's holding the holographic code
of the latest European currency seal.
We're using a counterfeit code. We're hoping
he won't be able to tell the difference.
But if he does, this could go south fast.
We're putting this girl's life at risk.
We could put the entire
monetary system of Europe at risk.
Guess who wins.
I'll be running point - we've have eyes
in the air, plainclothes on the ground.
Cruz, Jones, you're with me.
Burke, you know what you got to do.
Caffrey, put your hand down.
Put it down!
I'm just wondering where I'll be.
On a coffee run. You're not
even supposed to be here.
Any questions?
Then let's get into position.
- Are we good to go?
- We are good.
Okay, people, let's do this.
Can I come in?
Get in here!
Close the door.
You're right on time.
I like to be punctual.
Well, that's one thing we have in common.
I don't see you.
Of course you don't.
He's signaling us.
555-3147.
He's giving us Ghovat's incoming
phone number. Get me a trace.
Yep, I'm on it.
Good, Peter.
How do I know you have the girl?
I want to hear her voice.
Agent Burke?
Tara, are you okay?
Bethesda fountain. That's 300 yards.
You've got one minute.
If I see any of your agents or
unmarked vehicles move, the girl's dead.
Your time starts... now.
Everyone stay where you are! Stay down!
Everybody hold their positions.
We still got him on GPS, right?
Yeah.
- Just stay down! Stay down! Stay there!
- Standing down.
Go get the dress.
If you'll notice, agent Burke, I've added a little fashion
accessory of my own to our model friend here.
The belt is lined with plastique.
I dial a number here...
and she goes "boom.
" Give her the dress.
Toss it.
Please don't try anything.
I have five bar sand free long distance.
I can be far away and
still cause you pain.
Let him walk.
Even if he's bluffing, we
can't take the chance.
Yes?
Hey, is this Steve?
What's up, buddy? You never call.
Son of a bitch.
All right, keep calling. Jam his
phone so he can't trigger the bomb.
Keep calling him!
Hey, Cruz... stay with Caffrey.
Everybody else, keep dialing.
Jam the phones!
Keep calling him!
We're jamming his call. Get
the belt off of her.
Do it, do it!
Come on. Hold still.
Damn it.
Hey, Steve!
Now what?
That is pretty damn charming.
That's it. Good!
Everybody clear the area now!
Get down. Get down, get down!
You're actually doing the
whole hero thing.
Yeah.
Yeah, they're gonna write
songs about this.
Nice.
You okay?
Area is contained. Bomb
squad is on the way.
I swept the leg. He went down.
- You did?
- Excellent.
You don't look dirty.
Yeah, well... I know what I'm doing.
It was nice of your FBI
friend to give you this.
There's no sound. Why
are you shushing me?
Okay.
Does she always wear
her hair parted that way?
Yeah, I'm way past that.
Wait.
Her scarf is forming the letter "M.
13th letter in the alphabet. 13 is a prime.
Thanks... rain man.
Do you want my help?
There it is. There it is.
How's your Morse code?
"b"... "o"... double "t"..."l"..."e".
"bottle"