Morning, sunshines.
Coffee.
What do we got? We got any headlines?
Not much, although they
keep bitching about his bible.
Could be a debt ledger.
Well, whatever it is, it's
missing, and they ain't happy about it.
Hey, guys, we have a situation.
Is that Barelli?
What's he doing down here?
I don't know, but it can't be good.
That's Paul Ignazio, his
nephew. Here, turn the mike up.
Damn his walking over here
You guys are the FBI, right?
We need your help.
Last week, somebody walks into
my church...steals the bible.
A bible?
An actual bible?
Yeah, you know - the flood, Abraham
sacrifices Isaac. You heard of it?
Why do you want our help?
I'm a taxpaying citizen.
So? File a police report.
Come on, Burke.
You got your guys sitting on me.
It's part of the game, I know, but it means that
I'm not free to...uh, find out who did this.
Yeah, it means you're not
free to bust heads until you do.
Do I have to take these accusations?
Get to your point.
This bible -it's not just some book
that the Gideons leave on the nightstand.
This - this is five
centuries of history from Naples.
The saints prayed over this book.
Your personal feelings for Barelli aside, I don't
need the archdiocese crawling down our necks
because we refused to
help recover a medieval bible.
Fine.
But if Barelli asked for our
help, he must really want it back.
All right, let's get this straight, here.
You may go to confession once a
week, but the bureau doesn't forgive sins.
We don't work for you.
What do you want?
Shut down your book making operations
at Masso's club.
Masso's.
It's a restaurant.
See for yourself anytime...
after Thursday.
Please.
Please help me find my goddamn bible.
Please stop.
It's part of my process.
Look, either you taught her too
well, or it's just a bottle.
It's more than that.
There's a message here.
Hello?
Yeah, peter. I'll be down in 5.
Oh, okay. I'm coming right now.
Oh, the man interferes yet again.
- Can you
please -yes.
I'll take it back to
the lab, run some tests.
You don't have a lab. You
have a storage unit.
Semantics.
Thanks, Moz.
White collar - Season 01 - Episode 03
The bible belonged to the church of
saint Camillus De Lellis in Naples.
It was brought here in 1903.
It's been the heart of our parish.
Now this.
No alarm, no witnesses, no
sign of a forced entry.
It looks like a smash-and-dash.
Anything unusual that night, father?
No, not that I recall.
Have E.R.T. Run the prints
against the parish roster.
Something tells me
we'll get a few matches.
Nobody from this
parish stole that bible.
Oh, sure. You guys are all
choirboys, right, Barelli?
No surveillance cameras.
The lord sees all.
And that's good enough for us.
Maybe I'm getting my st. whatevers mixed up, but
didn't you used to run a soup kitchen here?
Not anymore.
Who steals a bible?
People steal everything.
Why would we steal one?
Just in theory. Uh, they're rare.
Yeah, it makes them
valuable, but not like a Picasso.
It's definitely niche markets.
Tough to fence.
People get weird about buying
stolen religious artifacts.
I think it's an irony thing -
that pesky eighth commandment.
Yeah, thou shalt not steal.
Well, it depends what's
important to people.
Did you know that an original "Star
Trek" dome lunch box goes for 600 bucks?
I don't try to explain it.
No, I-I can appreciate
that, but why this one?
Well, your missing book is famous.
It's known as the healing bible.
Really? Attribution.
I-in 1588, the plague
passed through Naples.
Father Camillus carried the book into
disease-stricken ships in the harbor.
Not a single person who
touched the bible died.
Good story.
20 years later, a blind girl regained her
sight when she rescued the book from a fire.
I could give you many more examples.
No, I-I'm sure you could.
Look, maybe you don't
steal it for the money.
Maybe you steal because
you're a true believer.
- True believer?
- You got something better?
Every person in that
church has a felony record.
The only people I don't
suspect are the ones in prison.
So, let's start with the faithful.
It cures blind nuns and lepers.
Sounds like every
story in Sunday school.
Okay. Look at this.
In 1918, 30, 000 people in new
York died from the Spanish flu.
No one in this parish even caught a cold.
Maybe whoever took it thinks
it's gonna heal them.
It's worth looking into.
- Nobody in this church got the flu?
- It's true.
Why these guys and not the
church down the block?
Because of a book?
Tough to swallow.
- I thought you were catholic.
- Lapsed.
So you don't think some higher power
could have saved the congregation?
Oh, I'm more inclined to think they kept
the doors shut and loaded upon vitamin C.
Maybe god works with what he's got.
And god said, "shut thine
door sand eat thine oranges"?
Why not?
All right, look.
When they dug up king tut, everybody made such
a big deal out of the curse of the pharaoh.
Yeah, two dozen people who entered
the tomb ended up dead.
Yeah, they probably caught some
old bacterial infection.
Germs - there's your
divine intervention.
God can't use bacteria?
I prefer my miracles with a
little more smiting and lightning.
Priest:Can I help you?
Thanks for seeing us, father.
We wanted to run down one thing.
You didn't tell us your bible
was also known as a healing bible.
I didn't think it was relevant.
Could be.
Was there anybody in your church who is a true
believer of the healing power of the bible?
Someone who was terminally ill?
Someone who had a sick family member?
I was afraid this might happen.
What?
Mr. Barelli has discouraged the
homeless from the church.
He made you shut down the soup kitchen.
How Christian of him.
The night of the theft, I let a
homeless man sleep in the sanctuary.
His name's Steve.
Is he sick?
No. But someone very close to him is.
Steve?
Uh, my name is peter.
This is my friend Neal.
You mind if we ask you some questions?
The church you stayed in last
week - they're missing a bible.
You know anything about it?
Yeah, I-I took it.
Great.
We need it back.
No. No, i need it back.
What do you mean? Where is it?
I took it from the
church like he asked me to.
Now, he said that he would show
me how to help Lucy get better.
Then he took it from me.
Now, he has not brought it back.
Do you know where he is?
No. I wish I did.
Who asked you to take
the bible from the church?
Look, he said that he
would help Lucy get better.
She's not getting
better, okay? She's getting worse.
What's wrong with her?
She's tired all the time.
S-she don't eat nothing.
Now, if I could get that
bible back, she'll get better.
The man who asked you to take the
bible - did you meet him at the church?
Yeah.
Steve, if we showed you some pictures, do
you think you could recognize him?
We just need to get the bible back, okay?
'Cause she's fading, all right?
You okay to keep going?
What?
There's more of them?
Yeah. Let's, uh, just get
through this one, okay?
Glad we followed your hunch. I
hope it takes us somewhere.
O ye of little faith.
Been waiting all day to trot that one out, huh?
Been holding onto it since lunch.
Um, I'm gonna be right back, okay?
- That bad, huh?
- Yeah, "that bad" was about an hour ago.
Just give me the damn thing.
No luck, huh?
No, not -not
really, no.
Look, um...I'm sorry I'm
not more help to you.
My bell got rung pretty good in Fallujah.
You were in Iraq?
Yeah.
T-that's where I found Lucy.
We called in this predator
strike on this trigger house.
Two hellfires came in...
...and just destroyed everything.
Then I hear this little whimpering, so...
I lift up this piece of roof, and
there she was, just wagging her tail.
Well, you think you could
look at one more book?
Yeah.
Okay, the rest of you go over there, make
sure NYPD doesn't touch anything.
Let's go get peter.
What's going on?
- One of Barelli'sen just got shot.
- Who?
Paul Ignazio, Barelli's number two.
Barelli's nephew.
- That's him.
- Who?
That's the guy that
asked me to take the bible.
That's our boy.
Close range.
No eyewitnesses.
Body's not waterlogged, so it's...
fresh.
. 25-caliber casing. European gauge.
It's a . 22-caliber.
This is Brooklyn, buddy, not Bavaria.
Pete Burke.
This is a homicide, not an art
exhibit. What are you doing here?
Ruiz, I see they let
you out of your cubicle.
Yeah. This is my shore now.
Where's your pet convict?
I left him in the car with
the windows cracked.
What are you doing at my crime scene?
This tails into my case.
This is mob retaliation.
It's my investigation now.
You don't believe me, ask Hughes.
Don't -don't
start with me.
You've got ruiz running organized crime?
That's unbelievable.
We offer you that bump every
year. Every year, you turn it down.
This isn't
mob-on-mob.
The bible's the key to this thing.
All you got is a homeless guy with a spotty memory who
thinks Ignazio may have enticed him into stealing the bible.
What we got here is a dead member of the
Barelli family probably killed by the Morettis.
All right, fine.
I'll stay out of the
active investigation.
Just let me take a look at
whatever's on that body.
It's Ruiz's case, and he's not comfortable
sharing intel while Caffrey's with you.
- Oh, come on.
- He's a convicted felon, peter.
And Ruiz isn't the only
one with reservations.
- All right,
- well...plenty of other cases on your sheet.
Let organized crime handle this one.
We're off the case. We've
been asked to step down.
You think this is a
retaliation killing by the other family?
I don't think Paul would have met a Moretti alone by
this river, not with all the bad blood in the water.
- Now, if Ruiz is right...
- that a Moretti killed him?
We may be sitting on
the edge of a mob war.
So, what do we do?
I can't do much of anything.
Ruiz is not willing to
share the case file.
So, where's that leave us?
Like I said, i can't do much of anything.
I'm getting a little chilly by
this water, aren't you?
Think I could borrow your jacket?
I swear to you, peter, under no
circumstance swill I impersonate the FBI.
Where do you think you're going?
This is Paul ignazio's apartment, right?
Hi, uh, Ted Jefferson from
the evidence recovery team.
I don't care if you're thomas
Jefferson. I need I. D.
Oh, sorry.
I pulled a double-hommy last night.
It's in the van.
My partner took it to
see his girlfriend in queens.
Not my problem, brother.
Look, I just need a urine
swab from the Vic's toilet.
If I don't get it soon, it'll spike
the cross-reactivity, and then -
I got orders, too, pal. No I. D. , No pee.
Oh, I know. You can get it.
It's easy.
All you got to do is swab around the rim of
the toilet, then drop the swab into the tube,
screw the cap on the
tube, and, bam, we're good to go.
No way. I'm not doing that.
Okay.
Now it's your problem.
- Yeah, cap. I got a local hero by
the name of - okay, okay, pee boy.
- Get it yourself.
- Oh, it turns out the hero's on our side.
Never mind.
Any problems getting in?
None. He thinks I'm swabbing toilets.
I figure we've got about 10
minutes until he gets curious.
Why, is that the
standard toilet-swabbing time?
Yes, that's exactly what it is.
You know, you look pretty
comfortable in that FBI windbreaker.
Maybe it's time to
consider a new career path.
Nope. I prefer to keep my soul.
What are we looking for?
Paul convinced our homeless
guy to steal a bible.
I want to know why, I want to know who killed
him, and I want to know if they're related.
He was researching something.
Hundred years' war, the crusades.
Illuminated manuscripts.
Illuminated...-
do you know the name maria Fiametta?
Doesn't ring a bell. Who is she?
Art historian, Brooklyn state.
Serendipity - Paul had an
appointment at Brooklyn state.
You find anything?
Neal:Your hunch was right. Ruiz
is on the wrong trail.
And how did you learn this?
- A friend. The same
friend who - same guy.
He's real. I'm not making him up.
Oh, I know he's real.
How much do you know?
Enough. What'd you find?
A professor who writes about
the black market -
Sicilian grave robbers, Egyptian
smugglers, and Serbian mobsters.
I mean, you can't run with those crowds unless
you're willing to get dirt under your nails.
- What's his name?
- Her name is maria Fiametta.
A woman.
A regular "Cindiana" Jones.
- Do you want Togo meet her?
- Yeah, I think I do.
You gentlemen are with the FBI?
Yes, we're hoping you can
help us out on this one.
We're working on a stolen bible.
Show her.
Thank you, agent...?
Neal Caffrey.
That's funny. There's a very talented manuscript
forger also named Neal Caffrey.
How talented?
You're him.
And you're with the FBI?
It's...sort of a work release.
I have to ask - um, is it true
that the Vinland map is yours?
How could it be?
But if it is a forgery, it's spectacular.
How about we get back to
my current problem?
A pre-renaissance bible
stolen from a church in Brooklyn.
It's...very beautiful, but
it's not a bible.
It's not?
Pre-renaissance, yes, uh, but
it's too small to be a bible.
Then it's a book of hours.
Most likely, yes. In the Italian style.
It's a large prayer book.
To show their devotion, monks and nuns had to recite the
psalms, hymns, or chants at specific times all day long.
- Sunday school.
- Lots of Sundays.
This is a particularly nice example.
Paul Ignazio thought so, too.
- Sorry?
- Do you know him?
- No.
- We believe he stole it.
Oh, well, I hope you catch him.
Can't -
he's dead.
Looks like a mob hit, but we're still
hoping to figure out who took the book.
I'd love to know. It's quite beautiful.
Here's my card. If you hear
anything or come across anyone
- who's looking to buy or sell something like that...
- I will call you.
- Thank you
- It's a pleasure.
If you are ever in the mood to
discuss medieval manuscripts -
oh, you'd be surprised how
often I'm in the mood for that.
Was this just an
exercise in schadenfreude?
Because you win. It's just a bottle, man.
The lab needs to re-examine its work.
The lab went over every
inch of that thing.
Fingerprints, chemicals, black
light - nothing.
I even tested the remnants of the
wine left in the bottle, which,
by the way, was a very lovely
boxed franzia from early October.
Oh, your FBI friend keeps
you on a tight leash.
All right, look, keep
looking, Moz. Something's there, okay?
She's lying about Paul, and she's two degrees away from our homeless guy,
but I also have trouble buying the fact that
an attractive history professor offed a mobster.
No, you don't want me to see the missing
inventory because if I come down there,
there's gonna be a lot
more missing than centerpieces.
You got that?
Okay, maybe it's not a complete stretch.
Hey, guys.
Sorry. Um, it was just my vendor.
No, it's fine.
We were just trying to decide if
a woman is capable of murder.
Oh, I think so.
What's the issue?
I-I think we're
dealing with a shell game.
Visual aids. Nice.
Big gulp is Paul, dead mob guy.
Coffee cup is Steve, our homeless vet.
Mug is maria.
Napkin's the bible.
Make maria the saltshaker.
Maria's the mug. Watch.
We'll start with
Paul, who, for some reason,
reads maria's book and realizes that the
healing bible is worth a hell of a lot of cash.
But it's also Barelli's pride and joy.
He doesn't want to risk Barelli's wrath, so
he gets...Steve to steal the bible.
Plausible deniability.
But if it doesn't work, then he
let's the homeless guy take the fall.
Well, that's evil.
Takes the bible from Steve, calls maria
to make the deal. Something happens.
Yeah, the deal goes down wrong, or Paul
decides he wants both the cash and the book.
Well, whatever it is, Paul ends up dead, the
bible goes missing, Steve never even met maria.
And our girl walks away
clean with a very expensive book.
Okay, how'd you do that?
Never reveal your secrets.
Well, how do we get maria to reveal hers?
Well, if I stretch it, I might be able
to get a warrant to get into her place.
You know, if she's smart. She's not gonna
have that bible anywhere close to her.
El, I've never seen this devious side.
Don't cross me.
Elizabeth's right about the
bible. She won't keep it close.
I've got it. She knew who you
were -Neal Caffrey, master forger.
- Alleged.
- Alleged. Whatever.
If she's got the book, it
links her to the murder.
She's gonna want to get rid of it.
We've got all the usual channels locked
down, but if she thinks you might be interested...
convince her I'm pliable.
We find some street contacts, float it out
that old Neal Caffrey is back in business.
No, that could take time to reach
her, and there's no guarantee.
Why don't you just ask her out?
That could work. Think she'll say yes?
- Yes. - I
could prob-
to history, old and new.
How does an FBI agent get a table
here? It's like a six-month wait.
Oh, an FBI agent doesn't.
Don't forget -I
had a previous life.
Oh, yeah.
Do you believe in reincarnation?
You could say that.
How about you?
Who were you in your previous life?
Same person I've always
been...with '90s hair.
I doubt that.
- Let me see your lifeline.
- No.
Come on, it'll - it'll
help fill in the blanks.
You're not seriously gonna
read my palm right now, are you?
Calluses.
Not afraid to get dirty.
Well, that's true.
What else?
No ring. Between that and the calluses, I'm
guessing work gets in the way.
Not a ring for you, either.
Yeah. Prison got in the way.
So, it must be weird for
you -working for the FBI.
I don't know.
It's always interesting to read
from the other team's playbook.
The other team? I thought you
were out of the game.
Oh, I am.
Retired and rehabilitated.
Have you found your missing bible?
Not yet.
You know anyone who wants to buy one?
Maybe.
Looters approach me all the time. So
do buyers. It's a very attractive offer.
It sure is.
- Uh, judge Rattigan faxed the warrant.
- Excellent.
All right, Neal's got orders to keep her
away from her home for at least an hour.
- Can you bypass the alarm?
- Two minutes.
Let's do it.
- Surprise me.
- Oh, you sure?
I might order something you don't
like, and then where would we be?
I trust you.
After all, you work for the FBI.
More wine?
Now you read minds?
The question is, do you?
Clinton: It's not bad for
a college professor, huh?
Yeah, well, she's either a
crook or a trust-fund baby.
Yeah, maybe it's both.
- They usually are.
- Nice catch.
Yeah, not a bad place to
drop a bug, either.
Yeah. Yeah, yeah. It's good
coverage. Let's do it.
She's bringing him back here for dessert.
Of course she is.
Oh, you jealous you
ain't getting any of it?
Neal? No.
I'm perfectly fine with the stale-ass coffee I have in the van, thank you.
- Good?
- Yeah, we're good.
Careful, Lauren. Don't
spill that stale-ass coffee.
It's a bug. I can hear.
They're home. Roll tape.
After you.
Some wine?
Why not?
So...what shall we talk about?
There's this story about these two
spies, a French duke and an Italian count.
They're sworn enemies who spent the
whole year trying to trick each other,
but on new year's eve, they got to ask one
question that the other had to answer truthfully.
Yes.
The trick was asking the right question
because you may never get another chance.
I've always said honesty is
a more challenging game.
"Honesty is a more challenging game"?
Geez, how come my
dates don't go like this?
Because you don't say things
like, honesty is a more challenging game.
That's because nobody actually talks like that.
They do in Neal Caffrey's world.
This wine needs to breathe.
I'm gonna get a decanter.
Why don't you put some music on?
What are you in the mood for?
- Oh, you know...
- surprise you.
10 years painting the same bible.
It's like stalking god.
If it weren't for the monk's
devotion, we would have lost one
of the most significant works
of Greek literature forever.
Stunning.
I agree.
You know what?
I don't trust you.
Smart.
I wouldn't trust me, either.
I think we have a technical problem.
That's one way of putting it.
Let's play the spies game.
- I'll ask you a question...
- and I have to tell you the truth?
And you have to tell me the truth.
Okay. Make it a good one.
Which Neal caffrey are you?
Are you working for the good guys...
or are you working a bigger game?
What happened?
Neal happened.
Did I answer your question?
Maybe.
The feds linked Barelli's bible to Paul Ignazio, and
you to Paul through his visits to the college.
Look, maria, I'm living proof. If
the feds want something from you,
they'll turn your
life inside out to get it.
They'll tell Barelli you have his book.
Even if I don't?
I can get you $250, 000in two days.
It is worth a lot more than that.
Not if you're in prison or dead.
Between the FBI and the
mob, there's no way you can move it.
I can.
The other team's playbook.
If I shouldn't risk it, why are you?
Won't they send you back for good?
I'm already in prison.
We have a deal?
How did you know she was in on it?
Lucky hunch.
- Ruiz?
- I checked Paul's credit.
He got wired 10 g's from a shell corporation
in Gibraltar owned by your lady professor.
Oh, by the way, how'd last
night's fishing go? Get any tape?
Equipment failure. But
Caffrey says she has the book.
She'll sell, but only to him.
Of course he'd say that. The terms?
$250, 000 wired to a swiss account.
No way. What if he cuts a deal with
her, he runs away with the book?
- What choice do we have?
- We don't.
I don't need another dead body
washing up in the east river.
We'll set up a dummy account.
It's risky. What if she
takes a shot at Neal?
I wouldn't lose any sleepover it.
Morning, guys.
Everybody sleep okay?
Cayman's first national.
I'll e-mail you the
pin right before the buy.
First they're sending me back to prison, tomorrow they're giving
me a quarter million taxpayer dollars in an offshore account.
Guess that shows how
much confidence they have in you.
And how much I have in you.
Morning.
You're up early.
Couldn't sleep.
Big day.
I can tell.
You're wearing your lucky tie.
Hey, did you find the bible?
Yeah. The professor had it.
Neal's gonna buy it back.
You're giving him money.
No wonder
-lucky tie.
No way. We set up a fake wire transfer.
Then what are you worried about?
He has to convince her that he's working
us, which means he has to cut his anklet for real.
The book's worth a
fortune. He could run with it.
Well You have a lot more faith in
a ratty, old tie than you do Neal.
Yeah, well, this ratty, old tie's never
forged a priceless map of Vinland.
Why is it so hard for you to believe
that he'll do the right thing?
Let's just say that's
not his first instinct.
And trust isn't yours.
Occupational hazard.
I like to know I can count on something.
I know you do.
But sometimes you just
have to take a leap of faith.
Ruiz: Look at him.
Son of a bitch should be in
leg-irons if you ask me.
Nobody asked you, Ruiz.
He conned you, too, Pete, huh?
Here she comes.
We have a chaperon.
White van over my left shoulder.
What happened to not
mixing business with pleasure?
That's for us. He's patting her down.
I need a cigarette after that pat-down.
- You're clean.
- Thank you.
Your turn.
Well, what is that?
She making sure that's
not a gun in his pocket?
No bugs.
So Where's my money?
Where's my book?
You ready?
When I cut the anklet, our friends
in the van are gonna know I'm running.
Can you lose them? 'Cause
I'm not going back in.
-I've been chased by the carabinieri, drug
cartels in Bogotá * - I get it. You're good.
With all due respect, Neal...
we could make quite a fine pair.
With all due respect, maria, shut up and drive.
He cut the tracker.
Right on schedule.
- Oh, you knew about this?
- Of course.
He had to convince
her he's rigging the system.
What if he really is?
There are a dozen unmarked in the area.
NYPD has eyes in the sky.
There's nowhere to hide. Let's go!
I can't believe I'm doing this.
I spent a long time looking for her.
I guess it wasn't meant to be.
It's calfskin vellum. The
abyssus perfidia.
Golden chalice of Paul.
You satisfied?
Very.
***
It's a pleasure doing business with you.
You'll never know how much
pleasure it could have been.
You know, I had a feeling all that
lovey-dovey stuff last night was B. S.
Next time you should
trust your instincts.
I did.
Clip. Lifted it when I patted you down.
You forgot about the one in the chamber.
Damn it. I've never been a gun guy.
Give me the book, Neal.
Sorry.
You gonna take me on, it's
gonna cost you a small fortune.
What's the matter? You can't do it?
Is it 'cause of the money or the history?
- I think you know the answer to that.
- Is that why you killed Paul?
Paul decided that he
wanted the money and the book.
Yeah, that's what
happens when you get greedy.
Drop the gun!
Gun down or we shoot!
Put the gun down!
Right now -put the gun
down, your hands behind your head.
Man down. Man down!
Cut it a little close there, pal.
Guess the big guy had your back, huh?
Well, I'll tell you one
thing. You made Lauren's day.
Yeah, not Barelli.
How did you and your cub
scouts find out about this?
NYPD?
I got one of those police
scanners. It's a hobby.
**
She's Paulie's shooter?
Some kind of lover's quarrel?
Just business.
I hate to break it to you, but your nephew
decided to freelance behind your back.
Oh, that's sad, you know. You can't
trust family, who can you trust?
So, if you guys are done, I'd like my
bible back. Mass starts in one hour.
Would it kill you to say
thank you? Huh? Would it?
Yeah, I guess it would. All
right, just give it to him, man.
- What?
- What do you mean, what?
Give him the bible.
I gave it to some FBI guy.
"Some FBI guy"?
You think you can get over on me?
You'll wish you were never born, pal.
Yeah, I seem to be getting this
speech a lot lately.
- Just shut up.
- No,
no, I'm not gonna let this go.
Where is it, Caffrey?
I'll let Barelli give you a ride home.
Look, I'm telling you guys. I don't know.
I know where it is.
Hey, pally.
What are you doing with my bible?
She would have died without it.
Not so fast, wacko.
You knowhow you're messing with?
You've got it, Barelli. Just
leave him alone.
No, I'm not gonna let this go.
Hey, sweet girl.
Her name's Lucy.
Lucky Lucy.
She don't look so good. What's
the matter with her?
She's been sick...until today.
I got this vet in Yonkers.
He saved my pugs from diabetes.
Want to take a ride, go see
him, have her checked out?
- I was gonna give it back after...
- I know.
How'd you know?
Okay, I didn't know, but I took a leap
of faith that you did the right thing.
- Elizabeth.
- Yeah.
I told you it's a healing bible.
- Oh, here we go.
- No way.
Barelli's a softy for dogs.
Oh, not enough smiting and
lightning for you?
That's not a miracle.
Come on.
It's not a parting of the red sea.
Well, I'll take my
miracles where I can get them.
- Can we have the honors?
- Yes, sir.
She's back.
Hey, is that my jacket?
He works in mysterious ways.
Mozy, look at. Moz.
Mozy!
Let me see your warrant.
What?
Come here.
Lemon juice in the canlde.
How did I miss this?
- Weren't you ever a boy scout?
- Oh. I got kicked out.
Pinewood derby, magnets,
it was a whole... thing.
It's a map.
Of New York City subway.
What do you think it means?